Seekers and survivors
Tonight it's best a minute, they're smiling
No horns, no pitchfork, no open hate
Just vibes, questions and a cool bond for betrayal
Da-de-na-na, da-de-na-na, da-de-na-na, da-de-na-na
As you want the tea, the keys, the coast, the private plane, the hidden roads
Not here to heal, not here to build, just here to see where the armor peeled
Too many questions, not enough soul, too much sugar in the casserole
Too much on neutral, too much on good, too much small
First they flatter, then they pry Who said what with the saintly eye?
Not to stir things, that old routine Meanwhile they mop the floor with kerosene
They whisper here, then drift right there Dropping concern like polluted air
Person A gets a spiced up quote Person B gets a soft to know
mess appears always so shocked with crocodile tears always protecting always concerned
funny how
Package, truth, then sell the stain
Danger two, they split the crew
Make folks doubt what they already knew
Danger three, they bait reaction, then point and scream
Look bad attraction, oh sweetheart, you built amaze
Now you're acting scared of the fire you raise
Danger four, they drain your heart
Double your focus part by part
Not always trying to win the war
Sometimes they just wanna wreck the...
A priest in style won't hug you close while sharpening lies
A real friend comes, a fake one stirs a real friend
As a fake one, there's a real friend who keeps the chamber sealed
A fake one wants your wounds revealed
So if they rush like destiny's clone, with hungry eyes and a borrowed tone
Don't hand them candles, keys or gold, some demons freeze when the door gets closed
But detrol, but detrol, cheap little ghoul in a satin robe
Moonwalks lick through the loophole, till the light
No more entry, not at all
The truth is harder than the mirror ball
Truth a yard, out your roll
Exit left, little buddy trolls
Smile all you want
We know the roll case closed on a buddy troll
Good man, man, it's not charging for some reason
Nick you know what you get your mod back since I can do it. I'll do it. Okay
Because Nick did a really cute picture today
Yeah, oh
I know I don't think you're talking about that because he knew like sometimes I'll say things it is a trigger to people because it's like
Some kind of something happened, you know, but it's like I don't try to do it
And it's like we'll say things that will trigger people and sometimes and it's like it's not intentional
and maybe you figured me sometimes and I
Think you got you look really hot and that Wendy's wig by the way. I can't
Has the cop already came today
He's really cute he's like the sergeant of the door is a sergeant like they sent to like the fucking top dog
Check on me
One of the checker whatever he was really really nice. I opened the door for him talk to him every time the cops are nice to me
So it's like you're not gonna like turn the police against me and scare me or something at the Avery
And
Here's another thing like he man
I think he man is a little bit maybe unhinged sometimes and he says things but he man saw what happened
Last night a he-man got it like he man says well Benny wouldn't really go anywhere unless there's like a
Motivation or a reason and we saw the reason he was snorning a lot of cocaine
Who sends cocaine or money for cocaine to people? You know who does already you remember the Tommy James crack stream?
We remember that so remember we know that this person likes to use cocaine and like get people like yeah
Oh, here's some money. Here's come cocaine
Can you do me a little favor?
We know this person.
That's our Emma.
And I also want to thank shout out.
I don't know if the person's here, but shout out to the person.
I wouldn't say your name because I don't really know if you have an alt or if you're like,
if you're in the chat quietly or something like that.
Um, and I just want to thank that person because you're, um, you're a sweetheart and I appreciate
you and thank you.
Thank you for sending me that catch up at this.
Sometimes I am a little bit in need and need a little bit.
Thank you, Jamie.
Jamie's here.
Jamie.
Jamie and I were having fun today.
It's funny like we have this woman that says she's like this this really serious Christian and stuff
Hey, cryptic blue. How are you? She's just Christian and then she's saying she's half vampire half witch
She's 675 years old
She loves
Christine I
Mean it's like Jamie right weird as all did you hear with the birthday part? I think we disconnected at some point but
You know Jamie's awesome
And Nick, I will give you that mod as soon as I can.
I just kind of chugged this drink.
It was a little bit hard to talk.
How was that beat us and stuff?
And Jamie, I stood up for you.
Yeah, thank you.
I stood up for you at beat us because, you know,
I think Christine and they were trying to attack you and stuff.
And I'm like, Jamie is,
You know you go on panels and stuff, but yeah, yeah
Lot of people are awesome a lot of people are and it's like even people that it's like will troll me and stuff
Because it's a troll community, right? It's a troll community and it can't it slips out of us sometimes, right?
right, I
Don't care look II care about you. Why was it because of you don't have a mod or you're mad about that?
Why are you salty? I'm you look II I
Mean, I care. I mean it's like but the thing is it's like I'm like very where were they attacking you? Oh
Yeah, they were saying oh Jamie's sitting there sitting there talking about you know
And she said she was lurking in be this that you're lurking in her chat and stuff
And I'm like don't mess with my don't mess with my with my lurkers beat has spies. I was under a spies
I'm not calling. I'm not saying Jamie's a spy because Jamie likes Jamie so Jamie likes to watch these shows
She didn't ever did anything to anybody. That's the thing. She never hurt anybody. She's like
Even people that are like like mean and she'll be like you should be like, oh, can you give them a Marenche and stuff and it's like she's like
She's like she's a good hearted person. Like if you know Jamie, you know, she's a good hearted person
not no mass I'm banned person on beauty because a
Lot of them are dox's a lot of them. You didn't watch you don't watch. Yeah, I
Mean the only reason she was watching beat the last night. I'm sorry for saying too much, but it's like
I was, I was putting it, I was washing it, and then Jamie was just hanging out with me, we hang out sometimes, and I was washing it. And so Jamie's like, yeah.
Jamie's a good person. She doesn't need to be picked on by anybody. Jamie doesn't mod. Jamie's not a mod. She doesn't mod.
I had it up, yeah.
Yeah, I mean it's someone has a someone has a show who's anybody to say oh don't come in my chat and stuff
Persian beauty be nice to Jamie
Jamie you can you can and Jamie and Jamie is my like top mod by the way
You know, I have a few times if you like I feel the hierarchy
I'll say she's a top mom because Jamie's been with me since the beginning and stuff
So if Jamie feels like she's being attacked by somebody or you're being mean to her
I don't really care if she times you out or anything. I know she's not
And Jamie, you go ahead and do what you want to do, okay?
I don't know. I do need a little help today.
I don't know if, you know, I'll be fine today. I mean, I'll be fine.
I had my one drink and like, you know, and that, but you win the link.
Come on, Ghost.
Jamie, here's one thing I'll say about Jamie.
Jamie has a great heart, and I'll always have her back always
Okay in Persian beauty, you know, I know Persian beauty is a troll and stuff. Well, I'm gonna put we have Casey coming on the game show
Oh my god, that wasn't him. I don't think that was him. That must have been a different person. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry
Well, I'm gonna invite the guests. Let's let's have a guest. Let's guest in
I don't think Persian beauty is a bad person. I think that she
Is a troll or he I don't know
I thought it was beta, but then it looks kind of like a hot guy and stuff a little bit
I'm in the human link concentrate. Okay
Someone can help me hold on i'm gonna write a private message right now
Somebody hold on
my god dude I'm getting tired of joining open panels man I know it goes is like
the number one open panels guy and he's getting tired I'm getting tired I had a
bite my tongue on be the channel because they were talking about you and I
couldn't even defend you because they're just gonna what kick me and they
kick me last night by the way
I'm getting tired of these fucking upper panels on YouTube.
They all talk shit.
They're all fucking stupid.
They don't know what the fuck they're talking about.
I know, I know, it goes, goes, goes.
I kept saying, I said, can I have five minutes
to talk to Bita?
Yeah.
You, let's have five minutes and then I won't bother.
I will never come to your show again.
If you don't want me to block, dude, that bitch blocked me
and said, like, oh, you're interrupting psyche.
Uh, when?
What the fuck?
I know, but you know what I respect about Bita?
She lets me up
You know she does. Oh
Shit, I missed a call. Okay. Does she let you up doesn't mean that's respectful
Let the man talk let him defend himself let him put his points out there like let him argue let him debate
I mean, that's how you respect somebody. Oh
I let you up because I want to get views now fuck that I
Magivated man my bad
I'm angry too. I'm angry. I'm I think I'm angry and I don't mean to put that out there in my bed
By the way, I uh, I was trying to get a hold of you earlier. I don't know if you've seen that
Have my phone on mute because I got like a thousand
I'm not gonna mention it on because you know, there's a lot of people watching
But if you if you see what I said, can you please respond because I don't know how to do it
Okay, I will all like is it in text message? No, I'm certain I'm trying to start my own pin. I'm trying to start my own channel
Okay, I'll help you with that
I'm trying to start my own panel, then I'm gonna, I'm gonna start, obviously I should start up my own open panel, you know
Yeah, it goes. You gotta do it. You gotta do it goes. You mean you're, you can't run it with anyone, yeah?
Because you're, and you can get people in there that are like, oh, yeah, hate me, love me, fuck it. Let's run it.
You go to the ghost is ready to run it, right?
Okay, these fucking bitches are talking shit about you for no reason but bringing up shit
Like you were literally obviously there defending yourself and they fucking just hate it on you
If they're gonna bring up a point at least have the argument at least let you defend yourself
Go see you here. I have a news. I'm I'm getting a sex change and I'm turning into a black woman
Well, I'm turning to a black lesbian
No, don't still my that's my I was I'm gonna be a lesbian too
We're both black lesbians
Okay, we're gonna be a lesbian together. Yes
Where's the lesbian bring to the second date a you-haul
That's a little
Hey, you're you're y'all I don't know if it's your buddy or not
But did you watch last night when I was I was this morning actually I was on channels and you know Stephen King
Yeah, he's cool. He's fucking blocked me because of fucking I was arguing because Alex
Crash the fuck out for like two hours, and then I fuck him up. He bought me for 24 hours
Wait, well, he's not blog. It's the college time out and that's okay. I mean it's the time out
And it's like I think but I'll talk to Steven and stuff. Yeah, it's even about it
Because
If you know him man talk to him like that'd be nice because I didn't mean no disrespect
I was talking with fucking Alex of all of you
And uh, and uh, Jamie says she'll take Ghost over Alec?
You're a fan.
Jamie, that's not a compliment.
I mean, I love it, but that's not a compliment.
You have to say over Mason or over Yumi.
I'll take Ghost over Alec.
I mean, not a compliment, I guess.
That's Rudy.
Um, the police came to my door today, um, goes and, and, and, and, and Bronzeberg was like, I'm going to hear the story, brother.
I, oh, I didn't mean to over talk.
Go ahead.
Sorry.
My friend.
Oh, did you hear the story?
And on 420, I obviously, I love the dude.
He'll let me speak about it.
But did you hear the story about 420?
You got arrested and stuff?
No, no, no, no.
Whoa.
Yeah.
But what happened, he fucking was on the bus.
He threatened the bus driver and he
went to go walk away and she maced his ass.
Well, I mean, 24-28, it's called karma.
You know why that happened?
He said, my nails were dirty.
I mean, I don't know if she like put it in his face.
I'm pretty sure he said she sprayed it to the left
and that motherfucker, the wind, you know, like the wind
got him, but he got it in his face.
Cause when I was like probably seven years old,
my little sister was like five years old.
My dad was like, my dad had,
my dad would always carry guns and mace and stuff.
And they always had this in his car, right?
And I was sitting there reading a book and my sister was like,
look how dumb my brother looks, whatever.
My sister picked up the mace and she maced me.
And she says she was just spraying the book, but it sprayed me.
And I was maced when I was basically seven years old, like maced, like hardcore maced,
right?
It's not even pepper spray.
It was maced.
And it was like, that was like probably one of the most painful.
experience. Yeah, it definitely doesn't feel good. Oh, it's bad. It's bad. And my dad,
but it was like, is that this like kind of like, why are you bringing that up just to
share the story? Or did you want to raise the. Mason stuff and he's like, he's crying
about it, but it's like, I got Mason as seven years old. No, here's my reason. Alex crashed
up. We all know Alex. He crashed the fuck out. He was like playing songs and like donating
All of a sudden, dude, were you watching?
I fucking try to text you like, hey, dude,
Alex Cresto, fuck out.
Well, I mean, that's expected, Rudy.
Yeah, man, that is expected.
I admit that, yeah, that's what I'm expecting.
Look at this guy, look at this little man.
Well, let me see.
Let me see that.
Hey.
Hey, yo.
You're just a ace, but you guys make money.
Hey, you want a big pussy?
No, do you have a pussy, dick?
Hey yo, hey yo
Hey, it goes you see me belly dance today. Can I belly dance for you a little bit?
Well, I'm not for me, but if you want to belly dance, go ahead. Okay, I'm gonna belly dance for the chat
I'm gonna take off my shirt
No, no, no, that's what I just meant belly it goes you ever
Have you ever seen my belly?
No, not for me. It's not for a ghost. It's not for ghosts, but I'm gonna belly dance for the chat, okay?
We'll shake that shit then. Okay
Well, double cheeked up on a fucking April Fool's afternoon
Fuck can I belly dance as well? Yeah
Me need them I don't know
No, no shake that shit you didn't even shake it shake it I'm trying to home. Yeah
Bustam Tadiana, Bustam Saquianna, Bustam Saquianna.
Whoa!
At least it wasn't a Speedo, brothers.
You don't find my Speedo, or I would have put it on.
We've been, we've been, we've been tortured.
Tortured?
Tortured.
I've been tortured.
I look like fucking skinnier than Jesus.
Yeah, you do look skinny.
What's up?
Not eating?
I'm hungry.
Yeah, sorry
Did you ever get your cash up because it's like if you're because if I can get McDonald's or something or like something
I'm so happy today. I
Want to have it
So I was able to buy one Mike's heart of hurricane punch with the arty drinking and one thing of cigarettes
And if anyone wants to help me out Venmo probably Venmo is the best right now
Can you explain to me why they I'm sorry, I just interrupt you
My friend can you explain to me why I beat on them or just talking shit about you? I don't understand it
Because they're all in the same coven
He'd be so proud of me. Oh go ahead. I'm so sorry. I'm really excited. I gotta tell you something
Go ahead. I can blow. How are you my friend?
I'm super fucking excited dude, you know, I come from a debate channel and these people like to debate
You know the powder does see an Andrew Wilson actually debate him
You know top tier obviously. He's the master. I actually fucking debate it the powder does see this morning and I fucking won
It's like yeah one
Good, of course you won
That shouldn't powder dusty type it in I know powder just been on the show
Maybe but
He wears a hat. He's like a little he looks like a little like heavy set like not heavy set
But he looks like kind of like a big guy. I will be sass and I dude
I feel like that's this is why it's a message you earlier
And I said can you help me out a little bit because I'm trying to because you obviously you have a YouTube channel
Shit, and I'm trying to figure it out because I I think at this point after I whooped his ass
I did I need to start my own channel, you know, I'll help I'll start for all help you started. Okay. Thank you, sir
I will help you start. Okay. Thank you
I'm guys so if you guys but you know, I'm totally broke right now, and I'll literally just running as open panels
Yeah, if you want to help me tonight and get a couple drink and I'll and I'll try to stay on as long as I can
You're gonna help me with drinks a couple drinks and maybe like a McDonald's fries and stuff
There it's been most probably the best way
But or me or if you want my zeal come back stage, and I'll give you my number and stuff
But I appreciate that but here you go goes and I'll dance for the cat
Hey, just throw dollar bills at me right now check it
You can join come on
Check that out.
You want me to put up the link? I'll put up the link and track him wants to run it
Let that man join okay one join one join join pussy and shake it
You can't join unless you shake it
Right
Hey, you can't join once you shake that shit you heard
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I
Get offended he doesn't get you just
Say whatever you want to him. He doesn't care. He's what's that I actually like this guy
You want me to run like I know I like him, too. I like him, too. It was no offense
Dragonball
Don't let me run it. Why are you watching sucky shake that ass though?
Why are you sitting there watching that shit?
I didn't see his eyes.
Yeah, he was moving, and you were watching him.
Ghosts who like ghosts like too.
And, Dracobal, you have to admit,
I'd make a beautiful black woman.
How about that?
Well, that's true.
Beautiful.
BBW, that's a black woman, beautiful black woman.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Let's go
There's been a lot of questions about the Somalis in America
Are you doing Somalis? Hey, a trackable. You want to send me a few folks for dinner?
Then you can talk about I look like a Somali and stop it. I want to say yeah, I do want to say I
Do want to be a black woman because my life
Attractable was on the podcast last night where they were making fun of people and then when I joined I burnt their ass up
They kicked me he was there
Is it money?
Money for 20 usually lets me up though. It was
He was there I'm talking about you not remember it or am I oh
I drink I drink a lot. I drink a lot
I might I might have been there as a black woman myself. I really don't remember
I was a black queen
Oh my god, ghost is like an African
when he's in a dashiki.
Hey Wakanda forever.
Wakanda? Yeah, he was playing the Congo drums.
If he keeps talking on trackable, he has nice teeth.
He's retarded, but those teeth are nice.
Wakanda forever brother.
Don't giggle, I heard you giggling, don't giggle.
I'm allowed to giggle, it's in the constitution.
Well, that's true, I have the first amendment.
There's something about giggling in there.
I like this, I like this week though.
I know psyche let me ask you a question if you don't mind every time I join other panels
I got to be psyches boy. I don't understand that also. I got to defend your ass. I understand that
You did them I don't submit my ass it's been my my wiener everyone's trying to cut it off. Oh
That's a good debate then. Let's talk about it. I think they want to take you take your ass
Yeah, we can check. Don't let them drive. We're comfortable. There's any a little bit too. I think they they're even hot to spin on the thing either
This one my god. Oh my god
Nothing nothing makes me uncomfortable. Okay. He doesn't care. Okay. That's why I love undrikeable. It's like
Before he don't give a fuck about nothing. Okay. I've said some weird chicken. He don't
I
In other places I've been called a fence sitter and I'm like don't threaten me with a good time
Are you a bottom
He is actually married man
I agree he's really dope as fuck
Yeah, it doesn't get any gayer than a Mary
What do you think about black north I know you know him do you think he's a good guy or no
Who are you asking
Oh, I'm sorry. How's that since I come back north? Um, yeah, I really don't care
But I don't care about anyone says and they can like, you know, say anything they want
He was fair in my book. He was pretty okay
Yes, you don't like him fucking I'll run it with him
I'm putting my information up guys.
If you want to help me out with food or drinks tonight,
I'd really appreciate it.
I'm going to put my Venmo up, or it's-
If you want to help me out with that beard,
you know, conditioner, or dye.
Yeah, or if you want to like me to, I'll save my head.
I'll buy you a half of my eyebrow if you want.
I'll shave your head for $50, I'll shave that,
I'll shave this head.
There, I'm going to pin the message.
There you go.
I'll shave the fuck out of your head.
But then it's also cash up or men is like at the cash up. I do a little money to them
So they might like they deduct it but are also Venmo if you want to come back stage
I'll give you my psyche didn't mention. What about a card reading?
Oh, and our card reading and you know, I'll do five to ten dollars. I'll give you a great
Can I I do I am I will ask you for a favor. Can I get like a one-card reading? Is that fair?
Get up and grab a moment. Yeah
And give my boy one card reading to beard. Okay
Yeah, okay. I'll figure it out. I'll figure it out. By the way, I just called you beard
We care, okay, one second, okay
I'm gonna pull my I'm gonna put me. I'm sorry. I'm oh, yeah, shut that shit. You heard me see, okay
I'll do a belly dancing card. Hey yo, Paul's
Am I up? Hold on. Oh my god, but don't belly dance
Oh my gosh
Okay, I'm trackable or goes first
Can you do my boy first if you don't mind?
Trackable I got this for you
All right, my um, my birthday is April 16th. Okay, so you're
So are you a you're an Aries Aries
Yeah
Okay, I'm tracking what's this thing there's a heart and a heartbreak there
Stabbed you got a heartbreak. This is like from the recent past there's a heartbreak for you. I don't know. I don't know
I'm sorry for that. Yeah, remember always healed and stuff. I'll do a few more. Okay. No
Was it have to do with a woman? It's like woman. This is also a fire sign against fiery woman
It might have been a heartbreak to do with this woman
What's her name start with a B?
No, yeah beat a broke his heart bitch, and then I'm getting this
But this is all to like clear the space
This is the tower and this tower pretty particular is not falling down. It looks like I almost a candy cane
It looks so it's a positive
Towers and as usual if it was a negative I would say the towers falling down, but then I'll say the tower
This is a really good
Big change for you like you're having a there's gonna be a big
Clearing out for something positive. I'm gonna do two more for a trackable. He's a Lisa. Yeah, give him two more
I think that's fair. He's a pinnacle. Someone's gonna come to you with this money idea
I have a business idea maybe if you can you invest in me or something it's almost a seed kind of thing
We'll go into something bigger and I have one more thing for you
Pentacles also
Someone's coming to you with
Something good something material a delivery a package or something like that you've been waiting for
Something something positive something or some kind of letter or something. That's it. Oh, you're making some money and so so yeah
I'll just take one card. Oh, yeah, you'll take one card got the carpet goes
for ghosts tonight.
Oh, it goes night of.
OK, well, this is the night of cups, but it's like.
The night of cups is like, you know,
someone coming in with a love offer or some kind of like a good
thing emotionally for you, but it almost is like.
This this reminds me kind of like the eight of eight of wands a little bit that the way he's standing which is
Which is gonna mean burdens. Okay. I think I need a second card. Okay. I think that I think it's okay
Reminds me of a second card. Please pull it. Yeah
Six of cups. This is like good. This is like nostalgia. I always say this is a nostalgia card
It's like this memory of this great
Pass the experience and you want to relive this thing and I think this this can count
I have but I can't use two cars. I do three cars
You it's kind of like you're like high school or college days like you you peak but you always want to relive
Because you also have the chariot. I don't know if your car really good condition or you're going really fast towards something
You see something this is like full speed ahead towards your goal. It's up. Okay. It's like in your and this is success, too
Like there's usually some sphinxes that are like sitting down, so it's kind of
I just had one card, you gave me three
I pulled three, I pulled three because I don't do, we said two
Then I pulled three because I don't like the number two just is like leaving on two cards
Okay, make it six, let's go
I'm gonna do six cards, okay, let's do six
Yeah, fuck it, let's do it
We're doing a full thing for ghosts, oh my gosh
Fuck it
And it's like, and then the, remember I said the burdens
Like
Hey, what the fuck
No, it's like burdens like you're carrying and they're not really that heavy
But it is like a lot of stuff going on, it's like a lot of activity, like there's a lot
of activity and a lot of like, you caring that, I almost see it's like kind of like
Not like you're being ridden by like a horse not to be weird or anything like that
But it's like you're like hey, I can help I can help you with it
I'll be with you helping a lot of kind of like a Leo kind of like a lion like I have a
Definite personality. I like to argue, but I like to help out people that are new and ones also is a fire card, right?
She's watching
There's your girlfriend the Empress. She's like all the queens in the deck
They really cool like really smart really developed woman that can help you a lot. I see that she's good stuff coming with this woman
Okay, good. So and finally
The star I think this woman is also the star
Another another
There you go. This is star. This is like just good energy coming towards you
This is like you're lighting up. I see this woman coming towards you. You're really just lighting up
I think I'm waiting for her and because you know you figure out this is the one I've been waiting for something like that
I didn't know anything about your dating life or anything
And I'm I am
Tell me if this sure now. I heard that I was a protector
Also, I'm a provider also. I'm kind of like
a gentleman also. I'm a Leo like I'm a lion. Yeah as a male lion. I like to protect people and I think that's true
Millions do but millions are also like they kind of like like to lay in the sun a little bit
But guess if another male lion comes along what happens you'll get up and
Your wrestle you'll do anything you can't like yeah, exactly
And you because you want to be the number one lion and those new line
You know the fucked up thing and I don't know I can say it on YouTube pretty sure
But yeah, I can but the new line will come in and kill the cubs
Okay, but I know okay, um 20 20. Yeah, there's been interpretations like I get particularly when I have so many different decks
I really like will like take the interpretation and mix it with that particular deck
And so with a star card for ghosts that I got
hmm, I see like
She's reaching it. She's reaching he looks close and he's maybe
Okay, he's right right so he got he had that he picked up on it long distance long distance thing
Oh, you know that makes sense though cuz I'm a astrology guy also, you know today
We're actually going back to the moon the first time ever that a woman is gonna go around the moon in fact
Also, we're actually gonna travel to the dark side of the moon. Did you know that?
Yeah, hey about this one little star
Yeah, the point is never get never give up goes because it maybe it seems far away, but it's close as you can see it
It's like within this one light year is not a year
But I'm seeing those follow that bird. It goes
People do not block me like beer
Well, she's not blocking you. She goes she'll let you on and stuff
I mean, it's like she lets me on and I think it's my guts and stuff speed is not a bad person
Like I always like I'll get this like this like evil side and it's like I think it's like not the evil side is not really evil
It's like
in the like a lot of ancestors stuff.
What the fuck are you, why are you cut,
you finna go to bed, what are you culling up for?
Because I don't have any drink slaps,
I don't have any food and I'm hungry
and I'm not getting any donation or anything,
so I'll probably fall asleep
and just sleep until something happens.
But I'll be here, I'll be here, I'll be here.
You need some food?
A little bit, but it's okay, I'll be okay, I'll be okay.
Hey, you somebody tell me.
You tell me, kid, like, it's a great stomach.
It's okay, it goes.
No one needs, no, you guys, everyone thinks I'm like,
I'm just begging for stuff.
If I ask for something, I do need it,
but I'm also like really resilient and I'll do okay.
And also, I've also, people have been helping me a lot.
And it's like, I don't wanna ask too much of people
or like seem greedy or anything,
but I'm happy to give like long readings or anything.
Those both were quickies and stuff.
because it's like and I appreciate but they were quickies but they were kind of long a little bit
it's because you're here up on the panel and stuff talking to me and and I'll also do free readings
and it's like if you if you I know people are under financial stuff and I don't want to make you
I'm not trying to make anybody feel sorry for me but sometimes I do need help and and uh
And it would be helpful, but it's not necessary.
And so I'm sorry if I'm coming on too strongly.
There you go.
And this pin, the link has been, I think,
for a donation if you want to help me to pay.
Thank you.
And it's all appreciated.
And you know what?
It's not to be like weird or like but it does come back to you
And so when I give I mean I just I don't even I don't expect it to come back
But it always does you know it always does this money is like a fluid thing that goes back and forth to people and it's like
So I bet I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I don't want to come on too strong
Oh, we have another guest on the show. Let's welcome. Oh ghost is back. I'm sorry. Here we go. Hey, thank you ghost
Give food. Thank you ghost. Well on the night and then 21st, I might be able to with the super chat
But thank you so much. I should be hungry brother. I don't give
First of the 21st, I'll be able to get something and if you guys
I mean she does the outreach shit and like I was respected for that. It was fucks. There's cool. I love summer this way
I'm sure she's still good man. Come on. I can't well that I mean the super chat
I'll get paid on the 21st and so in just 21 days. I'll be able to to get it a fries
What PayPal or go direct you
PayPal or yeah PayPal will or um, is that or something? Yeah
Well fuck what do you want? I'll fucking door-dash it
you will
Whatever you I'll put I'll put my address back there. I mean just went anything anything anything. I appreciate you go. Thank you so much
I'll put it back to you. I
Love you. Hold on one second. Don't put my address backstage and
Well, be careful make sure you put it backstage
But if I only untrackable and you can see it, I trust you. Yeah, but not to like, you know hurt me and stuff
and but I'm going to make sure I get the address right here we go fucking hungry that's all you
got to say brother thank you okay and I'm I'll run the panel as far as much as I can tonight
and there is backstage I think I got it yeah I got it perfect okay there you go
so intractable how's your day been today how's your April Fool's you know I'm turning into
Yeah, it was
There was no jokes
Wait, but I pull I just fooled you because I'm not gonna really turn into a black
false
I'm gonna become a black RG
Yeah, I wouldn't be a black RG and black RG or your mod back to others low look at you by the way psyche black RG
Was very respectful the other day
It's an RG earn your mod back because you know
They get a little boot in my tummy then I'll like
I'll be looking at the studio and stuff.
But I'm hanging out.
I'm going to open the panel longer than I can.
I don't want to fall asleep, but it's like a little bit.
It's a Wednesday.
It's kind of like Wednesdays.
I was born on a Wednesday, actually.
But I was also born on a Wednesday.
You should be awake then.
Well, I will but you know what Wednesday was when I was born. It was it was just getting over the new moon
I'll shut up. No, no, no, you don't shut up but let him talk. Okay. So you won't talk about the moon
I leave for work when it's still dark and there was a big full
Blood moon what those retards earlier like it was the moon was
You know like pink ish. Yeah, I love that blood moon. The blood moon is like a beautiful
Isn't it the pink moon or am I incorrect somebody Google it. I'm sorry
Well, I saw it this morning. I imagine it won't be much different tomorrow
Yeah, it'll still be pretty full, but it's now it's gonna start weighing. I don't understand why they were talking so much
About psyche, but when I wanted to come up
They wouldn't let me because they knew I will fuck them up. I feel disrespected
Sorry, I'll show you up a little bit, but it's like it was like Amanda and Christine. Yeah, it was fucking dumb-ass
Whining and bitching and like
Fucking complaining. Hey guys people say like I mean it's like, you know that they are like, you know
These whiny bitchy ladies, but they, they don't have to prove it to us every time.
Papas.
Pepper.
You know, there's, there's this joy that you get to choose to carry with you.
If you're going to pack something in your emotional bag.
Make sure
I heard you anywhere else besides here you something you should be on the radio. You got a nice fucking voice
No, no, I'm not trying to be gay, but you so you're so good
No, no
I like it I like it
You're a fan of trackable ghost is actually a good guy. You're a good guy. It would not not not like Chucky
He had a nice wish though, correct? I mean, I don't know why they're talking about you Jamie
But I think that they're just bitter people like they were me saying talk to shit about Jamie
I'm talking are they talking shit in the comments? No, it wasn't beat is chat. They were and on in the back
Yeah, I fuckin ruled that fuckin
I was like, don't pick on Jamie.
I was like, if you pick on Jamie, and then Kate says,
Don't talk about fire, you don't understand.
I was like, don't talk to Kate.
Let's run that.
I said, I'm his friend.
Let's run that bitch.
They don't want to run it.
They just want to run away.
Pussy. Master of the later, ghosty.
I was wearing this.
A matter of fact, if you don't mind, later, you don't have to do it now, but later, if you can possibly find the ghosty song, I would appreciate it.
Okay, I will. But if I play the ghosty song, can you maybe perhaps look at the Door Dash menu?
I mean, that seems fair.
Okay, I'm going to find it right now then.
That's how everything has to be a challenge, and I think I think so much that's coming
across.
I'm going to smoke right now, I don't usually smoke, but if anybody wants to run it, I'm
a debater.
I'm going to go get hired right now, so probably debate me now before I get hired.
No, I'd rather debate you. I love you, brother. Well, yeah, I love you brother. Yeah, we can definitely can talk after that's for sure
But anybody else wanna anybody else
I'm gonna listen link again home. I found the ghost song case or here's a ghost song
I should by the way guys. I want to point this out. I should my mom this song
She was sick in the hospital by the way. I should have the go song and she fucking loved it
It's great song. I love it
Yes, you may here we go you want to see this
How much money you need by the way
I appreciate anything I can make it I'll make it work
That goes through the night
That's how you know the haunt's alive
Lights flicker
Chats in the right
And somewhere goes about to die
He rows in loud like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks, cracking jokes
Keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts howling
The trolls start crying
Ghosts just grins
Let's fucking go
And now we're flying
When the sky lost its hue, they can't see the light, he threw in my storm, but I remember I was reborn.
May I have permission to crash out?
Ghost already did it to the whole crowd, heart of gold, voice of fire.
When ghost shows up, the stakes get higher.
Every hater gets fun right round, round When the chat goes cold, he brings it loud
When most just lie and chose to leave me
He's the king of the late night ring
Crashing out with a heart that sings
Gender is so half-sane, half-storm
Breaking norms just by staying warm
In a world full of clowns, he's the last to fake
When the screen went dark, he kept me awake all the night
TURN IN PAIN IN DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-DU-D
comes a dream dumb dumb to the ones who doubt he's the reason the flame never went out so raise your glass but go
I'm looking for the Jamie's Cowboy song now.
It goes jump top.
Okay, hold on a second.
I'll find the game.
If you like that one, and track up one.
Yeah, but I enjoyed music.
Did you just hear that?
It's a dumb, dumb, dumb.
I can't believe that song came on next.
Hold on a second.
I'm cold to psyche.
Yeah, you like that one?
I need to make an intractable song next.
You like that?
Hey, you use your
Usual abilities and I will not be disappointed. I promise
Okay, perfect. Okay. Max. I should I change my other channel from cult of psyche with a K to psyche's nightmares
I think Jamie's song is on there. I have to find it
YouTube
Okay, psyche's nightmares
because
My gosh, I shouldn't have drinking that beer without food in my stomach. Okay, cuz I'm like I'm too drunk
Oh, oh, one second. I'll be right back and drive. Well, can you talk to the chat for a second?
Yeah, for sure. Oh, I'll do my best. I'll be right there
hey welcome chat welcome to uh the cult of psyche
uh a bit of a playground of melding minds and searching for others
feel free to enjoy yourself
and ask me anything if if your heart so desires to learn more about
the untrackable. I can't speak for Psyche.
I can't speak for anyone else.
Have a good time. Enjoy yourselves.
Enjoy each other.
have love in your heart carry joy in your backpack be ready for anything
oh shit hi banny how are you i'm good dude like what happened last night where you were actually
making me mad a little bit bro what the fuck you're back hey what's up you know fuck with me dude
Hi, no, no, no, I'm I'm I'm I'm doing this. I'm doing my shirt
I'm a little bit skinny, but
Okay, bud
Don't be scared. Don't be scared. Okay. I won't do it. I'll be my shirt on
It's not it's just that part right there the third part of I didn't give a fuck about bro. All right, but no
So what was what the what was up the last night, bro? Well, I don't know just it just felt like
You know, I was like I thought I was being oh no no no listen, bro. You fucking pissed me off, bro
I was being honest, bro. Like I really am like that, bro
Like I don't fucking pretend bro, and then I actually like fucking like
Was bleeding my heart out and you fucking y'all like
Demonizing bro. I am a monster, bro. I told you like I don't really like the therapy and shit
Like I can't help this shit, bro, like no, I know and I was like, I don't hurt animals, bro
Like that's my point really
I don't you watch the video you've seen as soon as I hit my leg, bro, even though the third like like a shirt
That's it, bro
Like they're fur you ain't gonna shit, but like bare leg like no skin. No nothing like yeah, you feel that but like no cat
You're not feeling that bro. I just was feeling but I am not saying I was right, but I should like that does look fucked up
But like at the same time that shit doesn't hurt, bro. You mean?
Okay, well, I'm just like I'm hoping it didn't but I'm saved don't like never do that again
But it's like but I was never have you see my well my child
I live outside and then fucking my brother's fucking retarded outside cats are fucking attacking my cat late
Pissed the fuck.
No, listen, you know, he's like, bro.
Did you see what happened last night?
Do you know Alexander Mayer's posted after the show?
She said, stay the fuck away from Benny and try to use
you sick fuck to me.
And she's like, they're innocent little boys and stuff.
And it was just like this sick shit and stuff.
And it's like, yeah.
Let me get the post I don't know who that is, but it's a black a lot of females like me
I don't know I don't blame you and I and it's like, you know, and it's like
It's like I would
A million times I'll offer I would forgive you for that and I'll defend you for that
No, I'm not doing that. No, but you understand it like I'm really not like that after the video, right?
I'm not like that really. I'm not purposely going out on my abusing hours, right?
That's a big shit
It's just like, it's just like, that's like the, that's like the one thing that's like, it hurts my heart and it's like, and I, I, like I said last night, I was like, I don't even believe he would, he hurt the animal or hurt an animal because I saw him with puppy cat and his other cats and his cats like love him and your cat loves, I love you and stuff.
And it's like, I just feel like, I was feeling almost like set up because, you know, I don't know if you know Tommy James, you said you didn't know Tommy James or not.
Hold on. Did he drop off?
Did you hear of Tommy James?
I think he bounced himself.
Okay. Well, you know, I was trying to say it was weird because Tommy James a couple months ago
his girlfriend or whatever, or his e-boo,
like, donated for him to smoke crack on the stream,
or to make crack or something.
And then all of a sudden, Benny, who, like, you know,
usually has just a few twisted T's or something,
he is, like, has all this cocaine, and I was like,
did she, like...
Pay him or something to like say this to make it to make to break my heart and stuff
Oh, oh
That's what I was feeling because I was like he was like first he was like he's like well
I have a photograph of memory and I remember that you were in my chat that night or or something
I was like what this is it just it I was like she's trying to like
like take the last like
piece of the best piece of like
My heart out goes home one second one second. Oh
Here it is. Here's it
So, oh, there you are
Your savior I get you thought I was like throwing you but no, I was actually like traveling. I was trying to talk
I'm drunk a little bit. I'm getting drunk. I'm a third right
Listen, I was trying to talk to you really
Like I know I need open shit, but like that's why good fucking
This one's going like you actually get help for you. I mean like I'm like voluntarily like getting myself up, but like
I don't like, like, look at animal, like, I love my cat, bro, like...
I mean, look at any animal I've ever had, bro, like, they're not fucked up, being like...
I think it was a misunderstanding. I want to show you this picture.
Look what they're doing to me, Benny. Look what they're doing to me.
Yeah, bro, I think you're, like, worried, like, dude, you gotta not worry about this shit, bro, like...
Hey, look!
I'm looking.
Is that me?
I guess.
That was a big club.
Let me find the one. Oh, shit. I'm just trying to show.
If you're a male, hold on.
I think she deleted the Benny comment,
but she had this Benny comment last night saying,
and she posted a new one.
I'm not doing to delete this, but yeah, it was really crazy.
She also said, I mean,
I remember it's on the ip2weektjohn.info.
This is what I do, bro.
I get callers off of bitches, bro.
I have bitches wearing callers, bro.
I'm darling, really.
So it's I don't want it says she's elated it but she said last night there's a pose and it said
Stay away from Benny and Joker like you like sick fuck to me
Yeah, oh
Joker Joker
Don't get surprised, but he
he's uh
He's so scared like I don't know. He's not
Like Joker you both. Oh, is this it is it here?
This is a very nice guy. Um, I'm saying I'm not a nice guy, but
Okay, guys, she deleted them all. There's a completely different human being to me, but like by a long shot
Yeah
I'm not much of a nice guy myself
I just know when to tone it down when I choose
Does that make sense by drinking bro? Well, I'm I'm cooked up. I'm like, yeah, I I
All right, it's like I'm done. All right. Bye site. I gotta go. You got a little ago. Okay. No, no, no
I was talking about last night, bro
Yeah, I know it just kind of got uncomfortable because the chat was like I felt like it was like a set up
No, but you're like this interview is over. I'm like
Well, I don't think that he would he like I think it's exaggerated. Maybe he like plays up on this like, you know kind of
Because you are kind of no no no no that stuff. I look he like down great, but
I don't like go my way to hurt people really this is I know you don't I know you don't and it's like
I mean like but like
And I never seen that I like always like calculating the like I'm always like thinking in my head like
like that
What to say what to do like I could talk out my mouth right now like how I'm talking right now
I'm thinking about what I'm about to say like like I could think
Far, far ahead.
Okay, okay, okay, but I just remember like I can't say I don't believe it, I was gonna pay it back.
But she she as soon as I left the stream there was a post and she deleted it already, but it said
Okay, and it's like and I was like, okay
So and then she posted the day before picture of Joker and Benny's like ten-year-old boys with me as like in an ice cream truck
Trying to like kidnap them and stuff and then like before she was like oh Benny's so cute with his short hair and stuff
Well, I was friends with her so I was like it feels like
And then the Tommy James stuff, where she-
Yeah, but yeah, she's like, she's like,
she's like, she's like, she's like,
she's fucking sitting there like, fucking,
fucking, over-lighting over me.
Yeah, Benny, she literally paid this guy, Tommy James,
to smoke crack on his stream, like a couple months ago.
And that was-
Yeah, but she's like, she thinks I'm attractive.
Well, she said, she's like,
oh, he looks good with his short hair.
And I think he'll look good with his short hair.
I love it if they roll along here.
You remind me of like, like, what's that move?
Yeah, yeah.
You know that guy in case it was you?
Yeah, well, another thing is like, um...
I don't know bro like I'm drinking so like I'm like don't give a fuck on me
I did look at the gun and whatever they're talking about. Kate sent me a photo of it and it's like
Listing it looks like kind of like a more of a toy kind of thing to me like
What are you talking about gun?
There's no gun that I've ever posted that's a toy on my channel. I say it's a toy just so I don't get in trouble by
You're talking about that she's a water pellets or whatever
it looks like oh yeah yeah yeah that yeah that literally bro listen okay i can't
have like what all the cats i was like it was fucked up bro i'm not like i said to you last night
it's not good bro but like i'm not saying like at the same time that like i said i shot i'll shoot
my clothes yeah shoot myself over and over like proving on point like it don't fucking hurt bro
like it doesn't do anything but when you shot bare leg like bare skin yeah you felt that bro like
I wasn't going out my way like as soon as I did that bro like if you watch this like if you watch the clip
I'm like, oh shit. Yeah, nah, bro. I'm good. Like I'm not doing that anymore. That's fucked up
You're right in everything I get why you like would buckle me more
But if you watch like I said if you watch the clip bro, like really watch it, bro
You see like as soon as like
Honestly didn't hurt the cast because like the first is not gonna hurt them, right?
You guys, just saying with the clothes,
like you have your clothes on your skin.
You shoot yourself with a gel blaster.
You feel literally nothing, besides like a little.
We're saying like, we're saying like, you know,
I was saying, yeah, I understand people have a spray bottle
sometimes when the dog gets up and they're like,
yeah, yeah, I was just really blacked out, bro.
I was close.
Listen, I was, I'm not saying it's an excuse, bro,
but I was really fucked up in that clip.
Yeah.
Really gone.
I was gone.
Okay, I just think that you know I have like four cats and they're my babies and it's up and it's like you know
This is me off road about you bros you seen how I'm talking care of my cats bro
I know that's what I was defending you today still
I was like I was like I can't even believe that it's the cat was hurt because I've seen him with his cats and his cats like
Love him in a cat if a cat it feels betrayed
the cat will just leave like forever like the cat
well listen that's another thing well it could be like just like they also say like cats like see the afterlife is like they're not going to fuck with you if you're like you're like give me like
you're not going to talk to me
you're not going to talk to you if they think you're going to set her next but yeah
Kate, Kate, Kate
I like I just can't like I just can't believe I'm not like that, bro. Listen. I'm not like that, bro
I'm not going on my way to fucking her. No cats bro. Like listen. All right. I'll give you a story, right?
Okay, I used to love to him birds
And I said I was fucking evil right weirdo kid
But when my cousin would pop my 10 pump up and pop cats I snap on I'm like I did not like that shit
But I'd like what the fuck are you doing, bro? Like
He's like, oh, it's just a cat. Yeah, it's a fucking cat, bro. Like what are you talking about?
You're fucking weird, bro. And that's my cousin Dominic. He's actually a biracial cousin of mine
Yeah, first cousin biracial
We're a little kids. I have my temp on and I'm like aiming for birds and trees and shit
Because I'm trying to like anytime out of BB gun or 22 be gone 22. You mean 22 fuck kill you
But yeah, I have more time on 22 than I do BB gun, but you got right
Come pump that was you I think it was I might get my BB gun was you 20
Foot per second right
Thousand feet per second. Yeah
Listen to one pump one pump
We'll fucking put a bb in you in a person if you pump that fucker 10 times
Oh, actually bloke like they'll hit your shoulder blade like break your shoulder blades
Yeah, your mom there
Yeah, everyone everyone's here
This is it all as far as sender
There's outside. Yeah, it's part of the old like a tenders. I'm
No, it's part of a
One
My dad when he was like a child he had like a he had like a BB gunner or some kind of good
He felt so bad about she's killing the bird and he never did anything like that and also
I've never ever I've never went. I've never heard a cat right for some reason cats
I don't like something my brain like I can't hurt them. I love cats like maybe it's a spirit thing
I just love cats, right? Yeah, but like my my my ex-girlfriend right then I everyone's talking about dinner, right?
Yeah
All right, so her dog, right?
Bit her brother to the bone where he went to the hospital like and he has a gnarly scar on his arm like I mean like
nasty fucking scar
her ex-boyfriend has a scar on his leg arm and his fucking shoulder
fucking the brother has a scar also on the leg it's also from one fight like they fought once and then uh
it was originally the brother's dog right the girls it's fucking dog right on there like every person
she's ever like a lot of females make this shit up like oh
It's the only person it fucks with you like fucks with you this bitch actually had to have this dog put down like recently
Like last few days
I come over I come over. I'm sitting there chilling like we fucked are you mean?
I said they're chillin all of a sudden his dog pulls up like I just feed his dog and she's like freaking the fuck out
I'm not paying attention anything. I'm just fucking
kind of dog like this and I and she's like
Oh my god, I can't believe the dog fussed with you like did it up like I don't have to keep in a cage
That's like great did it up
It's probably my best day with me as long as you did but sadly not
I'm like bro. I'm like
I told her like bro the dog is not scared of me because listen
I'm not scared of this dog because if the dog bit me. I'm ripping its fucking doll open. I'm fucking
No, I'm saying that the dog bit me the dog attack me
How old are you I'm 24
Yeah, you ain't doing shit, bro
Can do fucking dirty pull-ups the hard way how many can you do one zero?
Yeah
Is that the competition?
Can you do at least ten full push-ups?
We need you. Can you do a cloud push-up?
I'm drunk as fuck. I'm on like I'm literally about 15 beers deep
I'll do two double I'll do at least two class for you, right?
I will I will not challenge you I am not
I've been through it
What you are talking about is not winning
What do you want to know bro
What the fuck is that I just did four pull ups. I'm sorry
You see me there, I'll be lucky to get out of this chair right now
Okay, I get it. Well, I don't but
I'm part all right, so I was a rare a-class lot like rider dirt bike was
professional and my family just ever had the money to
Don't know way and I
I'll have pain my lower back ankles and fucking knees or a smell
Where about like three inches tall like shorter than I should be from just like you guys think you're 150 feet
Smashing down like
That fucks your spine up, you know, but the real pain is when you need to take care of yourself
Dude like well, I have to do labor work to fucking make money, bro. So like I'll fucking be doing labor work, bro
We'll be fucking 10 hours in bro 12 to 14
Probably fucking dudes sitting there like my lower back, bro, like
There's days, bro. I'll be thinking like I'm a fucking class and I really like fuck
Nice keep going keep going keep going like this is like happening money, you mean
That's all I afford fucking alcohol and cigarettes really fucking actually working
But like most these people on like you do this stream and shit, but I don't never done a hard fucking day labor in our life
Oh, I'm so sorry for laughing at you, dude
You ever done asphalt or lead
Jackable
I did I did I did asphalt for fucking a year almost a year and a half
You're gonna find a wake-up period where I
Get your same bro. Listen. All right, so when I was doing asphalt, right? Listen, I was making 4k a month
Yeah, but what happened was I fucking family shit brother gypsies bro gypsies run the black top
They run it all bro
So like if you like
You gotta get bitch like it is like I can't bring it in myself to be like yeah, that's cool
Like let me like go like fucking
Balloon run your business
Now save your business, but like help your business and I fucking get paid nothing
Who runs you?
No resume right now. I
We do the services with my dad, so I have a service tomorrow, so I'll make fucking 300 a day. So
That's my first thing to do is services
So like basically
Yeah, you have your wire it goes for the fucking
This is the top. You have your joint box
You have to hold the ladder for someone doesn't put it up, right? You have to have it
I guess
Turn up the fuck off bitch. Yeah, I'm a punch you like
No, no, no, I
Your mom your mom and hey mom. I'm fucking talking. Sorry. I'm sorry. So it's fucking 14 feet off the ground
I think it's seven at the bare minimum the box has to be
From the pole, right? Okay, so I'm trying to tell you guys like code and like how electrical work really works like deep into it
If you don't want to know that it's fun
It's not beneficial to you guys anyway, so
Well, you know, I know you love your mom and stuff and I want to say hi to your mom. Hey mom. Hey, what's up? How are you?
Hi
To talk to you. Yeah, sure
There you go guys, I'm good
Hello
Nice to meet you. You look beautiful. Oh my god. I never like really like I don't think I've ever seen you
I was on the show a couple years ago
Wait what's your name?
I'm psyche awakens. I was like you I do terror readings and stuff and I was I mean I was
I went on his panel and I just was watching I watched a lot and
you know I uh I just want to say like I I know that you guys love each other a lot you have kind
of this like volatile relationship at times but I know I've seen the love too like right yeah yeah
we kind of grew up never mind my love here we grew up together kind of I was young
Jesus Christ hey on track why are you like X special forces or some shit
what
I
Could have sworn you're like some crazy vet or some shit. Maybe you're wrong. You weren't in the military
I was an army cook. Oh, you were a fucking cook never mind
One-handed push-ups, that's all
He just said
Anyone got it? I remember you for Marty's
Yeah, you were fucking I never talked to Marty though. Like that's the fucking thing
That's my fucker. No, listen. Listen. I have a K like in bikes. This motherfucker had a dude loaded my shit up bro for free
I'm like
Saying I crashed my bike fucking
Industries, bro. I'm like what the fuck and then he talked to this motherfucker
And he's just gonna be like, yeah, Benny's cool
He's like, yeah, I'm high on pills. I'm just bored. I have nothing to do bear. Like
I remember him from Marty's when he was slapping his mom around you just
Marty no Marty wasn't around for that. No Marty wasn't a thing
Marty maybe he might have saw it but no Marty didn't become a part of anything until literally like I had like
I was averaging 2,500 a stream live and chat shit the fuck up bitch
Okay, right
What he was doing was he would fucking make craig list ads bro. Like well, he would like
So those tell me you know
That Marty
This motherfucker said that yeah Marty said he felt bad for it when he severed up
He's like yeah, bro. I shouldn't have done that to Benny, but he's like Marty. He's sobered up. I see
He died he oh deed
I'm aware
Okay, well what are you talking about? He was on I was doing Xanax to motherfucker
That's like 90% of my fucking content with me on Xanax
I think a lot of your content is like fucking old
Does that look like you 12 it kind of wears me out a little bit
You fucking
I'm fucking with you, bro, obviously fucking take a fucking
Take a joke
Hello, but my dad fucking a Pokemon my death on a Pokemon. I do it
That's me. Who wants to are you?
To be to grand is the Adderall or coke that you're all up done
I'm actually a nothing right now. I
What I'm gonna cook probably sit like if you watch like if you watch my streets last night
I'm actually cooking up a like
Yeah
So how do you know this kid again psyche
He's not a kid. Okay. I found his dream. Hey, it looks like a kid
RG's 24 years old, okay, let's not like spread this narrative. I think you he attracts older men who like him
So they look young. What are you saying about me? When you're trying to say about me RG? I'm not saying you. I didn't say you
You I know but he's like what but what are you saying like what I'm not buying anything. It's just that's my thoughts
Bro like he's saying right
That's what I feel a little bit. I feel a little bit that people
Kid I'm not making it up. No, bro. I just got good genetics, but I get it. I'm six foot in relief, but yeah
I mean, how tall are you really? Yeah, I'm tall enough
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
Hey, because people are saying in the chat they're like, oh my god, they're trying to imply that it's like
I think they think that's like he wants to bang you and I'm I would believe
We're not we're not talking about this now
Exactly, exactly. That's what I'm trying to say. It's like
That's all it is, bro. Like the fuck is like, bro, like
Do you not think I get like I'm not in so I get pussy, but like what the fuck is this like I don't get what's going on here
No, it's like, no, Benny's a very, no, he's a very straight guy.
You got to, who are you?
I don't, I don't, I...
Where's that woman you were dating?
You're talking to this woman and I remember I got to fight with her.
Lena Horo's fucking sticking my dick in.
How old was your mom when she had you?
She looks kinda young too.
18, 19, but yeah.
I would have guessed younger than that, to be honest.
Oh!
Cock sucker!
All right.
Why?
Didn't mean it.
Well, I mean, that's a compliment to your mom.
It's like, she's...
That's
Dude, yeah, it's not think for a second. Okay. I'll think first
Kid me for a second, buddy. All right. All right, buddy. Um
All right, so how long have you known about me?
About you since Marty fucked with you that one time, and then I haven't
Actually like
He would, Q would throw you around like a rag doll.
You, Marty?
No, Q. Well, Marty was a fucking thing.
Q, though. Q's never been in a real fight and he's like,
okay, so Q came to my crib, bro.
Right?
That was bonfire and he brings his 30 rack.
And that doesn't even give me any of the beers.
You fucking, let me get like, fucking three of them.
Like, fucking pussy.
Sooner or less.
I have my own beers. Thank God. So I'm drinking we're chilling and we have a fire doing my bros with us
And I'm like, let's go to band of crib burrowless stream that like this is fucking boring
This is gay as fuck and he's like, oh, I guess it's not content
Bro because at that time I was throwing half sticks of dynamite and blowing car alarms on fucking stream
And that's what I was doing and going to be in a creeps
being a billion
So no, we get fucking we convinced you to go with us me and my brother
We how long it was this oh
Four years ago
Three and a half. All right. No, let's we get cute or we get we get the dollars right Q at this time. Listen Q didn't even have
Q isn't no one knew Q. I'm the one to put Q 45 on if it was not for Benny
Don't go Q 45 wouldn't exist
Okay, let's go. All right, so we're sitting there. I mean listen, it's me my brother
And I walk in and broke Q45 grabs me bro. He's like boo boo boo. I don't know about this bro
Cuz there's a mattress and there's a bunch of like like someone's definitely living in there. And it's motherfuckers
Who didn't holler and they're like, I'm not going in there, bro. I'm not going in there, bro
My brother's like bro
My brother was getting pissed
I'm getting pissed. I'm like just a little older
Than you it's 22 the time 23
I think I was 22. I was 22 right 21. No, I was 21. I was 21. No, I was exactly 21
I was 21
And we fucking leave it like he beg so he's like oh there must be a homeless guy there
But then beg me not to bring the gun. He's like bro. I'm not doing with the
I've seen cube fucking Mesa homeless guy. Yeah, that's my show exactly. It's just a fucking stupid. He's retarded, right?
This is this is my whole pro you see you're
Bro listen
We're chillin
We're on panel right now. He Q 45 is talking all this shit
Thank God he froze
Okay, oh there he goes. He's back. He's listening. He's listening to somebody. No, I'm looking at something important
Okay, is anyone's what for me?
Just let you know. Okay. I'm gonna have to pick me up. Okay. See you later, RG. Thank you.
Do it. What even is this, dude? Okay, I'm gonna tell him he can take me out to Texas.
Go ahead and talk in the shadow, Mom. Yeah, I can't even go ahead of him. He's just...
Oh, no, Buggers, I have real nice shit going on. All right, that was...
You live in your mommy's house. What are you talking about?
Cock-Sucker, I fucking do asphalt. What the fuck you do?
You're a roofer.
Oh, fuck no, I don't mind a roofer.
I'm tied down, I'm tied down, ain't got no fucking ground.
I fall off this fucking cocksuckin' roof.
Your view count means nothing.
We're good, we're going.
I'll plop that roof out on a fucking day, bitch.
I'll pop that fucking roof out on a fucking day, bitch.
What the fuck you've done?
This is what you fucking are teaching.
You laid fucking 90 ass balls, fucking you and three guys,
laid fucking 90 fucking tons of ass balls.
What you fuck you done in life, bitch?
Nothing.
OK.
Get on your fucking ass, fucking shit.
You besides a clearance school.
Might as fucking bare hand with fucking,
pull your fucking scalp out your fucking head.
Yeah, yeah, let's see if you see if you're so rude for what it's like you're
I want to know you
Sure you would have a dick measuring contest with a 15 year old stop it. Oh
15 so my
Insult cuz I'm 15
First place I think it's the
So fucking you fucking you know, he's young and he acts even younger
Stop it. Just stop it. Oh stop it fucking pussy. Those are the face. I know I know
Just because the genetics fucking fucking made me fucking superior to you. It's my problem. They're fucking just if I
Put the camera back on your mother and let's talk about fucking genetics
Your mom your mom doesn't even have a
Bladder your fucking mother doesn't even know fucking
Shut the fuck up cut that bitch don't even have a bladder at the hundred years of fucking pissing
My mom at least fucking did every dope under the fucking sun still got a fucking pussy
Is it one of those problems?
You ain't got nothing all shut the fuck up. Let's hear it. Let's hear it
Your momma's a fucking whore!
She was a fucking whore!
You can't accept your momma's a fucking whore, you're not your fucking dad's son!
Shut up!
I think that was supposed to do something or mean something. I'm not quite sure
Okay, I think he is a Dempsey, I think he's bragging about his mom's cut which is very strange
Who's fucking talking about cutting here you would just talk about your mom's pussy. It's weird
No, we're talking about a hundred cent. You're let's what was your father. I think he fails you kid
What was your father? Let's talk to him. Let's talk about your father. He's not in the picture, is he?
You can tell but it's not so good. Do you never got this fucking skull in your neighborhood of favorite daddy?
So join the military daddy only chance you're gonna have to live a normal productive life. Oh, where's your daddy at?
That's what I just asked you you obviously
Please do that's what I asked in the first place
Probably a step dad would be my best guess
There's no way
Pardon me, but I would have I would love this
All about listening to it
Again, it's the only chance you're gonna have oh
My fucking every one of my family tells me to join military cuz I can shoot
reason for it
You're the reason why we all tell you this.
I'm telling you to join the fucking military.
It's the only chance you'll have to fuck you up for fucking free.
One wife would give you good advice.
I think Joe's is doing good.
No, I'm not gonna fuck you up for free.
Joe, come on up.
Joe, I want Joe Shibbly here.
Come on.
Dude, don't fucking anybody up, dude.
Seriously.
Look at yourself.
Don't know a fence or nothing. You just don't the tough guy thing just doesn't work. No offense
I'm sorry. I've fed better people
What do you threaten you attractable are you scared like does he look like he's the tough guy at the bar does he?
Thank you. There is Joe. I tried to save you. I tried to save your psyche from like
RG yelling at guys all night, like RG. Come on. I like yelling at people, Joe. And I
tried to be nice to Betty, but even you would probably fucking wipe the floor with this little
kid. I mean, officer saying I never gobbled at you, ever.
What up? Good times. That's good times, right? What up? Good times is right. It's like he
Dragon about doing fucking push-ups
Who did push-ups are G who we talk you look like you shell shocked all the time you come off to me as someone who's seen some shit
And you're trying to figure out that's obviously a fake beard obviously fake peel that motherfucking beard all right now
You can't come on Joe. Yeah, Jack. What does it seem like some old special forces dude who's seen too much shit without it?
Yeah, but I was out
Trying to see the military. I don't believe him
You've got it a Afghani don't fucking lie to me
I mean
Yeah, I thought so
Dragon about doing push-ups with some special forces dude hilarious
Bodies apart and yeah, I kind of thought so
He was the cook while they were in the while they were out there doing their duty
You know, it's crazy he shaved that beard a week ago
Thank you. I wouldn't fucking doubt it. Yeah, he's shell shocked. He looked shell shocked all the time
How you doing, soggy? Thank you for letting me up big dog. It's good to see you got this little pipsqueak
Fragment about how many push-ups he can do
That was little kid think about how tough he is all I shit kind of silly
Oh you left
Physically
Oh my god, bro, I mean, I
Drive it on with Benny and Joe before like either his last pan the last time I did it was Joe was there
Many of us there and is that Joe can talk senses. I think Joe speaks have his language like, you know, not tonight
I can't I'm on my 17 natural light. So the sense talking something like
I would have talked in his special op. I want to talk to this guy that was in the special ops and did push
Just by looking at him
I don't know if I obviously can do push-ups.
You're saying you can cook that.
I'm not sure if I buy that.
Look, look what I can do.
When you were cooking the food, actually,
I don't want to be doing my job.
Look what I can do.
I really like making it.
When you were making the food, like on the mess line,
and you were having a really bad day,
did you ever think about it?
Did you ever think about it?
I
Mean
Oh hell yeah, let that say total an RG let that I can smell it from here suck you let that say it went right up my nose
Instell, thank you, psyche
Hey, you would have loved this Benny guy ghost. You guys can trade off fucking in cell horror stories
Nice
Hey ghost me Benny you two will love each other
Can I see your question untrackable? Can I ask your question sir like does it ever feel like somebody made a voodoo doll
Love you and like they're twisting your arm right now
All right. Well, how about now would be surprised if Alex says who do dogs?
Well, the joke RG the joke didn't land but the joke was like does it feel like a Buddha doll?
It's with your arm. He's like no and then I was gonna be like well how about now like I
It was a sage got in my nostrils
But if he has one, we look at each other's screens and went like this.
That's what we did.
Is that gay?
If that's gay, then you know what?
Call me gay.
That's not gay at all.
Thank you, sir. Thank you. You're in the military. So you should now thank you dude. Don't lie Joe
Anyone to the military be like that brighter or the
Child's play to like that, you know when they go to the military base or is part three. It was part three
That's the best one. Yo, memory when he remember when our chalky crossed the guy in the back of the trash truck psyche. Oh, yeah
Love that's my favorite, but I don't mean ever talk to you. That's my favorite Chuckie part 3
He's fucking awful. I just wanted to say that thank you. So RG
I'm in it's all
Still fucking worst
Untractable, how you doing brother?
I'm doing very good. How about yourself? His name's not unattractable
He's thinking about the last fucking village. He said on fire. Look at why you call him unattractable like that's not his name
So here's your sleep I bet you do
He can't read
call him his f**king name mother f**ker
I will reality Nancy. I'm just playing around. I don't know. I you know, I wish is for your son
You know, you know, some people
Where you can pay for shout outs and stuff
Oh psyche you want to go to a man that looks like
You don't want to pay me anything
there is no
This is Amanda folks. All right, here we go
Yeah, no problem
All right
That's actually be right that's
I mean, she yeah make a cartoon of Amanda
I hope you notice I lost weight
She was kind of fucking hot I will fuck this shit out of her. I'm not shocked
I
See that the bronze bird in the I don't need to see it again. I actually like
Listen if you're showing his picture and making cartoons with them, then you can't be surprised he has words for you
Right fuck. What is bronze bird gonna do about it? You're doing your things like the fuck bronze bird
Yeah
On the other hand, it is fucking awful
And the only reason why she's picking on you psyche is because she thinks it's a cool thing to do
That's the only reason why three days ago she loved you
But she's a phony crazy bitch and I can't stand her
I'd like Christina to help them though
She's just full of it
Do you want to walk out?
I'm like I say if you show you can't be bad that he fucking has something to say about it
Oxy means wanting my house the police came RG knows your fight. He didn't swipe your house. I don't believe that
You were yelling and they call the cops like they always do
There's no way for a wellness check doesn't happen that fast
Was it
Just don't door if somebody comes to your door. Just don't answer it
Kim don't know do you know
Yo, not so much
Excuse me RG. You want to say that to my face pal? Yeah, I just did
I
Jamie's cowboys is saying hi to you in the chat
Yeah, why am I gonna be at like a dork like here?
How is Kim to a person from San Francisco if she's literally in Maryland or wherever the fuck chose?
Because I did not ever team cold 20 out in 81.
Yeah, that's true. Back RG back in the day.
We only got the Ravens in 96, bro.
Can I finish another number?
Oh, I'm trying to tell it.
My uncle played football all through high school and sent me pro football to college.
Yes, the fuck he did.
All right, good.
Please don't even ask why.
like
I don't think he cares that much him he's already moved on
I like when joe is like Kim
Why do I have one roll of paper do you see my favorite towels and
Well give it about an hour psyche and that conversation will probably be happy
You just reminded her psyche. Thanks a lot
I'm sorry, I'll take her nine foot umbrella. You ever seen a fucking umbrella this fucking
Coast is a version and desperately these are pussy. What is a Kim think I'm an old ghostie here
I'm trying to look out for you. He's in the kitchen, but she always girl, which it goes back six months
Good girl
Hell yeah, Jamie Ravens next year Cowboys to Jamie. Oh Jamie's Cowboys the Ravens played the
All right, let me just talk to Jamie one second. Jamie the Ravens this year played the Cowboys on the road
I hope they start the season on like Sunday night football against the Cowboys. That's all the last thing about sports
Jesus Christ. Oh, hell yeah. Is that liquor?
You gotta give a fucking hammer it.
Is that liquor or piss?
Yo, let's fucking go.
I dare you to fucking do a nice 30-second slug of that.
Come on, take that 30-second slug with you.
Hey, singles gonna talk about a small purchase.
What's up, buddy?
Get inside me. Come on.
I
Did you know
I'm a fan of you and what you do go around talking about your shit
Anytime buddy
It is what it is
Today look at six years. Hey, how are you doing?
Yeah, this is the shirt really cheap to kill us actually starting to get yellow
To yellow to drink
No, this one is a margarine. You're gonna have the worst fucking hangover with that
It's like have you ever done some sort of
Ghosts of this seem like the social I do
You seem like I'm drunk
Why does it say BG on it why the fuck's it say BG?
There with BG
Tang breath over here
You fucking whore box back to the kitchen. You've got a
Beesive which I've never heard of this week
Can you abuse goes for us no shit 31%
I could only smoke in the game.
I was explaining to Kim that it's a joke, so it's a guy named BG, and she said it.
Listen, RG, she said it stands for, what does it stand for?
Beta Green.
Beta Green, and BG gets it.
So, it actually makes perfect sense.
It all makes sense.
Well, I said they said that all men's fucking sense now you're fucking Somalia mother fucking or signal and go see both
Let their chin hair their neck hair grow out like that
Signals is more full though. So he went
This is my style. It's fucking fucking nine years to grow that out
Take it down. Oh, there it is. Oh, there he is
So he's got the same thing going on. Yeah, I'm actually going to come up. You are G
Looks like a full like Amish
Listen, it looks better. I think it looks one guy got the beard
I do like to go to everybody we turn their camera on but our team so it makes our team turn his camera on
Hey, go start your camera on, they will have it like our team
I have a career, I'm like a like you bastard shipperizer
I got a career, I'm the queen of England
I do, I got a career
This is a hobby, I'm like
As much as I can understand when people say that
The part that I don't understand is where they're okay with harming others' livelihoods
That's the part that I don't get
I think that's just kind of cowardly
Fine, you don't want to show yourself
Because you have things to lose, that makes sense
But why would you do the same to others?
That's just like a pussy move
But what am I doing to others really?
Besides Groovy Jimmy
Yeah, but then you never
He's the fucking dishwasher
God be him
Okay, it's like he Kim said shake it. Don't break it motherfucker. Why are you doing man? Long time no see
He's trying not to think about all the people. He's killed
He's definitely seeing villages on shit, right?
Seen some shit. He sees some shit. I'm glad it's just not me
The booze doesn't help it kind of helps can I see your face? Can I see your face? No, you can't dumb dumb
The worst things in life are the ones that sometimes they help and then sometimes they don't help and you never know
I see jibbing in chat. I think jibbing in ghosts would be a perfect match
Right. I think you sound like a faggot. No, honestly, she's nice to ghosts. Yeah, fuck her. I don't give a fuck
She sounds like a so are you gay there?
If you're a gay guy, then I'm completely wrong. Do I sound gay?
Yeah, kinda. I
Don't want that bitch
What what's wrong? Why would she be she didn't do anything? She's nice
She hangs around people want to box me
Besides that she's nice and I'm just looking out for you. I retired besides when she arrested very cold and she's pretty cool
She sounds like she's
Yes, he did
Says you can see it right there ghost
What have you been with their way, psyche you've been like gain a little muscle. It looks like there's a goddamn. Why Joe?
He knows
Now nobody wants no only fans fucking whore fucker. She's not only he's a nice girl. She just hates my getter
Thank you. Do you take drugs or such?
People have but I certainly fucking didn't
Honest to God question. Thank you. I can see your rotator cubs, but I know
that's crazy
always been nice
oh that's actually your beard
sorry about that
well joe he wants to fuck you back to the questions though
back to that fucking faggot you're talking about the girl
uh nancy you camped up this is from a panel
fuck nancy
you can suck a dick
very nice
there you go this is why you're an insult who can't get laid
okay from the back
Oh my goodness. He doesn't look like I mean he does sound like what he looks like
Same thing with that Amanda just kind of funny. He looks exactly how she sounds like I bet
Everybody I bet that you look like a dork
I look like a fucking golem from fucking where the rings. Well, let us see it. Why is so scared? Let us see that
Joe exactly
Wow, you look like Sal cover now
You look like a fucking retard. Yeah, look like Baba Buie
You look like Bob Bob Foley
Fuck off who you like RG
Would you say
Say it against like say it against like
No, I'm trackable. What are you like? Are you reading something? Are you thinking about something?
You can't hear you have the time. Oh because well, you know, this it's not a bad microphone
It's something Alexander mayors door dashed me one day and you should hook you up with a register
He would mop the floor with a Benny block. Oh guy
Okay, there you go. Where's the queue was arranged to you?
Well, give you I bond is rich take I bond is rents and give it to Q give our Q. I
Know I vana should join the stream does she sound hot
it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it's been it
I'm just funny
Jimmy and goes the thing I
Want love to blossom. Oh my god, fuck it. Sorry about that. Why?
Again, did you see her Jill? I see the ball clapping
All right
That's a guy that's obviously a man. That's that's Amanda. That was her backstage. No, that's not a band. Oh, that's a man
That's a man. Oh, I got you the one where it's beat. I'm trying to go
That guy was he nice to beat us
You got a thing for a single memory. I fucking lost my not all over face
I want to get next to you. I'd say like psyche looks like the day before Scott Wilder dies
You look like Scott Wildings body. Hello
Well, we'll go with this one. No, we'll go with this one. It's that my favorite Joe pick
No, hold on let me fucking look at it
I don't know. I don't know.
You know fucking
Turn this light bulb off. There you go. Now the little game. You'll be fine. Whoa
Psyche you look as muster as a guy for mouse wits. Who said Jesus Christ?
The only test you ever pass was it you know what another one
I didn't say it
Yeah, that was when I was bored a minute ago. Thank you. Thank you
There's here. I just keep my hair short.
There's fucking hair on my head.
You just can't see it.
That fucking picture.
I took a screenshot of you.
That's what I'm saying.
Make the pictures full screen.
Compare the pictures.
You just got to do it.
He won't do it.
All right.
Now put the other picture up.
Now put the other picture on.
I can do it this way.
Look at the hair.
You guys see the hair off?
Fuck you, Saigi.
There it is.
Put it in the bag.
You hairy motherfucker.
You hairy fucking bag.
There it is. No, that is no mother put it full screen. That is not what the fuck
Foreign Stoic that's for foreign Stoic on AI you fucking view
That was not me guys
Greasefully too. Well, I don't embrace that actually. Can you um, can you anybody were to wrench? Can you ban RG by the way?
No, I'd see that's a joke. That's not you so joke. I have a rent too apparently cuz I made fun
Your ass
Hey RG, I'll make you managing mod for a picture of big clips
Yeah, and I might have to actually try to get excuse on me. I might have to report this stream for dot scene right there
I might have to do it. No, I would never you can't do for me. Can you take one of your streams off members only?
Yeah, that was that's too much. That's me in a minute. Hold on. I
Just need to pull a clip. Thank you 20. Thank you 20 20. Thank you
Oh, I thought you said 20 out of 10
Your band uh, 2020 your band
It was like it was the one me and Amanda. Where are you and I fuck you lay up in that I'm on
Hey, they've I'm all okay. So it's called something smells off dammit. I know that's you're out of here. I'm trying to boo
It was the list or what's cooking wasn't the list it was after that it was like two streams ago
Okay, what's this what's cooking all of them? I'll put you seven. Hey, I'm gonna put it on listed and I'm just gonna give you the link
To it. Okay. Yeah, that works. Okay got it
So you can yeah, you can there you go, and I give a RG a link like
WWW get the fuck out of here dot TV. That's the link. I want to fucking get them. You understand how that works
Okay, RG is
Somebody better way for that. That was funny. Somebody better fucking. Is that here RG? I think it's gonna be back. Oh shit. That's the wrong
Okay, I'll get it for once I don't want to prove that this chick was lying on me when I said I'm sorry you had cancer
and she fucking all right okay it's gonna go backstage and one awful by
Andrew I can't okay it's backstage thank you I've never heard RG say evil
I
Yeah, they say like all the drugs
Oh don't psyche. Let me fuck it's all
after this
After the ass a new truck in 1986 is in your hair. It's so hard to have a conversation with Joe. Oh, fuck you a conversation
It's a fucking conversation
Oh, whoa, whoa, I talk over people. What are you gonna fucking cry about a bitch get the fuck out of here?
No, but I'm gonna state it as fact
Oh, Jesus christ, like I don't even want to
Fuck it punk
putting this one on unlisted and then I'll send me this one.
Oh, but if it's not the right one,
then I'd probably deleted it, because sometimes...
I needed to delete it.
It was just like...
It'll be on Rumble then.
It's probably on Rumble right now, but it's this one.
Oh, I was looking at Rumble.
It didn't make Rumble yet, but let me check it.
So I'll check this one, if it's this one.
Okay, then you get buried like $10,000,
you fucking fat retard.
Don't ever tell me to shut up, you fucking fat cunts.
Oh my god, um, that's my Joe. I'm mods like that. That's so rude
She's a mod. Were you blind when you monitor? Were you drunk? I?
Think this is it. This is the one. Okay. Yeah, it is. Okay. Thank you. You're welcome
You don't think anything for your RG. Okay. No, I appreciate it. Okay good
To you
No, that wasn't good. All right, I'm gonna drop. Okay, man.
Talk to you later. One last yo, yo, yo, he always cracks himself up.
He's doing like the Thundercats Joe you're now you're made her permanent shitless case as Joe
Wow, I mean, I know I want to be up. Oh, that was gonna be another joke. I thought what's that song by L7?
That's the L7 song
You've made my shit list. Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's actually a Patty Smith. I think
Right it's a group of black guys actually, oh you're out of here sick you're out of here. No, let me take it shitless
I think it's Patty Smith. Oh, I
Remember back in the day when like Kirk Cobain will wear t-shirts like the Melvins or the Dolphins
And that's how you knew other music like back in the day there was no YouTube
You had to look at your favorite rock star with t-shirts. They were that's how you have to go to the nearest black guy
Don't hold your fear close to a candle say don't lean down if you have a candle like you might like your heaven
Yeah, and Kate says to Joe glad to know how you really feel about me you alcoholic coke head. I want Kate
I don't feel any way. You just told me to shut up. So I told you to shut up
When you can say that about like at least one-third I like Kate always like paper
I can't really tell me to shut up. I can't say something to her. It's a little joke
Little joke. Hey, I
So you get the neck beard this is this is basically I'm a wizard
That's a flammable neck get the neck beard you get the neck for it when you turn 30 and you're still how a virgin
Say six out Harry Potter when he was like 15 years old and he thinks he's like a wizard
Yeah, right. No, that's what it's harder, but it's so
30 years old and still a virgin you get the beard right so yes, you're saving yourself for marriage
Well, that guy that you marry is gonna be so lucky the day you get married that guy friggin you fucking it's gonna be back
It's gonna be awesome. Like I never knew I was going to marry a guy. I saved it for you
I saved my asshole for you till marriage
Georgie shut that bottle up your ass and get used to it
And his name is Georgie
That's who I'm married to I'm married to this man named Georgie
And we're happily faithful
I'm almost positive there's a song that's like, I can be your Georgia, Georgia.
And then you take a shot.
Exactly, perfect timing when I sang that song.
Thank you.
Your neck pubic here is so, I'm actually going to shave my pubes and glue them to my chin,
just to be like sick actually.
I'm going to do that.
Like hey, look at me guys. You'd like Joe. What's wrong? I haven't already done like Joe
How'd you say that I haven't already done that they like Joe? Why does your neck beer smell like your dick?
I'm like, oh cuz that's where the hair came from. Thank you
Who said that
Anybody got a gorilla glue I could borrow tomorrow
I have a gorilla dick you can suck on you know, that's a key. That's a little too much
Loud I'm so sorry. Oh
You were thinking about
I'm a Guatemalan vagina you can lick it's it's called Wow Guadabra by the way, that's not even wasted. Why drew
He's got a mom. Are you gonna mom? I have I have a flesh like that one of psych
No, I'm waiting for mold to grow inside of it
Fuck you sig you dirty son of a bitch
You see how yellow this shirt is
I thought if you say gorilla blue, I said gorilla dick.
One thing I love about Goodtimes, at least Goodtimes gets the uses out of his clothes.
Like he wears them for like one month, he gets the use out of them.
Yeah, but don't tell me you're, don't tell the nipples, I might get porn play, you know.
You might get porn play.
Psyche, after three more beers, I'm gonna shake my dick, I'm gonna shake my dick, big dog.
Okay, okay.
But we're gonna be with Joe for like another 20 minutes for easy. He'll take three years, bro
But I want you to know some there's a reason they called me Clifford the big red dog back in the day
I'm all balls. I'm all sack. Oh, no
Ginger's rule Rizor says Rizor says are you a Riz? Are you a ginger Riz?
Sometimes when I'm jogging my knees, my ball sack is hitting my knees.
Ouch.
Let me take a picture of that.
That's Corosee.
One jar.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
Sig, are you not going to take off your shirt?
One more jar.
Hell yeah.
Sig, do it.
Shit in the jar.
Do you want to play the soggy biscuit game?
No.
Ew.
Have you heard of that?
No, but what's it what's it entail? Well, we all drink off a random biscuit and whoever's last gets has to eat it
Oh, how about if I was last we just make sick eat it anyway, okay?
Thank you. Thank you so honey sauce like
We can twist the rules a little bit we can twist the rules around that's how the game's gonna go
I think that's a thing that works. Somebody has done that before Joe
That was the best day of my life in college.
Isn't Tripp and Sip the guy that called Bita Lyre
and then came to the panel for a month crying about it?
Like, oh, I did was call you Lyre Bita.
Like Tripp and Sip, you're a fan.
I might be a panel killer, but you're a faggot, Tripp and Sip.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Um, cryptic cryptic blue has heard of the soggy biscuit. You've heard of it. Are you case to the soulless Humphers?
I've heard of this
I mean for somebody to have uh, I mean it must have happened at some point in history
I think it's happened several times probably in the world. I mean the military exists, right? Yeah, exactly
It's like the the sailors right they're like stuck on a on a boat
They they're stuck on a submarine's boats, whatever for
months at a time and there's no women allowed you know and then they're like hey we have all we have
it is a MRE full of biscuits and ours and our horniness let's all i'm pretty sure females and
males in the military are your own submarines it's not an all-male submarine you liar hey
i'm not a fucking all-male submarine is that gay actually it would be it's because they would be
Bad things would happen. Right. So they have to have a soggy biscuit for dinner and dessert and then everything goes well, right? Cheers
Here's queers. Get it together. Surely. What are you calling? Surely?
I'm just kidding. That's all stupid joke. Okay. I'm 15 years older and trippin sip and I'm alcoholic
Well trip at least I have to get drunk to come on these finals. You're retarded. This is here every day sober
You're what you're what we call a loser. You understand English. You're a fucking loser retard
Oh my god, let's calm down on the everybody take it easy
You know what was that I have like like earlier I was on beta's panel. It was Christine Amanda beta. Oh
Those show boys she's so long go check it out go over there
I'm not I'm not gonna watch I just want to like jack off to it. Oh
Get out of here out. I agree. I agree. Oh nevermind
Yeah, no, don't agree with him. I do not agree with that. I meant I mean, I don't agree
That's why I have a D a big pink D right here. It's like do not agree
It's already watched a very disturbing porno involving a butthole and a tennis racket. Okay. I can't take any more of this shit
Exactly. Thank you
So what else is new guys, what's up?
One time when I was like younger psyche, I was playing tennis with my friend and I was fucking with him
And they're having to be like a pile of horse manure rounds
And I fucking I was like here hit this one and I threw the fucking like turd ball
And he fucking was like I'm gonna fucking hit that thing like Pete Sambris and when he hit it
Then he got like shit all over him and I was like, ha ha ha. I don't like you
Little white little white shorts little white tennis model go back over to stand
Let me show so I can go back over to stand look at him to all get my air conditioner
Look at her standing right in front of the fan on her neck. Why is there?
Psychi read your t-shirt psyche
Justice for Kim, what does it say?
Because I like that
I like that, you know what they should change it to because I'm a bitch. That's why cuz she is
On a joe shirt, okay
The more you got me better not say i'm gay and that's why you better not say that it says kim makes me drink
Oh, I thought it would say it makes me horny. That's what I would say
I was yo, and you can only suck my dick if your name is psyche in your oh
Dad come on now. We don't talk. I don't talk about people. I'm gonna just say you were right, but I'll talk about a female
That's what I made for myself
We're not females that I like like other females. I'll fuck anyway
Oh, look, it's like the gym. Hold on. Look, it's like he's going he got
He's got this man. He's not it's not COVID. He don't have COVID, but he's wearing a mask
I know if I go in the store, they say please take that off sir
That's like not really legal to work
But I was like people were wearing masks over their whole face over cove it
I like yeah, they'd like sir. We pulled you over speeding. What the hell is that on your face?
I know a devil answer the door to the the cops
He's like, okay, um, just step outside the door
Never mind
Now I'm four eyes like there you go. I have eyes on top of my head. Oh, yeah, sorry
little horn still nice
No, I'm saying the mask has little horns
That's for you RG
Well, look at this one show you like it's nice. Oh my god Kim. Look at this. He got some of the best
We're here. I just had my camera start all the phone looks like he's gonna show us a mess. Oh my god
Papa shango in the house. Hell yeah
There are no offense like you that kind of looks like Christine. Is that a Christine mask?
Yeah
Wow, that's pretty cool
See my Christine picture joke. Yeah, I did it. It was pretty funny. You know what does it say one thing?
It was fucking hilarious when you made the picture Christine flying on the like a witch. Why the fuck?
Yeah, that's hilarious. Why are we so now this community is so far like gay that we can't even laugh at this
This is what we should be laughing at
It's hilarious. It's only a joke, Christine. Joe
Stop is no sensitive
I don't want to be rude sucky but because of that picture you're actually going to jail so put your hands up for your skinny
Put your skinny
Going to jail for this one. I'm Joe. I'm going to jail for this one
Hold on. Have you seen this one, too?
Hello?
Is that one, Joe?
No, you know, what's one thing I like about bonds bird
How the fuck does he find a little tiny crown the put on her bird set like that crown is the size of a dime?
It's a I it's on a real everything so I think I'll say one thing to you. This is the truth
That is what I believe and only what I believe
I think bronze bird is not like he don't act like this in real life, you know
But on the panel with old ladies like I'm gangster. I'm bronze bird like bronze bird
I would slap you in your face and just be like what the fuck you gonna do about
And I told him I said you want my honest opinion. It's fucking terrified. Well, psyche loves a i so
Well, psyche loves a i so you're fucking with somebody that loves a
Well, I know what real is fake and I know like I'm sorry, but I know real and fake and you're real psyche
You're a real man. You're a real motherfucker. Thank you. I
Like when you troll the fucking I like beat I like Christine no problem, but I like when you fucking troll them
It's fucking fun. It's fucking funny. It's what keeps it going. I think it is
Like if you and psyche and beat up like we're all best friends like nobody want to join like oh, they're just kissing each other's ass all day
I like that person someone send me that photo. It's really disturbing. Oh my god
Is that Chris? Oh, is that Chris summary? I hope not. It's like a turkey. I don't got either
But I'll tell you right now. She has some nice thighs. Oh
Get it. Nice thighs nice breast. I can't
No, other photos I have are like mini Manson with a razor by his vagina. I
Love what made me man? I like mini Manson, but I love when he gets all aggravated like oh somebody troll me tonight
I'm never gonna go live again, and then like the next day. He's like singing sweet dreams. I'm made of lost
Okay of lust
who am I to glue a net beard on I want to look like fucking sick everybody's neck
is airy I want to dance for Joker though
oh my Christ Peter Kim look at this
Oh, yeah, that's a real man right there. Look at him. He's doing it again. Look at
Christ, I wish I would have my camera off. I wish my eyes were off when that happens. Oh my gosh. I wish I could have turned my eyes off.
Yo, don't be cruel. Come on.
Don't be cruel
You're very skinny you need to get away. You're 95 pounds of excellence. Thank you
I had a friend of mine that was literally as skinny as you are she was 95 pounds wet. Where is she now?
In the face
So yeah, I'm gonna be myself real quick
I'm gonna pack a bong and smoke up what you don't mind
I'm just gonna be myself for a minute big dog. I understand a little bit of my cigar
That's all you look like Kurt Cobain's uncle. Thank you. Hey, you know what? You know what color or Kurt Cobain's eyes were
Shit brown no, they're blue because he blew them all over the place
Okay, now it's bad. I'm sorry. I
Don't think I got the joke exactly right though
They're blue, but the blue blue the mouth or something. I forgot
Hello
Okay, he's doing it. He's doing it. Oh, he's taking I'm hitting the bomb, but it's just to back to backer
My bomb thank you reminds me the old man crucified on the heart shape box video clip. That's not very flattering
She eyes me like a Pisces when I am weak
Courtney Love hired a hitman to kill me
What did I just say?
Shit
Okay, well, I'm gonna play my I'm gonna play my my my new video again
Like this is called buddy troll enjoy this guys while Joe's taking a bong it enjoy this to Joe
They'll be right here. There you go. It's right back or should I play the rodeo? I'll play the rodeo song
This is the road. This is called rumor rodeo
Sorry, it's great. Oh, sorry when you're done shaking your ass. I'm dancing right now
Don't trust your pelvis to us
Is that John Depp
Just a trailer full of gossip with my picture on the frame
You take a half truth to the tavern, let it soak all night and gin
By the time the sun comes up, you swear the devil wrote it in
You paint a little shadow till it covers up the sky
But a light dressed like a sermon is still alive
It's a rumor, rodeo, round and round you go, swinging that lasso like you run the whole show, big talk, cheap shots, boots full of bling, new day, same to same old gang.
You can dress it up in glory, you can make it sound grand, but gospel ain't gospel just because it's light and plain.
built by association, built by look, by laugh, by chair
if somebody waves hello, you say they must be in on there
you throw mud at the wall and call the man
I love this fucking song
thank you
At the town square type of stone
Wrapping up a mainstream in some self-righteous uniform
But I ain't here to wrestle tumbleweeds or argue with the rain
I know the difference between sunshine and somebody's need for fame
I'm gonna send you my favorite fucking song.
I
Eat your heart out Metallica
Thought it was over sorry about that I was over
Your heart out my town arrow snips fucking boring sniff. This is better
Yeah, we lost a lot of those first episodes RIP man that I don't know why you're mad
I didn't I thought RG was showing us me an episode of
Of Roseanne
Before that song started Kim's nipples were fine, but now they're like missiles. So that song really did something to my friend
Thank You psyche. I
Mean, I don't know how you feel a big dog. How you feel good times nice to see you
Yeah, I'm um, I've just got nipples on my mind all of a sudden hell yeah
Did your dad grow your grass today? Oh damn. I got a fucking 18 pack on my mind. I
Can actually see your heart beating psyche. You're so skinny. I can see your heart beating mega turn that shit off
Put a shirt on I can see your orchids
I can see you're kidding me, Spare.
Where's my organ?
I'm just kidding.
Oh.
That's a big one.
I like your bone too far.
I like you far.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you for letting me on.
It's like, we're having fun tonight.
We're having fun.
Got a hug and kiss?
Remember back in the day when panels were actually like fun to join?
Like, oh, this is going to be fun.
Like, nowadays it's like, oh, God, like, what the fuck are they going to cry about today?
I think I want to bring back fun panels. I want to bring back fun panels, you know, it's like
I watched Sam and it used to be about like like cooking now. It's all about like
God bless America Sam and shut the fuck up you fucking loser
And then now it is all big trouble doing your makeup for six hours and then it's all everybody's friends
Everybody talks it's like one group one group gets together and they're all friends
And then they attack another group and then they don't never say nothing else or they get banned
It's like west side story where it's like
You know, you know, one thing I was like, one thing I do like about you, brother,
I give you a fist pound. I actually put this fist where you don't want to, or the sun to shine.
But listen, one thing I like about you psych that you don't cal down, at least you fucking
still fuck with them and troll them. It's all, this is what YouTube is. It's fun. We're up here
to fucking troll. I mean, it hates me more than life itself. She said, let's be on our show. So
I'll go up there and like, you know, have fun and like one thing. Go ahead. But one thing I hate
When Christine joins the panel sometimes she'd be like, how dare you say that about this?
Like Christine shut the fuck up. This ain't fucking you. I don't know. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to tell Christine to shut up. I was talking to Kate. I love you.
That was a joke, Kate. I like it. It was a big bump for me 2020, not this to me, but I'm open to either.
I'm just kidding. What up la la. There's a W in the chat. La la
You don't know Christine so don't stop did you hear that Christine knows husband is across I did hear that
But how would you know that? 95 years old though? I mean
In the morning where Christine like makes herself a cup of coffee and her husband a cup of coffee
I bet she fucking puts something in his coffee to get my drift.
Yeah, she's slowly killing him.
She's slowly killing.
All right, I want to do more.
Eye drops?
That's bad.
Oh, my coffee tastes a little bit like science.
Look at who's coming.
Aldi, my boy.
Why does my coffee taste like cyanide because I'm married to Christine?
What's up psych? What's up? I miss you, honey. Where the fuck do you buy a grade of gay blue t-shirt at?
Did you guys watch the fucking the the the space launch?
When William Shadiner went to space that was fake. Oh today mother fucker today. Where did they go in the moon? Yeah
Already you're a brother to me brother, I love you
Historical event
Whoa, I'm actually glad I missed that one glad I missed that
There was
Yo, why don't you go ahead Joe yo go live in WrestleMania on 18th already
We're gonna have fun to shit watching WrestleMania, brother. It's gonna be a good as car
We're gonna 19th. Yeah, exactly. I'm gonna get drunk for the whole weekend. I'm getting drunk all week
I'm gonna be naked actually. I'm actually gonna be new
Man on rumble we could all get naked if we
So why do you look like Mr. Burns?
Yeah, what?
Rock child.
What is your body look like Mr. Burns' body?
I mean, while he's so skinny,
he can wrap his arms around his whole body.
You're like Mr. Burns without the money. You're like a poor Mr.
I wanted to ask you though, listen motherfucker
Why why does these bitches try to extort you and cry when you be talking shit and you well said
right. Why don't you stay as bitches be on your gay dick huh? I don't know. It's easy.
It's easy. All the other women can talk shit on psyche but if psyche talks shit then he's
the evil man. Like it's slightly darker than he's the evil man.
Don't I get I don't get it either. All day. It's just confusing. It's like, you know
I'll tell you what it is. It's basically if you don't agree with Sam man and
Oh, then you're the bad guy
He's never apologize psych. Thank you never apologize. Yeah, all of you can tell and I like Sammy
But you could tell Sammy and never stuck his dick in a pussy because he's like kissing
He's old ladies and it's like oh don't talk about my 85 year old friend. They can fuck you Sam, man
What's funny to me though, what's funny to me is like
that girl Christine that girl Christine, you know
Dog as bitches she likes she tried to like porn bomb me with my boys signals cock on
rumble. Yeah, and like it but it was too small
People on rumble you can't porn bomb people on rumble
Yeah, it's like
Another view that they just love it
People try to fit in I think it's funny. Ha Joe. Did you already did you call her out when she did it like ha ha don't work
So I was busy poising to my husband during that time, but
What Christine stop wouldn't sign on your fucking poor husband's coffee. Oh bag
Yeah, stop fucking poor and fucking goddamn bleach and your husband's fucking cop
Yo, remember when these panels remember what?
Oh, oh, we got a blunt coming up here boy. Take a look at this already Joe. Tell Kim. I said what's up?
You show the blunt again Joe
That should look like a fucking birthday candle.
Are you fucking dead ass?
Wow, that's the thing where they go.
Thing is actually drugs.
Try to do some once in a while.
You're fucking retarded, John.
I'm retarded?
Yeah
Because we're not in cells
Where's Lala
Hey, oh my god, bro
Lala I said I've never talked to sing again than the next day
Where next he's like I think I like it's crazy
Day by day tell me the story of what she said, uh, oh, I hope you die
I
Yeah, one trackable if I were to see you in real life
I want that that bitch Lala. I want to aim that
Recarded bitch Lala. I want another track on trackable is like what good times wishes he was
What up good times cousin keep robbing your hairy face you motherfucker
You hairy son of a bitch
Joe, Joe, for real, WrestleMania 2 Night of Man, you motherfuckers.
That's gonna be awesome, fuck you, bro.
You better fuck this a lot.
Yo, but listen, already I got a new phone, so I can't come into your rumble and
chat, you gotta drop the stream yard.
That's the only way I can join now, cuz I can't sign up for rumble again.
What the hell is that?
That's my boy, Steve.
To the world crash Bendicoot
Bucket Squidward. I know you ain't wear a pants. They got no you ain't got no pants on but
Motherfucker just buried a body in the middle of the day
I actually wore that same shirt in seven fucking grade
Motherfucker is look-snaxing right now. I got mad. I knocked that boy out. I knocked that boy out
boyfriend
Young dating Squidward now
Oh, yeah, I feel bad for you. That's the fucking guy you're dating
Well, we clean that 713 shirt was fucking faggot classic you look like a fucking guy you look like so sexy
Well, I'm taking my girlfriend is peach and my boyfriend is obesity. So stop it
I know I look so good all these us winger
Fucking weirdo
Yo, the fucking is the it is this shit back back on earth or the astronauts back on earth right now
Bro, it's gonna take them like six hours to get to the moon
Yeah, you're not going to the moon bitch. What the fuck up
You know honestly like
What I was thinking like today like why would we send like four super smart people up to the moon?
I was thinking like because how the fuck do you think that you're gonna get to the moon?
How do you think that you get you think that you're gonna put a fucking dog in a in a spacecraft and this
Fucking stupid retard
Yeah
You think that it was gonna operate the fucking shit
send all five of us
fucking smoke down
send all six of us to the moon
this fool's psych is jacking up
this fool is
jacking up
this nigga is literally jacking up
that's crazy
fuck
yo
that's something that's going on
that's crazy
this nigga was actually jacking up
It's like a machine gun
All right, that's too far. That's it. You can only jack off when Lala's on stream
Yeah, you can you can definitely
Yeah, I'm trying to smoke a blunt in kid
Let me see the blunt then
I'm trying to smoke a blunt
Kid's like you gotta hold the hole
You gotta hold the hole
I didn't know I was smoking a blue whale
You fucking hole in it
You gotta hold to this
You wanna see a little hole in it?
This motherfucker Joe's
And we're lippin' the blunt
She didn't even get a hit herself
You're and we're lippin' the blunt
Joe, stop and we're lippin' it
Stop makin' the tip so wet
Come on, Joe.
Worst hit of weed ever took.
That was the worst hit of weed ever took.
Stop N wording the word.
The word.
Hit, dawg.
For what?
Because you can't hit it?
basically stop being weird you know what I would just be like already I would
slap you and be like what the fuck you're gonna do about it bitch
Baltimore during summer I could stay there for a week we're gonna fight
every day not each other we're gonna fight other people not each other
We're gonna do a job for you. We talked about this. I'm gonna do a job for you right before I fly back home
I'm gonna can I ask your question already already can I ask your question, sir?
This ain't about you Tim listen
Do you remember one time when Q45 was on the RV and Saint 10 spit on Q and Q was like I dare you to spit on me again
Nick, I'm gonna tell you right now, somebody's gonna have a fucking clip of that.
Listen to me.
I have a clip of that, hold on, I gotta find it.
I dare you to spit in my mouth.
No, I would actually lick the spit up and say yum.
It tastes like bull.
I'd actually beat the shit out of it.
No, no, that's a little too hard.
Spit.
Spit in again.
You have your two in square word.
Nice walking in bulldozer.
I would have been like, I would have been like,
next time can you spit on my dick?
I'm like, yeah, next time get to spit on my eyes
and get it right on my cock.
Right on the people like that shit
Get your spit a little more accurate
You need to aim for my penis instead of the ground why is where we're sure white in the sleep
Peter mouse said all these did you see that artwork Alex made of psyche recently?
I don't give a fuck about Alexander Meyer. Exactly
Who the fuck even do the fuck said if you see that Peter South said hey Peter South
She has a
Disappointed in her, uh, at the end of the day, fuck Alexandra Myers, she's a stupid bitch, she makes memes, I make real content, fuck her!
yo imagine being a loser like peter south in the chat like did you see what
Alex did like peter south
Look at the driver drive full speed into this fucking gas station and blow himself up
Look at them this panel so born. I would have drive into a wall
Anybody got a coffin I can borrow
Squiddy poo
What a fucking loser squiddy poo
That's so
You didn't do anything right. I was just trying to pull you into it
I bet you you won't drive into that gas station full speed on fire. Yeah, I bet you won't blow yourself up
I bet you won't light yourself on fire and drive headfirst into that gas station. I bet you won't
I bet you won't put a bottle rocket up your ass and light it.
That's too far, Kim.
Kim, that's too far.
Kim, come on, Kim, chill, Kim.
Really, Kim?
We're just talking about the guy lighting his body on fire.
Don't shove a rocket bottle.
What's it called, a rocket bottle?
Shove a rocket bottle up your ass.
A Roman candle, is that better?
A Roman candle.
Don't talk about Roman brains, the tribal cheese.
The tribal cheese.
Roman candle. Don't call in that. Take a Roman candle right up his ass. Let him shoot out pretty colors.
I'm gonna have to do you like a stable.
Look at the sky. Look at the sky.
When you went to the barber, you said give me the full Amish, like give me the Amish.
You busted him up and then died.
that's crazy
maybe looks like a fucking drama
Squidward's hair looks sick
bro that fool has like a
nice bang
nice bang spad
he has a sick dad's hair
well if your my dad has hair back
you fucking opposite
this doesn't need your hair cut actually
Shut the fuck up, man.
I'm on fire, yo. Blackout Andy, thank you for the rage.
Yo, it looks your hair looks pretty fine.
It looks like you're in oasis.
It looks like you're an old Gallagher, actually.
Look at Squidward, man.
That looks so white.
But I'm a fucking beater. How does that make sense?
Your head's like a sizable dick.
This room is crazy.
Yo.
Joe shit, please show your hair. Yo, Squidward say you're my Wonderwall cuz your hair is like the same as Oasis
Say can you say I'm your Wonderwall brother?
Thank you already. I can say anything. They know what you want to say boy. I want to see your fucking hair
Well, that's a little too far and I want to see your your bail on your hat. Let me see if it shrunk
What it why would it strip? I'm not like you the things don't be don't shrink already. I'm not like you
Where's good times, you know, you're watching good times like what else is good times do it right now
Nothing get up here motherfuckers times is out of money and out of beer. So he's not gonna join for
Hey fucking
You know what good times is right now he's figuring out how he's gonna survive because his aunts gonna kick him out soon
That's what he's doing. Sorry. La la no link for you, baby. Just
Laughing because it's not funny. Are you flexing?
Faggot and I feel bad for him
the
of the
i already hired a homeless guy in michigan to like
i hired a black guy to come in bro i'm gonna be there one way or the other i'm there
yeah you too bro there's gonna be over a thousand people there like is he gonna tell us all to go
away like easily a thousand i don't think i'll say it's over close to ten thousand
try to shoot
I'm hiring I'm hiring a guy to throw a thousand fucking flyers
Right over Lapeer, Michigan off of a plane
I'm being serious. All right, I believe it. I'm not be awesome. All right
He requested a bouncy house, so we're going to get him a bouncy house.
Aw.
It's going to be a bunch of liquor.
We're going to have, literally, we're not going to really have to pay for anything.
The vendors paying for the spot on good times property are going to pay for the whole event.
Exactly, they'll make the money back three dollars three to five dollar tickets. I
Emailed a couple bands. I think
Biscuits gonna come out. No
Listen, I told good times I told good times like
We're gonna make like 50 K
That weekend is
I'll give you 90% I just want 10%
Until he sees the money. He's gonna be like, all right, Aldi. That was cool. Whatever
Plus, you know
We're gonna fucking pull up on good times. We're gonna have a good time
Alright, go ahead faggot keep talking you fucking blue shirt wearing Harry fucking bitch
Come up and
That's not what you just call me. What the fuck you just call me
Boy
Aren't you aren't you a Mexican?
Excuse me, don't you ever fucking call me that again
What we're gonna get super fucked up. We're gonna like eat a bunch of food get super fucked up and then
June 20th is when the bands come out. We're all hungover
We all on LSD and mushrooms and we all fucky and we all have sex with each other
And then we're like well Ivan is here shady. We're wearing a bra on our tie-dye shirt nice nipples. I've on a nice
up a lot of these bitches are going to get trains ran on her
they're going to fucking see his face
the thing about it is I have like a thousand NDA contracts
so like whatever happens at Good Stock
does not leave Good Stock
or else you're going to get sued
exactly, that's the old saying
whatever happens in good times backyard stays in his back
it's a listen I don't even know where good times live but I'll just drive through the pier and like as soon as we see the back like
We have shipping delivered this week, and I told the guy like yeah, we told the guy
We told the guy just keep driving through the pier until you see the bamboo
Yeah, like you see 20 foot bamboo that's just that and like the
the 12 feet corn. Yeah. Yeah.
taller than his house. Yeah.
I don't know where I'm at but
I'm in like a maze of 12 feet
corn. Oh, you're at you're at
the right spot. You're at the
right spot. Look at the fucking
The moon is like so crazy looking wow the moon the moon is
Like bro, there was just a fucking god damn
What
The moon
Go ahead
Dry, it's like look at me. I'm dry
Let him talk the strong silent type wants to speak
Yo gay guy on track a bar you fucking like a mute. Are you deaf or something?
More or less
Cat got your beard
I mean, I don't I don't have an orange dick
Don't talk about my sister like that
Yeah, your your sister is
Nigga your beer your jaws are creaking when you talk I can hear you put some wd-40 in your fucking jaws next time you talk
Yeah, you know why a trackable is not talking this because none of us are gay. He only talks to gay men
Yeah, 100% that is actually
He's like he's so active whatever a gay guy is talking
What's up on trackable what you're doing to have a train run on you or what bitch
He has been staring at sick for the last hour. He's been staring at sick for the last 45 minutes.
Yeah, why are you staring at sick, bro?
He's not gay. He's just allergic to women.
Wow, it's like a big piece of hair with teeth.
He's not gay. He's only allergic to women.
It's like a piece of hair with teeth coming out of it.
Not gay. I just get hives. I get hives.
Dude, that moon looks so fucking weird and crazy.
Ivana Punches talks to me and I start getting hives.
Yeah, I'll definitely make you swill. Oh
What the fuck I can smell your cold sore from here Ivana, so stop it
Show your show your cold sore signal you showed it on clubs. He's show your cold sore
They gotta have a cold sore. What the fuck?
Oh, that was a joke
My lips are chapped
Yeah, because the alcohol dries your lips out
Yo, you know why signal smokes fentanyl cuz it cures aids and herpes is that well, yeah, it goes games
That's Georgie Georgie Floyd. Well, it's actually French. It's Jorge. It's actually
Motherfucker
And he's gotta chase it and he's gotta chase
Oh my god, what about what's wrong with the chase?
It's not a war, it's a fucking skin tag.
You're a bitch, I guess.
What the fuck are you saying?
You ain't a bitch, I always chase it too.
You think how many people do you chase in pussy?
You think you're the hottest people in pussy?
You're my bitch.
That's gay.
Remember when stop speeding, remember when stop speeding showed his cock and it had like a general
look at Lala's comment, and he was like, that's not a genital war, that's a God with skin tag.
Lala, you do need saving. Lala does need saving, good times is just not the one for that.
Yeah, you know, how does it feel that she picked good times over you?
That's how you feel you feel like a loser it's understand
Like still best for Stallone and the Rockies stop being weird I'm sad about it. I'm actually very sad about it
I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I've had a lot. I
I bet you this fool got a badass for Psyche.
Bang!
I've never seen it.
Show them cheats.
And who's called who gay around here?
And who are they doing here?
I'm calling you gay.
All right.
Are you acting?
Because I'm going to be in their cheats.
Are you caging or something?
Are you caging?
of the
I'm going to make sure that you're unbanned from all the bars involved more, Joe.
And I'm going to handle the job for you, Joe.
That you are.
That's what I'm going to handle.
That's what I'm going to do.
Joe, I'm going to handle the job for you.
And then I'm getting the fuck out of Baltimore.
That's what I'm going to handle.
You're on track, but when I see all the in Baltimore,
I'm like, why is there a fat Aiden Ross in my house?
I'm like, no, it's already, sorry about that.
He looks like a Jewish Aiden Ross.
That's a fucking, that's a goddamn fucking compliment.
I love Aiden Ross, motherfucker.
that I haven't worked out in 20 years and I
Yeah, look like you're fucking look like
You're in a wheelchair. You're in a wheelchair, bro
Roll your ass off the grand canyon get in your wheelchair and roll your ass right on the fucking wheelchair
Can you roll into like traffic?
I would still I got how the fuck is your wheelchair at four wheel drive
But there's only two wheels to begin with what the fuck is going on say does your beard ever gets stuck in the wheels?
You ever felt like an old meal in your beard like oh, I'm hungry and I found like yesterday's lunch in my beard
Aldi, can you crash your ram into a lagoon they're shut up. You sound like you're in a fucking bathroom squibber
Shut the fuck up faggot
Yeah, don't fuck with me bro. I got shooters by the dough. Me and Joe Shipley. We're gonna break the internet when I go to Baltimore for a week
you'll probably break your own asshole, tripping on a five-month...
Yeah, my asshole's gonna be broken, Joe's ass is gonna be broken.
Listen, if you man up and come to Baltimore already, we're gonna have fun, motherfucker.
We're gonna have fun.
That's what I'm saying.
Just don't...
I don't wanna smoke weed, though.
I don't wanna smoke gay weed.
I don't wanna smoke...
And then Baltimore are full of dumbasses like Joe Shipley.
Well, I say they might be dumbasses. They don't look half as gay as you squibber. They might be dumb
Now fake $20 bills to the blacks in Baltimore and we're gonna create a whole another George Floyd BLM protest
Yeah, you know what I'm gonna do already. I'm gonna where we're about to we're
I'm gonna go to the first person that looks like Squidward. I'm like y'all want to knock you the fuck out
They'd be like why I because you're like this fucking gay guy. I know from YouTube fucking loser
And I'll come up behind them and I'll slit his throat
Y'all already one thing I do want to do with you when you do come over here like I want you to get into a fight
And I'll just listen, I'll just walk away and then when you're talking shit to him,
I'm gonna sneak up behind him and just fucking knock that nigga out.
Well, we don't fight fair. We don't fight fair. We don't fight fair.
We scratch out your eyeballs. We don't fight fair.
We lie. We cheat. We steal.
I'm going to bring it. Yo, Joe, what are you going to say when like I, I grab somebody's eyeball and I put it in my pocket.
And then whenever we're back at your house, I pull it like three eyeballs out of my pocket.
Well, do you know what I would do? You know what I would do I would show them and then I would put it into dry ice
And then I would smash you with a hammer
There's no fucking chance you're gonna recover
I'm in a pickle jar and then we're gonna eat your eyeballs
We're gonna put his head and we're gonna put his head in a pickle jar
I'm gonna put your balls on the rice
All he's coming to Baltimore Kim. He's coming see that couch. You're sitting on Kim. That's where all these
Peach peach. We're going to Baltimore this summer. Are you ready? He's just coming to hell
Only Kim and even my girl, but I'll double date if you impeach coming in cable double day with y'all
the
I'm not talking about dudes, but if it came down, that's why you get a fat girl
I'm not getting laid down, but like at the end of the day it's like if shit goes south
If I knock somebody out and he just getting her ass kicked
I'm gonna suck her kick a bitch in her head. Yeah, if somebody
Like yeah, there's no fucking chance what if she knows kickboxing
Now that when you consider like that it makes more sense
You better watch your mouth. Say you can knock the fuck page will hold the bitch down and I'll just suck or kick her after I
Knocked out here
You know, I remember one time already when Brittany was alive
She got to a fight at the bar and I was like, I don't even care if it's a woman. I'm gonna fucking knock
But I'm not gonna let Brittany get beat up. I'm gonna knock this or out and I did and I got arrested and went to jail
You said when Brittany was alive
Well, she's passed away. You know, it's you got hair in your ears. You got a beard in your ears
It's like a fucking beard with teeth just
So it's like a fucking beard with buck teeth
Yeah, we got a big one. We're gonna run through all the Georgie tonight
Did you go into my discord today when like
Somebody posted the clip of you saying all of all these dreams are watching black people reels
People fight and then he goes and then he watches
NBA 2K and everybody on the team is black.
So what did SIG say that was a lie?
I don't hear anything SIG said that was wrong.
That's a great clip.
Listen, I love black people.
I'm an African.
I love black people.
Wow.
Well, actually, it's a black people party.
You know how many black people play basketball, baseball, fucking football, I love black people.
Only good, nice, awesome blacks.
10% african or he is i know kim slammin but he actually is
Please join the stream
Join the stream i promise not to be
I just want to fuck the shit out of you like i really want to
No disrespect
I want to make you fucking squirt
No
Dreamyard.com
Take a shot say thank you. There's no way that like anybody could join in here. You guys like dead ass like
All of a sudden, all of a sudden the trifecta, the quadruple, the fifth, motherfuckin' case!
Oh my god, is that the fifth needle?
Is that George Harrison's baton, son?
All of a sudden, the fourth horseman, me!
Oh my god, he went through the barber's head, giving the ring your skull!
And now you guys want a joint, shut the fuck up!
Go join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join, join,
Piece of shit. Take a sippy sip, squiddy poo.
Let's go.
That had a cigarette.
I already did.
Retard.
This is my last beer.
Oh
No, I'm not porn bombing the gay guy. That's gay. Yeah, right. That's gay to poor bomb a gay guy
I mean, come on. I only got a gay guy is super
Saved the poor bomb for a heterosexual guy saving for a real and bombing like you got a porn bomb a gay girl
I'm not poor bumming psych because I'll tell you this I respect psych for not
apologizing to these bitches. These bitches are trying to control the psych.
So I could poor bum you. That's an Audi. That is an Audi.
They really are trying to control with this.
Lala, go live. I want to do the helicopter. I want to do the helicopter, Lala.
You're trying to I'm trying to like go like no distance with my propeller
No, he's not our day. He's laying down, but
Thank God they can't let black RG. That's the reason I'm so up here. Thank God. They get because all everything black RG says
He's like, yeah, they're every fucking thing. He's like Freddy
It's actually like black Freddie Mercury. I like black RG, but he is turning into like
Can I say somebody I like black RG is like a speed bump when I tried my truck
I like to just roll him over like a speed bump like oh was that a speed humber was that black RG?
Cuz I don't give a fuck what it was. I'm gonna back over it actually
I'm actually gonna put it in reverse and back over
This is the bitch, you got a simp on.
Whoa, what the hell, is that like a fucking circus?
Is that a clown?
That's a witch, I think that's a bitch.
What the fuck is that?
I like that.
I think that's a gypsy.
Where's the bruhat?
That's like a psychopath.
Don't decide a bruhat.
It looks like an emergency.
The eyes don't like, chief.
No, it's not.
Already moved out of the way so can't see it. Well, that's that's uh, somebody. Oh, what the fuck is that?
That's me though you motherfucker. That's your best friend. That's your best fucking friend
Vita, you're very good looking. They called you in the wrong time.
And I hate to absolutely will not come to the defense of Vita.
But what I will tell you is that you can catch just about anyone
at a really awkward face.
We don't need a fucking guy like including yourself, bitch.
You don't need one.
It's what you don't want to fuck this Egyptian whore.
That's a which that's not my fault, bitch
It's not my fault. So which regard
So which wise awkward silence
Have some silence for the victims of beta
None of you niggas are being silent
All right, shut the fuck up, then bitch starting with you
Starting with you shut up. I want to have the last word fuck you
Fuck you
Good words shut up
Shut up. Well, how long is this goddamn fucking now all of us have to shut up for there to be silent
You're fucking stupid dude shut the fuck up already
Which one of these bitches do you want virgin bitch
You've never even had sex with a woman, and you're over here calling them out. Oh, I'm sorry
Already you got the Rolling Stones logo behind all the shut the fuck up Joe shut the fuck up everyone shut the fuck
You fuck you
Let Joe Shippley talk all these shut up. No
Shut up
Talk to beat us. We're gonna talk after the fucking moment of silence, bitch.
You're just like Sandman. You want a moment of silence, bro?
We're gonna talk after the moment of silence, you fucking retard.
You want a skit kitty gang? Go pay your cat, fool.
Shut the fuck up.
Moment of silence for a kitty gang.
Because kitty gang died tonight.
I would fucking kill all the kitties in the kitty gang.
They should read in kitty gang stinky gang because they're old pussies all them only what are you using to make your background
transparent because it's all fucked up and retarded
What is it that you're using because you're using the fucking worst thing possible
You're retarded
Imagine six cats like be like imagine the smell in her house like no wonder she's been divorced three times
Yeah, if I was two blocks away from
That was a way to sell a joke already.
But if I was two blocks away from Christine, I'd be like,
did anybody smell like cat food?
I'll be like, ooh, that's Christine's old puss.
Thank you.
Did anybody smell a black person?
No, that's Albie.
Anybody smell a dead cat. Oh, that's Christine's tits. Does anybody smell a black person's ass? Oh, that's all
Already already that's too far. Now, you know what? That's all
There's a major black though, so you'd be smelling your black person dogs ass
the
The
What's it called Matt coms damn bridge third Avenue Bridge?
This is for all the witches the power of Jesus Christ will fuck you up witches
Willis Avenue Bridge can't forget that one
Witches
The power of Christ compels you.
Bang!
It is what it is.
Sometimes the truth hurts.
Sandman won't go live until this weekend.
And he's just collecting clips.
He just went live. I'm sad man
That guy said man at the end of the day
At the end of the day that dude Sam man was scared to link up with me
Little nigga
I'm a little nigga I'm five foot six. Oh, I'm a small person
Damn I feel bad
Hey, what why I didn't hear that what he's awful said he's five six tall cool Sam yet
No
I'm really scared
Sam and but I still
Understand that I went at three in the morning with all of the blacks
That are they're waiting for their methadone. They have to wait for the methadone clinic to open up
they're just walking around the block like fiends like they got like they're
like fuck I want my next hit
you're smoking joker stairs joker stairs pull up to the joker stairs
bro isn't it funny though like like bro like uh signal like yesterday when like
clumsy was doing a stream and like how Sandman was crying
Tommy was crying all these motherfuckers were crying about what clumsy was doing in the middle of the night
That shit was funny as fuck to me, bro
These motherfuckers are so easy
To literally destroy. Oh my god
Clip it and ship it react to this Sandman 1k. You're a bitch fool
And when I go to fucking New York after we stop listen
I'm gonna go to goddamn
Baltimore this summer and me and Joe are gonna drive to Lapeer, Michigan, and we're gonna go like uh like hang out with good times and
Then we might spin the block and go to fucking New York. We might go to make it happen and pussy
Do it
Yeah, and we'll get your fucking retarded ass five six ass out of the house
That was fucked up
Can you hear me Aldi yo fit move that motherfucking thing I'm talking Aldi
All right, think of all the people that have died before us like on this earth and all five of us are lucky to be on this panel right now
We're having fucking fun as shit. I love all of you. I love already the best and psyche square word
I'm actually close to my eyes when I look at you, but say it's all I love you guys man
Yeah, I really do
Man, we get one right being gay
Stop being a homosexual, bro
Was that gay? I was trying to tell Kim that Kim just getting into it
Was that gay chat put a one in the chat if that was gay put a tube it was gay
You look like a lot of five in the chat if you went to Target and bought a big blue t-shirt like already did fucking
Erie animal looks like a large bar quad
Put a fucking fist in the chat that I can put right on Aldi's jaw and knock his ass out when I see you Joe
Nigga fucking Aldi listen, I know it's nice to know you bro
But if I ever fucking you ever aggravate me in real life like Aldi listen
I know we're only on YouTube
But if you ever talk down to me when you're in Baltimore, they got beat the shit out of you boy. Yes
Go ahead show your fucking areas
No shit, we can't kick shit. You could only kick his own dog's poop
I'm a talking to you boy. I'm talking to you little boy. You're talking to me now nigga. I'm talking to you little boy
I'm right here, bro. I'm right here come through. I was talking to sick. I was talking about boy sick. What I'm saying
What I'm saying
Sick is with your brother to me sick say you're like a brother
He went to the methadone
He's withdrawing our phantom
If I met all to your squid in real life, I probably knock them both out
But if I'm at cigarette life, man, you're like a brother to me sick. Thanks a lot, buddy
Sick is a real man sick. Actually don't give a fuck. Did you get like herpes?
Oh, nigga, you won't get some
Oh
PG-13 we're on YouTube come on who are you talking about clumsy
Midnight I got some for you one plus one he goes get the fuck out of here
What why you're what I said you fucking
Let me see major let me see my boy major when I'm crying about where my boy major
I would have seen my dog major when I asked for him
Major is sleeping. He's sleeping in my living room. He's fucking he's fucking turn the camera. Let me see him sleeping faggot
All right, well, dude, I'll take a picture of him
I'll take a picture of all me sleeping in the god
Yo, who do you think called Randy or naughty? Who do you think was on the other end of that phone call?
there's more than one royal family in wrestling.
Okay, I'll show you right now. Look at him.
Aw, come on, man.
How can that let you out? How can that let you out?
What the fuck is that?
That's his dog. What do you mean by that?
Is he pregnant?
I thought it was like a baby or something.
At first.
It looks like Black RG, actually.
Hey, G.
You're feeding him too much, nigga.
My god, he's eating like Carl's Jr. You feed him like old pizza
Yo one time my brother used to drink he used to feed his cat chicken
Like imagine feeding the cat chicken and the cats
Those Western burgers from causing yo screw where my mom took her cat to the bed. They said that cat needs to lose five pounds
Five pounds to a cat is like fucking, you know what I mean? That's like saying do a human being you got to lose a hundred pounds
Like 50 pounds
No, my mom squibber my mom thinks like the way you love a pet is just to feed it
And I try to tell but you there's no talking to my mom. There's no telling
She made my cat lasagna like Garfield, okay, that's crazy
Then he got fat as fuck, huh? Oh, yeah, they got addicted to the lasagna. It's silent
Dicted and this is
Sign is fire, bro. I'm on lasagna. I
Actually respect sing like with like sing sing probably has girlfriends that squirt
So I respect that sings wearing goggles. So like this girlfriend squirts on him like it won't get in his eyes
I love you, sir
All right, that's it. We're out of fentanyl the goggles. He's wearing he's like Horace Grant, basically
Where's your somebody better write lol with that joke or I'm gonna fuck imagine being a pussy and be having
Wait, just from opiates. That's so gay. I need meth. Don't fuck you. I mean, uh, that's so gay
Well, I'm not being a little bitch and go through the withdrawals
Bro, you want to hear about a little bitch like I was yesterday when I got a new phone
My mom was sending me old pictures, so I could I have all my pictures back and one was a rave
And I see Raven I just fucking ball my it's out. That was my best friend right there boy
It's my best friend the dog. Yes, the fuck it was
Give a fuck about your dog
You're done ever one time squid like looking at Raven on the couch being like I know this party can't last forever Raven and
I tried to soak it in and I did soak it in and now she's going to set up my best friend here
It's Kim eating my fucking lasagna and steal my toilet paper to black guy. Thank you. Nothing lasts forever
That's how you sell a joke good times. I know you're watching. That's what else are you fucking doing?
We're gonna be eaten by worms pretty soon. So it doesn't matter
Yeah, the Beatles called squid. They want their fucking haircut back
That's really crazy, that's actually
That's called Rose
I don't know where he's staring at like already so like intently staring at gay porn like look at it
Like oh god, I'd never seen a guy this nude like already blank blank twice if you're fucking alive
He's fucking frozen. All right, it's fucking dick is frozen
This dick is frozen inside of a ass
Already if you're gay, don't move up. There you go. Yo, la la. Where you at? Join my stream, la la
Let's all go to six rumbos. Yo, la la. Let's have a freak off la la
Say are you a bust out of fat nut where you a mod drop your string yard or drop your fucking rumbos
Everybody go over there. Let's go
Joe
What niggas know where to look well trip. Oh
Dude, I would
I would fuck Lala so good that bitch would be squirting nigga. I would fucking Ben Lala around like a fucking oh my god, bro
That's not even know my place went there. I won't guess what
We can go further, baby. Oh, she would be squirting like a fountain
Raining pistol me she would she would be in love with me and she'd be squirting like a fountain
Dude, it'd be insane. I'd be like anybody know why there's like a fountain of fucking squirt coming down to me
Reason oh, that's right. Cuz I just saw my fist up Lala's ass
I just did that to Joe, because he just gave you a golden shower.
I was like, Lala, why does my hand smell like you're Uranus?
You know, Joe, that's an all in it.
That's actually a planet Uranus.
So, you know, you're retarded now.
You're all retarded now, you dumbass.
You're drinking too fast.
Yeah, you're all retarded and shit.
I have an emergency pack.
You mind grabbing it for me?
Well, can you take that bite and then grab it for me, please?
Babe, I'm drunk. I can't walk.
I want to have that bitch Lala squirting bro, she was like Joe, I can't walk
You know what I want you know what I want I want Lala to feel good
I don't want her to feel fucking all over the place shows her tits
Always feels all over the place, and you can see it in her face
I feel bad for them today when la la porn bomb Sam and I'm like all the times I fucking lurk in Sam
Man's gay channel. It's the one time I couldn't see la las tits, but according to he man she man
Yeah, she said like they're far apart and show whatever I'm not judging you la la that's what he man she man said like they're far apart wonky
Why has already been itching his hair and ear for like the last 20 minutes?
Hello
Aldi if you're gay don't move
There you go
I mean the proof's in the pudding guys
All the if you're gay, it's your ear and don't move your hand
Well, say there you go. He's
All the don't don't move at all stay completely stationary if you're a bitch
Well, I couldn't hear you guys now
I got it. Yeah, all the all the
Blank play with your hair like Lala does if you're a bitch
I'm not a bitch, I'm like granny.
Sigs, right?
Yay!
Oh, I fixed it!
I fixed it!
Let's go!
Fire!
and that's how you defuse the
the mic's working yo Scotty the mic's working for you son
nice defuse son that was a good defuse son
it's the earbuds that I'm using like
one of them doesn't work
W
one of them doesn't work oh shit
the lighting I got lighting outside
oh I fixed this one
I fixed this one
fuck
oh stand man's in the chat yo stand man
Send man. Tell us. Why do you love old ladies there, man?
Why did it have sex with a Mike's underage kid and
Tell me about how doing monkey app is pedophilia and you sent money to pebs
Fuck
I definition
I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like
That's crazy you
Something that's real. That's real that motherfuckers obsessed with controller. They probably had a fallen out
They were probably like sexting sending money back and forth. You know what it is. It's a mutual relationship
They understand that this is mutually beneficial. I'm gonna do this and you're gonna report on that
It's literally the same
It's the same shit
It's called yellow journalism it's called yellow journalism
You know, it's funny to me that like that motherfucker salmon he like he'd be calling me a pedophile cuz I do monkey up
But at the same time it's like ETC and pebs they literally showed up to fucking controllers children's fucking school
And he sent them money
Mmm, that's weird to me. That's weird to me
That's definitely too far
That's really crazy
That's really crazy, and I can't imagine a situation that would warrant that
I can't imagine a situation that would warrant that that is definitely unacceptable
That is weird as hell
that's definitely like some israel shit we're not doing this that's what they're doing in israel
Clumsy school is shit like same it makes fun of clumsy Steve like you're missing two teeth
I'm only missing one tooth. Oh
What I respect about clumsy is that at least he has his camera on exactly hell. Yeah, that's that's true
That's true already all these people with zero all these people with like zero cameras
They'd be talking shit about people bro
That's that's what makes it funny. It's like all these people that be like talking shit about other people and the way that they look
They're at the same time. It's like at the end of the day like you don't even
When's the last time you ever put your camera on?
Say man, you've been streaming for like what let me say some orders now. Come on, Sam Man 1k
Yo, the Audi if Sam Man were to show this camera like a year ago or two years ago
It would have been nothing but the longer he goes without like turning on when he does finally turn it on
We're all gonna be like, ah, you are
You can't see it. I said you
Walk you all do you talk bitch
All right midnight, I'll talk midnight you're saying he's talked for years
Mopita doesn't like me and him and his brother turned on me like that. I can't lie
I don't give a fuck about the camera shit is not a flex. Well
Why even make your input if you're not gonna turn your camera on?
Why even talk just stay a chatter
Why even like join panels if you're just gonna like talk and talk and talk
Especially if you're gonna make fun of people's looks and shit like that. If you're gonna be a
That's the key element if you're gonna be a bitch be the whole
Be the whole bitch that you niggas are
In my opinion, just about being the biggest bitch
So what I was saying
Go ahead asshole
That was joking go ahead
Now I was a Urore
All right, I'll talk I'll talk
Sandman like you were crying about how like
Clumsy didn't let you on his panel last night
Whenever I joined your panel, bro
You kicked me out whenever I call you out on your bullshit because you don't want to look like the bad guy in front of the girls
That you send money to Doug
It is what it is, man. It's like hilarious to me, Doug
Oh, why did why did clumsy kick out Sandman? And then at the same time, bro
It's like you got it the other way around. Hold on. They're sending one to him
Let me say one got the other way around. Let me say one more thing
Let me say one more thing
You were make said man, you were making hella fun of clumsy
Because clumsy did the clumsy 1k shit and I told him like to take it off
then clumsy like clipped you saying oh should I make my name Sandman 1k or
should I make my name Sandman Andy oh what happened with that what happened
with that Sam and Sandman 1k or Sam and Andy which one you want to copy
You want to be salmon
Please say some go ahead. Thank you, brother. Like where is Artemis right now?
The shut the fuck up bitch
Where is Artemis 2 right now?
One minute ago, Kim was like, can I get some cubs and noodles, and listen, Aldi,
I know one of those cubs and noodles expired in 2025,
and I sent it there the other day, so when Kim goes to grab them,
I sent the expired one there, and she fell for my trap.
Ha ha, eat those old noodles, bitch!
Cubs and noodles don't expire.
Nigga, yes, they do it says Marsha 2025 nigga. What the fuck you mean? They don't they are you a spiral. Oh, that's just like
That's just the best cell date my dick doesn't I really meant that I did put the noodles that were
Fucking they don't even know like it's complete darkness
That's evil nigga. They're literally in between planets. There's fucking nothing
There's nothing you don't even have you don't even have the waves of the ocean. What are you talking about? There's nothing
Don't have the ways of the ocean signals about to start walking a water look out of the wind shows a black
Blackness nothing
Signals about yeah, let's let's send I'll be going K to do this
Yeah, let's send let's send niggas like Aldi to do this
Oh, yeah, I bet they'd fucking survive do what?
Do what what are you talking about? Yeah, what the fuck? What do you mean? Do what say?
Why are you copying ETC fucking Sam Man's best friend is a like his beard copier coppy copy cat bitch
Little copy pussy cat
Yeah, Joy said me to say kitty gang 50 times in a row like girl
like
37 years old bro like Sam and you're 37 years old yelling kitty gang you're a man bro. Are you a man?
I'm actually killed myself and I ever said I'm kitty gang. I'd actually kill myself. Oh
My god, this motherfucker is trying to be a beat us. Wow
Fourth husband trying to be be this kid. He's fourth ex. He is
Yeah, he is trying to get divorced. Well, are you trying to buy
this bitch a ring? Like you're gonna get divorced again.
They're like, you know, one thing I've always gave that same
and only like he clips everybody and restrains him. But like he
never reclips beat a re like shows her face when she's drunk.
Like you gotta be even show everybody's clip and then whenever
And whenever he gets clipped looking in the wrong, oh, can't review that
Yeah, you know, I already
guarantee you beat insane and fight text each other listen to me already I
Guarantee these faggots probably text each other like oh, I'm gonna go live in five minutes
Will you be there like I can you ever text me same and I'll cut your fucking head off
Well, what's funny is like trip kick is probably gonna make a video about this and I guarantee you I sort of God
Sandman will not review this because it's gonna make his ass look stupid as fuck
Tripping simp that's a bitch tripping simp
Let me tell you one more thing
Okay, where's that old bitch came at?
No, five six, but Sandman is like five five know that came over you
Dude, can you know? No, he's not I bet he's not I bet this is like a six foot three ass nigger
Oh, well said, I'm scared, bro.
Oh, you can't say that.
I'm really scared.
I said, this is what I said about this nigger.
This is what I said before.
I gave him not once, not twice, not three, not four.
I don't even know how many fucking times.
The pull up.
What's up?
Now we're gonna have to do it now. We're gonna have to do it in a boxing promotion
Now we're gonna have to actually pass me a check
I'm gonna lose I'm gonna lose but I want to check at this point
I was ready to lose for free. I was ready to lose for free nigan
Now you're gonna have to pay me a check already for real
Who do you think will win the fight a fist fight say or say a man for real?
Sick would not sick with body the fuck out of Sam and oh kitty
guy save me kitty gang ain't no kid he's here to save you Sam and it's what's crazy is like
a signal would pull up by himself but Sam and he would like probably pull up with other people
yo see go with this five hours from Baltimore nigga drive the Baltimore sick we'll get drunk
you can stay here for a weekend nigga we'll get drunk signals not no yo Joe you say you're a boxer
train me Joe turn me into a boxer I'm gonna hit up a Sandman what's up let's
run a boxing promotion nigga I'm scared I'm a little nigga and I'm scared let's
run a train on signal
Let's run a train on sick. If he drives the Baltimore
I'm gonna knock him out and then steal his car and drive around and sell drugs to my friend
You know signals car goes 150 miles per hour
Exactly he'll be here actually in three hours not six hours. He'd be here half the time crazy frog
Crazy frogs
What's so fucking funny Aldi niggas you didn't knock that too boy look at this motherfucker
It's called Rosie. I got to stay perfectly still in order
Arms will be fucking
Mortars when I get I got to stay perfectly still they be like why is all these arms and legs and rigor mortis?
I'm like, let's just knock that nigga out
The funniest thing to me that I will tell you guys is like, how like all this shit is like, oh my god.
Oh.
I gotta react to like somebody's clip, but when's the funny part when's the funny part? I don't I
Make a why do you call everybody daddy same man, that's crazy to me
If tomorrow beat and Christine gone to a fight same
able to hate Christine, like if tomorrow beat it was like,
I hate Christine.
She talked about me.
Same maybe like, oh, you're right.
She's a bitch.
Same as a little like no offense, same man, but you're a clown.
Like I'm really like, do a real man.
You're a little clown as bitch.
Hey, poppy.
Does he pop your dad?
Oh, God bless America.
Nigga, fuck you.
Hey.
Boppy, hey, you see that with the Boppy guy the guy this is stop calling me Boppy like well
That's how Dominicans are Dominicans. Are they do you hear the other name?
Dominicans think that they're black and shit and they squid the other day when Saman went live. He's like kitty gang
He actually perv
Already the nigga purred he's like
Like Sam and you're actually starting to purr nigga calm down.
It was a black guy.
He said man was a pussy but now he's purring like god damn nigga.
Yeah stop purring my ears Sam.
What are we doing?
That's a little too sexy same man.
Come on Sam and you got to start somewhere.
Right you want to get up to UFC Dana White?
Nigga you got to start somewhere nigga.
that's not going to join us
If I agree with all those world panels salmon, you know, what are you gonna do and be this kiddies dies in a tragic?
Yeah, what are you gonna do just kind of run out of content fair question that is a fair question
When she gets hit by a bus died my cats were fucking she gets hit by a bus
Time to start humanizing it.
That man's gonna like fucking like have like 10 cats to take care of after beat his dies.
I like Sam Man, but it is fun to call him gay because he is kind of gay.
Let's be honest, the guy's a fucking creep.
Not a creep in a weird way, but a creep like in a gay way, Sam Man.
Like, you're always like loving old ladies and shit.
Like, if our grandmoms were on the panel, Sam Man will click the link.
Like, if our grandmoms were up here, you'd be like, oh, I would have thought that.
Somebody better put a low on that chat. I sold that joke
If I don't see a lmao in the next fucking 15 seconds you're old
Don't be mad that I be fucking your grandma and she loves it
Don't be mad
Sandman is trying to copy what I do trying to make it seem like he's not mad
Nick is the maddest ass bitch. Oh, we're saying they was a copy you already been pissed on the floor and throw up every night
Then you be already said we're fucking three hours, bitch
Take a shit in your bed and piss on the ground every night, and then you'll be all these say man about you actually
Well, I'll be all the be everything and all the fucking time of the year
It's in the beer can and then pour it on peach if you're really
Get a turtle fucking hair and spray it all over his ass cheeks. Oh the get a fucking turtle
Turtle shit turtle, I don't know
Dingleberry
I ain't
Well, please don't call names don't call somebody Diggleberry
If I seen you in real life already I'll grab you around your fucking throat and be like what are you gonna do boy?
I'm gonna choke you out
The fuck you gonna do about it punk?
Oh, stop choking me Joe. I thought we were friends have like friends till the end and the end is right now
Next time next time you go live
Sandman, what are you gonna do when I click on your stream and I and I click on that bitch
You're gonna like be like go up all day. Oh, I'll do you. Sorry man. You can't come on here and then I remember oh
You're crying bro
You're crying whenever you were you were crying to be led on
Plumsies last night. That's crazy. I mean man
That shit is so funny to me
Next time you go live send man. What's gonna happen when I when I click on your shit?
You cry yo Kim just said to me a Sam and that guy did love cats and he always says kitty gay
I was like, yeah, that's a fucking retard. Hello
Yeah, that's what he says like oh, where's my Christie my beetle like anybody says a bad word about beat up
We got a ban on because that's my lover Sam and fuck you
Now I like that man. I'm probably I like be the two I wouldn't that's why I'm jealous of you. So I won't I'll be back
This be what I
Would a tie be the joy
Thank you, Sam and you're a bitch nigga
Make something happen nigga
You're really that nigga make something happen. We'll see
But my shit's like fuck
The lighter
Where George, I don't know but I need one you're gonna have to find oh here
You're goddamn right I'm a flat earther and what about it sorry Joe go on
I was going to say if I asked you to dance would you dance, but you were talking about your flat brain or something
You're a flat brain or what is that? No, you were talking to salmon. You weren't talking to me. Oh
If I was thought to say I'm in it like Sam in I want to make fun of your boyfriend
Because you're obviously gay Sam and like where's your boyfriend said Sam and
That I've seen
That's actually rude as hell to call you said that because you are way fucking more real way more of a legend
That's a bad ever. I am an entirely different gradient. I
Would say never change sig but I do want you to just rip that fucking neck beard out for your chance
This is fucking horrifying. Thank you
What's not going?
It's a permanent fixture
Well, I wanted that Kim see it. She is a female Kim. Come here
They'll go
The thing is the thing is I don't care about our opinion. It's a permanent fixture. It's not going
Who's opinion?
Oh
Cam is broke. Cam is like Cam is like such a solid ass girl
Kim is one of the most solid ass girls of all time. She's a real last bitch and she would hold it down, too
If you were to get in a fight if Joe were to get like him say something about six beard
I know I know
What a fucking start skin was to say something about your beard sick Kim would say something
facial hair and certain people do you think Sega's attractive it's a good
track that I just don't know if this is going to be a little bit of a mess.
He got a nightmare from what he just heard.
I thought Kim was going to be like, oh, six beard is this or that.
But she actually was like, he's handsome.
What the fuck? Are you sure, Kim? Your eyes are what I was.
Where would I do?
You have like coma, yes or yes.
Are you but.
You're the last time you got a knife, Sam.
There's a mic in this.
And you need a lot.
No, she already saw you. She said you're ugly.
This guy's psyche was even looking at he's acting like he can't fucking hear us
Stupid retard my phone's dying. I'm a sexual faggot
Get on it man
Guys, how are we doing?
And that's when I come out I'll put the link on every jungle link. He's Trixie. I
Know see I knew guys like sick and it's fun and everything, but I have enough of them sometime
He showed me his wiener recently
Mmm. Oh
Anybody want to donate for some food before the restaurants close tonight a little hungry
Um, gay Jesus. Yeah
Or a psych you good. Yeah, I'm okay. Oh, where'd you go?
Okay, oh, he's back. I know it's sick. Oh, it's cold. I'm here with my man
All these in there. Oh, you've been all the oh, I'm okay. It's like, you know, a little stressful. Oh, you're not my man, bro
Like me and so be easier dating. I
Didn't mean it in a sexual way you faggot
What the fuck?
I mean, it was like a speaker's piece, my man.
Like, you know, like a bro or something, but what the fuck?
Sorry, I loved you guys alone with him.
Everyone okay?
Well, like your your butt body saying man
He was he's been in the chat like crying about like how you betrayed
Beat us and stuff like that bro like that dudes
Saying like that flow has been like
Sending so much money to like fucking beat us kitties that like he feels like he has to defend beat us and shit
I mean
Well, you know what? I'm not a white knight, but I'm gonna stick up for my friends and stuff
It is sometimes sometimes you gotta like sometimes you gotta destroy motherfuckers, bro
Don't don't ever apologize either. Like if you got a bunch of pussies like telling you to apologize to them
Because oh you said something about them and you called them out on your bullshit
You know what I mean, like if you call out somebody on their bullshit
You should not apologize. They get mad because they get called out on their bullshit. Yeah. Oh, yeah
I think maybe you're here. Yeah, like
Exposed some hypocrisy in the community like that is like where it's like I do something
It's like a national scandal. I said the n-word the other day. Oh my god
I'm fine. You could say the n-word. I'll give you the n-word pass
Okay, you have one. I want I need an extra one. I haven't Africa and I'll give you three of them if you want. Thank you
Well, it'll be like a all-time pass. You can say the n-word whenever you want. It's called the Sandman
Well, Sandman Sandman only does whatever his bitches want
He sends money to like oh
Sandman doesn't have content if controller doesn't go live
and judges girls and stuff and like
Sandman only like watches girls that like the girls that he donates to
Don't like
Any reacts to their shit and stuff. Come on site smoke some fucking cracks stop being a crack
I just have tobacco. I don't have like another beer tonight. I'm like fucking happens. Hey, I haven't had fries today
I've eaten today actually, but go back to bed then
No, I don't want your hair leaving you alone with the chat smoke some of your hair. I'll be cool
But you but it will smell like it'll smell like Germany in 1933
hmm
They're like fucking peaky blinders you're fucking smoking
Tobacco and heroin. I think my last hit of tobacco
Rather than yeah, but like I said all I wanted to tell you bro
It's like like at the end of the road don't be listening to these motherfuckers
Trying to tell you to apologize when you call them out on your bullshit
And then what they force you to apologize bro, and then they do a whole last dream talking shit about you
That's like every time
Have a full full six hours stream yesterday. That's
Was a six hours on Christine's six hours on then money for 20s
He's then making fun of my nails and he was a mod in my chat
I mean, it's like I mean, it's like what the fuck is wrong with these people and understand and Amanda
She looked like Ruth Bader Ginsburg. She looks like Roseanne exploded. What the fuck is going on? That's what I'm saying
That girl Christine she tried to porn bomb me on rumble, but like on rumble, bro
Like I don't get porn bombed like this. It's impossible
So whenever she tried to porn bomb me with signals dick
I just put up like a porn video of like black guys fucking
and I just showed her
But I can't get banned
Look, I love his sex a man like right like has to run through the other account. Oh
but you went the link that sometimes it is what it is sometimes it is what it is you know I mean
the content content here's Air Force 10 man Air Force 10 man it's here again
as you guys remember the link is pinned I mean the link is pinned for do you want to kick anybody off the show
and because salmon's coming on 25 dollars you I'll kick them off okay you want to help me out tonight
that 25 bucks 25 no hold on yo salmon if you want to join
$50. Come on. Let's get $50.
He's not going to pay. I mean, he won't. Yeah. He won't. I mean, he won't.
Come on, Sandman. 50 bucks. We need 50 bucks, man.
If I need to send your dick, uh, pick.
50 bucks, Sandman.
Let's go. 50 bucks, Sandman.
Yeah.
50 dollars.
Send your mirror dick pic, please.
Let's go. What?
Well, what are you talking to me like that, bro?
I don't know how you do your nigger ass talking in the chat.
Oh, and turn on your nigger ass camera.
Turn on your nigger ass camera.
Whoa.
I thought I couldn't take the link in and you're crying about the n-word. Whoa
Controls
Nick
God bless America see y'all see you at Dominican
I think a hundred times either night in like five minutes my family's carrying
And that fool's not even black he's not even fucking
Dominican and I have a bigger dick than him, so I'm more black than him. Oh
Let him know let him know psych I do I know
I was told I just don't know what time it is
That motherfucking Dominican know what time it is. He's not black. He can't say the n-word
It's not African. It can't say the n-word
We're gonna come on react to this clip later on Sammy
Yeah, I mean next time you go live react to this gave me for sure next
Next time he does a 50 because he said something rude to me
that's all he has that's all he has left psyche that's all he has all he has is
reacting to controller clips now because his daddy and his mommy etc and pebs
told them but oh we showed up to controllers kids school
Now it's your turn to harass, control, and react to her clips and cries.
Maybe friends with Zayn Pebs?
I don't fuck with them. I don't fuck with them at all.
Okay. Well, I like them.
Yeah, I mean it is what it is like at the end of the day. I'm not gonna be a weirdo
I'm not gonna be like oh you fuck with somebody then I'm not gonna fuck with you
All I'm saying is they get mad like Sam and he always be saying oh all the YouTube monkey
Like you're a pedophile type shit at the same time. It's like
Sam and was sending money to peps whenever peps was trying to have sex with Mike stroke cops underage son
I was just on peps and says with Sam and the other night like told you nice to a row
He was on the panel with me. I mean, it is what it is at the end of day. It is what it is. I
Just don't understand why these motherfuckers be like being weird and stuff like that. You know, I mean a
Lot of these motherfuckers. I just don't understand though either like
The only reason why I'm here psych is because I'm not gay it's not because I know you're
It's because like at the end of the day I don't like how these fools and these bitches
are pressing you because oh you talked some real shit and you said some real shit when
you were drunk and you called them out on some real shit.
And they made you apologize bro don't apologize to these motherfuckers
And then they go and they make hella content talking shit about you
How the fuck does that work?
I don't know and it's like and then I'm not and then I'm not even allowed on the well beta. That's me on beat on her show
She's always like putting me on but Christine. I
She all my all these people pretending to be me are all bad and I'm not even I haven't talked to her chat really like I said
And I'm banned too already there for a hey permer band forever. I mean, it's over. That's so mean
Yeah, it's just weird. It's very weird. And it's like, you know what, well, just listen to what I say site
Don't apologize to anybody stand on your fucking words stand on fucking what time it is. That's right
You know a lot of times it is what it is. All right
I know I revealed like secrets about the period blood and stuff and they have been angry as fuck
Hello
Oh, I think Aldi, Aldi, you recently dropped off.
Hello?
Oh, I think I triggered some bad memory he had.
Yeah, I know what happened to me too.
That's what happens.
I don't know what you left.
I offended him finally.
But he had an important bomb, that's a W for me.
Where'd everyone go?
Well, six still backstage, but nobody wants him,
came to be here.
Let's see what happened.
Let's look at some trip kick video of my show.
And there are better times.
Oh yeah, you know about it.
Z11 knows, yeah, it was spaghetti sauce.
Oh, I'm gonna bring you a nice Italian dinner.
And so, oh, why is it all,
why does it kinda taste cold and a little bit like metal?
Like I'm like copper metal.
Oh, nothing.
That's just like my grandma's secret ingredient.
Yeah, my grandma's secret ingredient, my ass.
Okay, let me see.
I offended, I offended all the off the panel and Stig left and guys, I literally, that
fall see for like three hours and they, I literally left for three hours and with them
on the show the whole time and they didn't born bomber.
It was good.
I'll put the link up again, but I mean I'd rather put on a let me see a rumble one second
One second, what does it say? Oh
Let me play that whole clip of the
I'll play the whole man something I thought something regular YouTube one second
Well, not I'll play the what happens before after between
Hold on
Okay, let's see.
Oh, it's on Trip Flix.
Or Trip Kick.
At least Benny got a kick out of this one. It was fun.
See here it is
No, it's oh, yeah, this is it's kind of talks about something else, but it's not funny. It's not gonna be a
No, it's a theory bitch about be anymore. Okay, share one
Hey, we're here we're here we're queer you stood everybody is the YouTube takeover by the gay guy
Oh, look see there I am
Former friend of ours is saying that me to beat it and I tried to like spiritually traffic her
Chose a house of random
tied up the family at gunpoint
Then ordered his followers to go inside and commit ritual slaughter
I'm telling you, you're doing exactly what I said.
Wondering band of members of a so-called religious cult,
well, a leader they call Jesus,
has had three of its followers arrested.
Called themselves the family, they came and went,
and the number varied from 20 to 30.
Police said they were a pseudo-religious cult.
What do you want to call me a murderer for?
I've never killed anyone.
I don't need you to kill anyone.
Let's take it.
I haven't here.
of that Persian spell put on me.
Great Morse for what?
You people have done everything in the world to me.
Doesn't that give me equal rights?
I can do anything I want to you people at any time I want to
because that's what you've done to me.
You know, if I wanted to kill somebody,
I'd take this book and beat you to death with it
and I wouldn't feel a thing.
It'd be just like walking to the drugstore.
You gonna feel blamed?
Are you mad?
Do you feel like Boots and Bob's representatives
get friends?
Now I'm being called a spiritual trafficker. Well, at least I'm not like a sex trafficker. It's 45th of Gotham 45. Thank you
At least it's not at least I'm not a sex trafficker, but I am a spiritual trafficker and I have a mistress
And she's said I'm not gonna mention this person's name. She's just a psychic
so I won't mention I don't mention this person's name, but she said I'm not even allowed to speak of her but I
Have to respond like when things are said about me like I'm a trafficker
My traffic what I want to traffic you to like heaven. I want to traffic people to like
The hot like the higher up to the north node. I don't I wasn't trying to
Be a beat it and I were not trying to
spiritually traffic her I don't understand I
Didn't like I mean she makes it sound like I like his old plan. I didn't I'm she came to my show
I mean it's like I
Yeah, we're cat-trapping. I don't know what's going on. I'm confused. I'm confused. She says I'm gonna be punished by Bita
Bita owns me. I'm like a goon
You know a certain mutual friend former friend of ours is saying that me to beat it and I tried to like spiritually traffic her
I've never even heard that like spiritually traffic. I mean like
I don't know, I don't know, I just don't understand.
It's like, I think it's just gone too far.
It's like, okay, okay, maybe, see a man with his UGO
turns into like, you know, a trafficking,
I mean, that's like, I mean, that makes more sense than this.
I mean, it's like, it's really, I mean, really,
and it's like, and I think just my,
my like professional psychic opinion about it is,
She's a little bit paranoid like I I'm paranoid too, but it's like she's paranoid. I think like thinking I mean is yeah
Think she's a little paranoid and I hope that she's okay, and I have no hard feeling
I liked her a lot and it's sad that it's come to this like because it's just like what I was told would happen, but
I'm not
That's I'm not like a really any kind of mastermind or manipulator. I do I have I have studied all these kind of things psychology
Carl Jung spirituality the onomatica
It's a you know mind control. I've said all these things
Not to use them on anybody, right? Thank you so much. I've heard birthdays tomorrow, too
I wish we could both have like you know, we're supposed to like you know
Hang out this year on our birthday and that turn out to be like really the opposite
I almost think that it was like I was I feel kind of set up by the situation because she can't she do come to me and then
You know, it's like once I serve my purpose. I guess I was very easily like
Expendable like stay away like she's like I'm so good. She said I'm coming from China stalker
I've stalked other women and like I mean it's just like turning into like some kind of ridiculous thing
And I just fooled her to like, you know
Offer me a three-part series and I fooled her into like coming out and visiting me and I'm just like this like you know evil
Psychic that's mainly theatrical whatever, you know that she got several readings from anyway
so I'm all these bad things and then
My plan failed and now be able to be punishing me
Getting a website soon. Yeah, I'll be like spiritual trafficker psyche or something, right? I need to like start to like fucking
Resorting some like bad bad domain names
It's not easy. They'll turn on every two years. She's turning on Frischalicious, too
Because Frischalicious was that's the thing my vegan Patriot two years ago and who cares
Whatever sweet feet what what what image that stupid picture idea to beat it is it wasn't it wasn't even an insulting image
Wasn't even insulting image. I know everyone warned me everyone warned me. I was but I thought hey
Give the same birthday. She's like, but you know what as soon as
This happened. She's I said I looked at her watching yourself. She's and she's
Mean she says mean shit. She's like, hey, I want to kill these people
I was like, uh, she's like, oh you people are like, you know, and like animals and she's like white people are black and
She just changed just changed completely. I didn't see her saying you that shit
When I was friends with her and all of a sudden she just changed
Okay, got it. You go you go over there. You go talk to her. You know these lot got it first losing things over between us, too
Thanks a lot, you know, they're great like, you know a person to like you know help help in this situation
You didn't do shit. Thanks a lot. All you do is break up break it up a friendship. I mean, it's like so stop me here gloating
dick
Hey
There's a trafficker what it would be who called you anything. Nobody you need to stop and you stop doing it
Stop what? I'm not truly trafficking anybody. I don't work for me. Yeah, what are you talking about?
She doesn't every day. I was trying to kidnap her for there or something like that. I don't know
Yeah, be this every day. What do you mean?
She had to get her episode about me as a trafficker. I have to get I have to at least respond. She's a fantastic woman
She loved bomb the shit out of you convince you you were this amazing talent
I'm an amazing talent.
I mean, if it was a good camera, you probably wouldn't be up here with you, sir.
Definitely not anywhere, sir.
Sorry, that's just blue. I listened to.
Okay.
Okay, a car, a car, a car.
Hey, I mean I'm calm down direct from the man's in cave. This is it
Is that like a is a toadstool from the mushroom or something
The man's in cave with me it's warm in here
Smells like pee though
So that's like 45 year old pee
Hello chicks here. You're going to like it
And then the cave it's cold in this cave
That's where that's what you want. You just want to be on my lap
He's like dad your bear is a mate
Mmm, what else there more clips we can watch you see you watch Chris K and the dwarf
That's funny. It's always funny how he gets a lull.
Okay, let's have a look.
It's a Tommy James clip. He gets pressed for smoking a bull by God.
Well, I don't know if he likes me very much, but I can edit this out. Hold on.
My god, he doesn't I oh, this is I'm sorry Tommy. It's not my most flattering angle
Look at his face right here
Don't get scared Tommy
What the hell is that face for make that face at me
Look at his eyebrows. They're like
What is that like?
77 degrees
coming down his face. It makes
like a little pyramid right
there. Is this Illuminati,
guys? This is the quickest way
to clear out stuck poop. I
have to. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Stop. Stop. Stop. Yeah. Stop.
Please. Not sure yet, guys. Okay.
Over here. A little courtyard
action. This might work.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
What over there?
It's actually CBD, but I'll go ahead and respect that
Well, you can call somebody if you want go ahead and call the cops dude
Well, you're being kind of an asshole
I was being very respectful and you're kind of being a Karen dude
Dude, if you want to be a Karen about it, you can be a Karen
You want to be on film too? I can make public. I'm gonna film you call the cops
Call go yeah, go walk your door go walk your door go call the cops fucking faggot bitch made
Oh, I'll record I'll come closer
Go call the cops lock your little door call the cops Karen faggot
Let's go suck a dick
Thanks for being my content, pussy.
Go fucking lock your door and then try to talk shit out the window, fuck you.
But I'm also not a dumbass.
Call the cops, Karen, I'll be long gone.
I'm not worried about getting a $50 ticket for smoking weed outside.
wish he had a little bit more balls that would have approached me get a face full
of pepper fucking that totally interrupted my sesh what a Karen you're
smoking you don't understand people bro
And I'm only gonna treat you the way you treat me. So I
Don't know. I felt like he was being kind of a Karen and a little bit of an asshole. So I
Will not be cool to you at that point
Tell me I can't film it your shit. I'm in fucking public dude fuck off
Not coming right up to your window and filming you either
But I mean if you're gonna cry
No, and if you're if I feel like you might be capable of doing something cameras going on you, buddy
What's up, man, why do you have a Hitler mustache that's orange which it dude looked younger than me?
Dude would look like he was like in his mid 30s or something
But I know a cop caller when I see one. It's a baby boy. What a yeah, we really has a Hitler mustache
We're the God. He has a Hitler
Hitler I think Hitler exterminated gingers
I thought, yeah, it's a balcony where you should.
I thought about smoking, staying there and smoking.
But my main thing is I'm educated about the law.
So I do know that since I'm smoking pot
and visible public like that,
they can give me, I believe it's like a $50 ticket.
They can give you a ticket.
I just got to mind my own business.
So when that happens, I don't know,
like I don't handle it, awesome.
Hold on one second.
Say, if you want to come up again,
you still owe me for form bombing me.
So you can come up again for $20 to my Ben Mo or cash out.
Cuz I'm like I'm minding my own business and now you're up in my lemonade trying to fucking control me, and I'm all about my freedom, baby
Back stage yes ginger ate off Hitler same reaction as if I was shooting up or something
What world do you live in that you don't think your people are gonna eventually see that that's like
That Hitler don't look
How about that? That's the stupidest thing about this fucking law here and the laws in a lot of places
These ones are German decriminalized by the way. You've decriminalized and rec real ace rec real
Recreationalized marijuana you recreationalized it you decriminalized it quote quote quote air quotes air quotes, but
90% of places unless unless you own
No smoking inside or they can like take your deposit a bunch of shit kick you out if they want
But so I can't smoke where I live, but oh I can't smoke outside
Because I could get a ticket
I'm sure if they want to be asked if they could find a reason to fucking take me away
Just like they did last time take me to jail to let me leave right away right away
what a waste of money I don't think that's a lot of money unless they give you a meal
make more work for yourself because you're having a bad day well I know another good
pot spots dude we're not done I if you can't tell I need to get stoned I'm a young flying
nickel and my weeds way louder than whatever bullshit he's smoking right now
That's what it is. Hey, if you would have came and asked nice, I would have been more than happy to like share
No
Sharing is caring
Fucking crying outside your goddamn balcony balcony warrior a porch gangster
Good porch gangster
over a little bit of weed.
It just just shows you how far we have fallen in this bitch.
Crazy.
A lot of it's geographical though,
and I know where I live.
There's a shit load of fucking Karens of all varieties.
That's why I really fucked with Vegas a lot.
And I fuck with a lot of Cali a lot
because people are a lot more open and just chill.
Especially like Vegas was almost a culture shock compared to like east coast west coast. I
Can't speak much for the I
Can't speak much for the Midwest. I know that the south is supposed to have right. What do they call it southern hospitality?
So I assume that people are pretty fucking dope in the south and from my experience they is
All right, am I going the right way? Yeah, I think
Hey guys, guys, guys, I literally was like making it to half naked today.
I went on to regular BMs.
It's all about our payment.
Fastest way to clear out stuck-ups.
All I made was dollars and ghosts, and it's like, I'm starving tonight.
Like, to be like, I know this will get clipped.
Oh my God.
Guys, I'm literally, I'm like starving.
Hold on.
Okay.
Where's, where's McQueen when I need him? I don't know.
This morning I had to turn on some channel. He was on at like five in the morning screaming at somebody. He's still tired.
What else is there? What if you guys see anything good?
There's Aldi right there. He takes over Sam Ant's panel and he gets clapped, okay?
What's this one?
Tricia Heaton looks great at 67. Here is her. I know what I forgot he performed on me and he's banned from the show
I didn't remind me
And see his band I mean here. This is a good one. I like this one. We're Tommy James
He shops for poop tuna. Why does grandma's tummy look pregnant 32 years as a literal poop surgeon and people still don't believe
Why is everything about fucking poop stop it?
Not that Persian spell, but on me.
I'm nickel ain't done, peeping Tom, peeping Tom.
I'm peeping on you all.
Nickel ain't done, son.
We peep on you.
Come on, keep it up.
I just wanted to come say hi to you, man.
And I hope you have a good day.
If you're around, I'll see you around here.
I'm looking for my brother over here.
He's small, autistic.
He gets lost.
He's kind of hard to find sometimes,
but his name's Sigmund.
If you see a little kid, brown hair,
he's got real big man boobies.
You can't miss him.
If he looks lost, maybe just say,
hey, your brother's looking for you.
Stay here, Tommy.
Oh, mind if I get a hug to smell you a little bit closer. Oh god
Didn't mean to weird you out
My cousin touched my wiener
Any
I wouldn't mind stringing your cheese.
Sorry about that.
Yeah, I haven't been taking mine actually.
That cheese actually knows me and he is spot on.
He knows when I'm not on my meds.
You know that?
Ooh.
You got tuna here too, huh Bob?
Wow
Whenever you have a minute, I think I kind of know
Whoo, I'm gonna be honest with you real quick. It smells like my ex-girlfriend over here
Not in a good way, but that's what we love about seafood, right?
You know, of course, of course, but I just want to make sure that we're going getting the best me for the best price
And then every time I keep thinking about the meat,
no freaky, I smell that smell and I'm wondering,
is that the product or is that you?
Did you need something for me to eat?
You know what, sir, maybe I see you have the tuna.
At least it isn't pooped tuna.
I'm gonna let you go about your work
and figure out what I want.
Apparently I'm not ready.
So let's go, just let me know.
Yes, sir.
I'll be back on the way out.
some goodies too. What you got there are some little taters? Little taters? No, not at all.
I'm just looking around still. Sir, I gotta ask you to leave. We can't have you filming in here.
Oh, no filming. I was watching a movie. Yeah, I can see you filming and we had customers saying
that you're seeing profanity to them. Oh, no, no profanity. Yeah, we need to ask you to leave.
Oh, okay. That's fine, I suppose. I suppose I can respect that. I didn't take my meds, so maybe...
No, maybe that's why he got mad. I don't know
Yeah, I'll just walk out. It's not a big deal
It's not like I'm having a psychotic episode or anything
I'm not gonna do anything. I'm not gonna do anything weird
I'm just gonna leave
Someone said that dive was she pulled out the kid they pulled out the Karen phones on the oh
Oh, are you sure?
Oh, I'm leaving right now. I'm not gonna try to come back in or anything I
Didn't do anything wrong I
Didn't do anything wrong
See then the other one came out the other turn came out what they're gonna come back on me. I'm not doing anything wrong
Pull out the Karen Brigade on me, dude. I
Didn't even fucking do anything wrong
Yeah, she's like searching me down. They're like trying to flag down security or something. This is nuts. I mean, I'm not gonna run
I hate Disney
All right, so let me sit down here
Is it okay if I take my shoes off and kind of oh, okay, cool. So you probably prefer I don't take them off
Sorry, I have a little autism in the way that I sleep is really weird. I usually start with something like this on my back
So I'm gonna just lay back
How much would how much was this again?
If it does that hardness feeling kind of go away, it feels a little hard. I take it the more you
sleep in it and break it in all beds kind of have that. I'm not familiar with memory so much.
This is how it would feel because I can't help but think like
I'm fine. I'm fine. This is normal. I actually do that about every night before I fall asleep.
And I have crazy night terrors. Kind of while I was looking for a bed to help with some of this.
But honestly, even just putting me like sitting like this is putting me in a really dark place.
That was good. That was good. Tommy W.
No, I'm getting up right now. It's gonna take a
Okay, I'm hurrying.
That's you big guy
What did I do are you calling the police on me?
I'll just leave are you calling the police on me?
What after you know him is he a regular guy should I be scared?
Can you tell me what he looks like so I don't get attacked out there
Sorry, that scared the hell out of me because I see everybody looking outside and I'm wondering what's going on
That's pretty scary you guys do. Oh, no problems cute
They won't tell me going inside of McDonald's like last time I almost got beat up by black people at McDonald's
So it was more exciting than just putting filming my camera on the ground. I know I understand
um, I also skipped like
I skipped like a crazy person and stuff and then I'll go to the liquor store too. I
Know but I'm not gonna go
Insult the McDonald's people. I mean these are my local people and I was outside the police station. They just waved at me
But thank you for the advice Q. I know nothing's gonna be I'm not gonna make me some homeless person or anything
But I'll try to do a decent job. I'll try I'll do my best deal with that a lot
Was he dangerous just to have a annoying more than anything
Yeah, they were definitely trying to call the police on me. I'm not fucking stupid
I'm not fucking stupid I'm getting the fuck out of here Jesus Christ I didn't
even get to the other store yet you guys and they're already pulling this shit
on a nickel all right chat be ready for an interaction with the police
apparently they're gonna find me I'm right here
So they're gonna find me. They're gonna fucking give me hell. I might get detained for nothing
Let's just go I think I freaked her out a little bit much with the autism
Yeah, they're all like peeking out the windows looking at me. I'm not fucking stupid
She tells that guy, okay, you call the police discreetly. Why the fuck would you need to call him discreetly?
And I see come on dog
Dude acting like I'm gonna fucking do something crazy
I'm not dangerous, dude. I'm getting the fuck out of there. We're switching we're switching locations
We'll finish our IRL over here on this part
And if something happens something happens
I'll be right back on with you in a second. I have to leave the cave. It's a secret passageway
Oh wait, I made a weird face, I'm sorry.
It's a beautiful night though.
It's a beautiful night in my neighborhood.
A beautiful night for a neighbor.
And not the kind that you're thinking about.
Hey, wait, what were you thinking about? Hey, look at the moon. Do you see it?
How's that for IRL?
See it, I know it's hard to see the moon.
I'm gonna cough. Yeah, I'm getting a medium prize that I, I'm gonna, I kind of probably will piss them off because I said light salt.
So, I did like a little bit of salt, but they're gonna have to like make a new batch.
So it'll be a hot by the time I get there.
W for that tip. Thank you. Oh, look at the moon. Look at the man. Look at the man. Look at the man. Look at the man.
You see it? It's kind of hard to see. It's cool. I should have put on a jacket on. I should have put on my pants and jacket.
Be very, very quiet. KZ might be around.
Or that was more of a black-eyed Andy in the mutation.
Oh look how pretty it is!
You can see the man on the moon.
Would you believe
I put a man on the moon
A man on the moon.
No, I would not believe that.
I think it's all life.
I think it's a lie.
I'm just kidding, I'm kidding, I didn't trip.
Okay.
You waskily wabbit.
That was the real case of the, you know, the chat the other night.
It was cold and my nipples are getting hard.
I'm sorry, that was too much information.
Things I do for content.
Oh, it has this work with my camera at the ground doing nothing Q. Am I doing okay?
You're my best. I mean, there's no there's literally nobody outside. Oh, there's a lady right there
Or man
Yo, guys, I'm just surprised I'm so good right now.
Look how bright the moon is.
Look how bright it is.
Look at that.
The clouds cleared up.
That is a sign from God right there.
See that?
That wasn't not the light, but here.
Hold on.
Look how pretty it is.
Look how bright it is.
I'm not making you want to make her
Out of which I don't know it's it looks pretty
There's a place
I'm lovin' it.
Oh my God, I'm eating my Cora!
Do you ever notice it looks kind of like big boobs?
I know, a little bit. Not much.
I'm the biggest boob out here.
We got here
Well, let me say anything else for you once I got rid of it
I'll send people in.
Okay, I was I was able to order free cheeseburger
It's quiet is a mouse in here. I'm the loudest person
Look at the back workings of the kitchen
This person has a good mail. No way chatter. They're crazy. It's the best part about it
Anybody want a free tarot reading? I don't have my cards though. The ladies, the ladies are super
I'm not, I think they literally, I think they literally have to restart some Friday
Hoopie I got me a free I'm a free burger
You think sound is terrible I
Don't think they have those here. I think that all the fish filet you mean yeah, but they're only 350 on Friday's
Because I can't get kicked out of here. This is like oh, this is like I then I wouldn't be able to eat anymore
Be careful
Any Tommy had a mug
Mocking the McDonald's right now guys. Can you believe it me?
Hmm, I kind of use my imagination or maybe you can put on pink
Colored glasses of them will be
Hello, I'm getting a burger to get cheeseburger. Yeah, I had to add it when she's there. Thank you so much
W you thank you, sir. We're gonna you too. Thank you
Polateness will be you far in life. Okay
They were staring
the guy with my doll's worker had his broom i should have shown you but he had his broom
like not brooming he was just standing staring at me sorry
hi good night guys good night ooh the fries are warm hold on
oh
The fries were free, the coffee was like a few bucks, and then I got a free burger.
So I'm gonna have to double use them all right?
I'm gonna have to double use them all right?
So far, okay.
But I'm gonna get an F because, oh shit!
I'm gonna get an F because I can't hold anything really well.
I'm going to put the coffee down for a second.
OK, nice and easy fries.
Put that in the pot.
Like fries are pretty good.
Light salted.
Oh, good.
I like when they burn your mouth.
I don't even know they're good.
If I didn't say it light salt, it wouldn't be so hot right now.
Okay, I mean that would have been bad
That anonymous donation I would have freakin
Bit out of tobacco I
Would have not had any more alcohol. That's why what I would have just gone a bit
Coffee's fucking hot whoa my mouth is like burning
I mean my other drink already wore off.
I hadn't had a coffee, that's why I'm kinda tired.
I drink when I'm addicted to coffee.
So good.
Now the people here will talk to me.
They're nice.
Hello sir, how are you?
Good, good, good, good, good.
Good, I'm good too.
I'm gonna put this right here, okay?
Like always.
Okay guys, what do we do?
How about one of these? Strawberry, lemon, and another hurricane punch.
Can I get two Swisher please? Thank you so much. Silver is good.
Thank you.
Perfect.
Have a good night
So yeah, that was interesting like I went on beat and show I don't know like my costumes need work
I mean, I was when I had some money coming in I was able to get that wig and that
Outfit on Timo. Those were like good days, right?
And it's like I felt so professional this morning. I like basically just took off my shirt and put like
I like put it into a Daisy Duke style and then I
You know picking myself fake boobs and I put a towel or not or a shirt on my head. I
Think I was okay. I was able to do like a cool background and stuff on the stream yard
I was able to do like a harem kind of thing and I said and I disguised my name to you
I put Siri and princess. I don't think be it was fooled. She just kind of rolled her eyes. Oh my god
Oh, Sy! Sy!
No, no, that's not me, that's Christine.
Oh, that motherfucker!
Oh, wait, wait, Bronson was so mad.
He's like, hey, John, John, John!
Like, you don't know my name is John.
But anyway, I just docked myself.
I just docked the fuck out of myself.
I just docked the fuck out of myself!
I'm just kidding. Hold on.
Hold on. It's like, I can't eat with the...
Hold on. The cradle's just on my boot.
I might do but I don't know where it is.
We'll try.
We'll get cold.
Oh, there's a doggy.
Oh my god, there's two dogs.
I'll go ahead of you, but what kind of dogs are those?
doggy, what's his name? Phoebe. Phoebe, what's that? Milo. Phoebe and Milo, have a good night guys.
See you too.
How's that prior, you guys?
Hey look, I wonder if CB lives there. You know CB, that person? I wonder if CB lives there.
Because her name's on the door.
You know CB? I saw her TTs.
Back stage once. She actually could tie them in a knot and throw them over her shoulder just like the song promised
So here's IRL, this is my neighborhood. Look at these apartment complexes. Wow, what did you like to look like that?
It's kind of suck though to have your balcony facing away from the ocean. I wonder if that's like a lot less because it's like
Oh, it's like okay. I live on the ocean, but my view is of the Bank of America
Right? Where's the Bake of America? My views are the Bake of America, but I you know
It's it's called the ocean view apartments by the way. I have to dox anything, but I
Like myself in this light give me that red
Baby I'm yours
Baby
If I car again
I'll give you the red light, the green light, the green light, the green light, I'll give you the red light, the green light, the green light, the green light, I'll give you the red light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light, the green light
Down her house
Protected by oh, she's a security guard to
She protects this house
I feel safe. I'm sure they should just you see it was it's about beta's name
Directed by beta
Okay, don't don't call that number don't call that number
There's a pier that way, but there's that literally no one on the pier except for like the security guards
So I'm not stopping there tonight. Nope. The fish taco people are long
No poop tuna for us
Actually, it's not poop tuna. It's like probably the best tuna in the fucking world
Fish tacos, baby. Oh, excuse me
Hello
Yo psyche home safely man
I'm doing IRL say I'm doing IRL now or I'm a bit I'm a better streamer than you
Please go home safely
I'm trying to remember when you did IRL in the car
I've done a row driving many vehicles
I've done my own many vehicles in many places. Yes
To get from one place to the other right
That's what well, that's what my feet are for
Right
Cover a lot greater distances with a longer distance vehicle. I don't want to go in it
I'm scared of the world. I just want to be look my local neighborhood really safe with the local police
It's a
Makes a lot of sense
No, I do make sense sometimes I need the local police. I'm getting threatened by bronze chicken
Well, all you have to do is say that you're being threatened by them and tell them that your live streamer
They know they know I told the cop came to know the cop came to the door today. He's like John. Are you okay? I?
Played cool. Yeah, I was well. I was screaming at a beat and Christina. I've been pressed by state troopers and those are about the worst
For you to be pressed by just play cool
Like I said my uncle if they if they sense if they sense that there's something wrong with you
Then that's where they will press you further
He didn't press me for that. He said I said
He said I heard you screaming at the top of your lungs when I was walking to the door
And I was like, yeah, I was like, you know this woman named Bita. I know I say troopers
You do they're just like whatever man
Plenty instances
You think that would work if I offered him a bloat well, I mean, maybe some of them
I cannot guarantee that at the same time
You're probably gonna get in cuffs
The state police are like they like to be serious for the most part, but you know what I'm not gonna say
percent I
Know are you not like bondage? It is what it is kind of a kink for me
Yeah, I know it is what I'd be like you please that's what I do and then and so I'm not gonna
Say that that's what the officer also likes to do
understand
Well, if it was Alex McQueen, it's a hundred percent. Yes
But he's in New York was Alexander
Fucking McQueen
Queen
McQueen
Hello
That's where I am shoe like going to your house where you're like safe
It's right here
Is it isn't like when you're like 40 approaching 50? I mean beat is already 50 years old
Like you're just like I don't give a fuck about my life if I died
It would be a tragedy and it would be something that everyone's gonna be sad about
Is that what it is?
And someone explain fucking fuck this is
There's a fucking blinding me fucking shit
You're psych all 50 years old, so I'm just gonna be a fucking tragedy
It's ever really what we're doing whatever
No, I had to get back in my cave
My seat is called the back cave
No price
Six show weiner. It's nothing
Don't show it. It's not impressive anything to show but you've already seen it already seen it in a brag about
You're all saw I'm fucking trip, bitch
Look at all this
My delicious
Yeah, I'm em knows
That's Oscar de Leon who's that?
Don't is that that's not that's not somebody that's a streamer that I know is alright. I know that last name. I believe that shit, too
Mmm. Mmm. So good
Say what do you have sex the rest of pieces this guy with a good on this guy really knows
music, bro
This is like yeah, I'm not talking about you, but like
You don't know how many bitches I had dancing
We're all shaking their ass to this music nigger. You don't know
No, don't do it. Don't play it. Don't play it
Thank you
So good
And they're all black so good
Free napkins, oh more fries I found
More
He'll go
How are we doing guys
34 people just one with everybody
I don't know like i'm kind of sad because i see like
Chris christine she just started
67 of people she's talking literally about trivia and like
You know needing a sweater and stuff
I'm fucking usually half naked with like, you know the most interesting panel
No, I don't Christine 46 likes psyche probably less than 10 likes on the stream. It's been on for like five
These things happen. It is where it is.
I'm smoking fentanyl. Don't trip.
I'm back.
I can't play the music because it's copyright.
What happened the cats? I ran across and pulled the plug out of my computer
Hmm, but thank you for I thank you for the offer, but I can't do it can't play music right now
Mmm-hmm, that's so good. Where's my bag of alcohol? I
Didn't move and forget it today
There's my alcohol
Oh, there is
Mm-hmm. Oh, God
Mm-hmm. Oh
My discord starting up to say how have you been I will worry about you something. Hey shit. Say are you a trip kick?
Say you hear me you guys I'm thinking you can hear me
Not frozen. Oh my god. I don't know almost almost did it again. Oh, it's tricks is chasing around his mama
Well, that's cool. Hey, are you tripp kick? Do you have the same avatar? Did you ever realize that?
Sick you don't hear me. Hold on
Sick oh
No, oh, oh he dropped. Oh shit
Look, I've never heard sick silent. I think I might be on to something because um someone said that
Tripp kick was a transgender
Yeah, the kitty cat. It's right. Um, this oh it's pepe. Everyone uses pepe. I know but it's like
Oh, lol, don't growl. It tricks you. That's your son
You know, I know it's Pepe the Frog. Oh, yeah, you told me he's like he's like
Tripp kick is a transgender and everyone will just like say oh and that's obvious
And I think you know six kind of transgender and it would be a kind of obvious with the same avatar, but I guess not I
guess not
Yeah, six tripping out. I know he was like
Careful
It's ran aside. Okay, I know every what and not everyone uses Pepe. I don't use Pepe because isn't that some kind of maga shit
I don't like too much. Okay. Hmm
I think mag is just trolling me, you know
So how are we doing tonight, well, I mean it's like fuck
Oh, it's 4chan. I know but wasn't the like Republicans using it or something?
Thought I was kind of associated with the Trump campaign or something, right? Am I crazy?
Isn't 4chan that horrible thing that like that like world of t-shirts, and oh, there's somebody else, too
They they only got trolled to death. That's kind of like the IP so it's almost like the IP2 of like the
of like the reddit sphere
You miss Benny on the show. Benny was on last night and tonight
You know I do think that he was bribed with cocaine to like try to troll me a little bit last night, but hey today was better I
Know but he wasn't talking and it's like I don't want to stare his dumb face. Oh shit
He left I was about to let him I just I seriously clicked and he'd left at the same time
I was about to let him back on to ask about the Simone people
Um, yeah triptych has an avatar of Pepe on one of his channels. I think on the trip flicks channel
Pico gram. I uh pico grams a friend of mine. Did I meet you at midnight? Did I meet you at benny's?
I met pico gram at benny's
And he was there when I was with benny and tried it and so
It was like not I wasn't there. I was what we were all watching them at the um the comic con
um
Yeah
Peacogram the chatter. Oh, no, no Pepe the frog Pepe the frog
It's Pepe or pee pee pee pee I don't know if that'd be a dumb name to name your the name of your offspring Pepe
What happened to Lisa Jordan, she's like she's streaming she's good. I mean it's like
You know, I I noticed like I started like
When I would OB over there people would be kind of like rude like like and like trolling and I didn't want to like
You know bring any harm to her channel. Hello
Hello
It's cute guys, it's not like I didn't ah
Okay
It's scary me
What's up, dude, what's up, how are you? It's having my coffee hot coffee
Can you look really healthy you look good you have a nice you have a nice skin tone. What's up?
Kind of I work in the sun all day. Yeah pretty I'm
I'm like as white as like this is pretty white. I mean, it's like I I haven't been in the sun in years, but um
Yeah, you look good. My scheme is not girly. I've screamed girly before you know, but I wasn't too girl
I was like, ah because I lost my voice because of Christine
Why'd you scare me? Yeah, you know they hate you psyche. Yeah, I know
You know, they want you dead, right? Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. You know, they they will stop at nothing
They hate white people. I don't know if I told you this before I have there
I have the list of people you can go to my
Not my face, but my YouTube community wall. I put a list up there if I disappear or anything happens
Just go to that list and interview those people. That's my message to the police
So you're saying you're not suicidal
Not at all
So if anything happens, they they can't blame that definitely them because I would never do that
And it's like in there and first they tried to coerce, but I said I wasn't as you I see IDL
You know, honestly, I my first
Like the first person I would I would look at is Christine
You know she has a lot of skeletons in her closet. Well, she's on the list, but I think she's second on
And she has somebody, you know, you don't I've only lived like 28 years and I've done some wild shit
I can only imagine somebody who's like 70 they've probably done like a lot of shit
But she keeps saying like go jump off a bridge and if you heard of Isaac happy like he was not suicid al either and
He said it on a stream. He's like if anything happens to me
It was the Illuminati and then he was found
He jumped off a bridge, right? I don't know if you jump them and that's Christine's MO. So is Christine involved with Isaac happy?
Let's think we need to find out. I think we need to find out where Midnight lives and send her some concrete in the mail
No
Midnight. Yeah, the heaviest bags of quick creed so she can drag them around to her backyard
Well, you know what luckily like someone took all the concrete away, but you know
It's like they put it right next to the dumpster, I was too lazy to lift it up
So I just have to but I eventually I was like I got like I have like one or two bags
I just I mean if you were to just leave it there the people would take it like it's valuable
You know what I mean like people people definitely
It's like $1 a 10 pounds. It's like I mean it's that's like, you know cocaine
I mean, it's valuable enough that there's people out there that would love to have it for free, you know
It would definitely like if if I was like Jimmy I would be selling it to people
That's a good thing because they would then they would send like the scrap metal people and I'd be like
Oh, I don't have a bicycle spoons or lawnmower, but if you'd like a free bag of concrete or
then you're welcome to it and
But three out of four tick one or more
So it's kind of like a nice of them proper or selfish feelings like I just like I really didn't have to do anything
It was like, it just took care of it.
You should start giving free bags of concrete
to all the pizza delivery drivers.
I know, but the ladies like, oh, mi esposo, necesito.
Come here, because there's a Mexican pizza lady.
How do you, I don't know how you would say it.
Hey, por favor, concretos, concretos, that's it.
That mean free concrete? I don't know free dust concrete is that's kind of a cute way to say it
But I don't think I mean I mean I think that means fried concrete
Right or fries concrete. I don't know
Well, free dust is fries
I'll say free dust concrete us
And then I'll say buy me mcdonald's fries and you can have a bag of the concrete
I'm gonna have it sign this is free free toss concrete us
one mcdonald's large fries
all the concrete you can carry out of your life.
When was the last time you ate anything
that wasn't McDonald's?
I had Wendy's the other night.
Jesus Christ.
It was actually good.
Yeah, the best part of it was that there was a potato.
The potato's healthy with chili and cheese
and sour cream and stuff on it was delicious.
I'm gonna buy a McChicken Big Mac.
That's called a McGang bang.
Hey, can I come?
That's really I mean that's was really a thing
You know, it's like a it's a it's a code word where you can go there and say the code word if I say people use this
That was a myth people use it
That was like an old internet myth if you went to McDonald's and you could order the Mcgang bang off the secret menu
But that was like an old internet myth from like the fucking late 2000
You know, we've been playing a few of his clips we all laughed he let me give you a hint he has a Hitler mustache
He's a, he's a special person, so he's a special person.
EJ, Tommy J, oh, and one more thing.
It's young Christine's talking shit about me.
I have to find out about this.
Hello, oh my God, oh my God.
He is Hitler.
Hey there.
Oh my God.
What's up?
Oh, sorry.
Hey, Tommy James.
What's up, buddy?
Tommy James, how tall is the grass in Germany?
It's about this high stop it stop it stop it stop it. Hey, what's your hair like all like it looks like you were like a surfer the other day wasn't all big
Oh, I just wanted to get my young area in on it. Oh, but you but you're me so Tommy James you saw that picture of us making out, right?
I want picture
Okay, I keep I can't put it up because you know, this woman is a little bit crazy, but I can put it backstage for you. Hold on
Just look at it. You can just kind of see it backstage. It's hard to see a little bit, but it's right here. Let me see
Downloads one second and this was a shocking picture. I just want to say thank you for coming to my
Okay, if I if I put it up, did you see it? If I put it up, I'll have to
Okay, look at I'll just put it up real quick. Okay. Yeah, just hold on. Just put it up
Okay, take it away. Take it away. Get that get that get that out of here
That's somebody's mind of what they want sexually inside their mind
Obviously, but that's a that's a black woman's fantasy for you. What can I say?
Hey Tommy you look fucking crazy right now
Like I've known you for so long. This is oh, this is a way different like I know you've done the Hitler thing before but like fat Hitler
This is like
The final days of Hitler before he got killed before he killed himself
Public and everything so I don't know
You know like gingers were like the number eight community that went to the concentration camps, you know
100% they've been discriminating against my people for thousands of years. Oh gaze gaze to gaze
Listen, for good reason.
Okay.
Well, you know what?
I don't want to, okay, I'm going to say it for people.
Personally, okay, I was like, I looked at your eyes and I was like, he has that, like,
that, I think Hitler has like 23 degree eyes or something like that.
They go down at a 23 degree angle.
And so do you hope, so do yours.
Like, are you related to him?
Cuz you know people he was maybe they say gay vegetarian you do actually like look like him without like you know
It's it's pretty crazy like the facial structure is there and everything
It's like a lot of when you see something crazy
I have my great-grandfather. I found a picture on ancestry and he's a great-looking younger guy, but when he was older
he's like the spitting image of Adolf and I'll show you a lot of people did look like that
back then though be just because their hairstyles and the mustache so that was this popular style
to look back then too so there were a lot of people that rocked that look it's like how you
see today it's like how you see today like all the edgars and shit
Yeah, that's that's Marilyn Manson. It's a show. That's Minnie Manson
I wish you could choose the rest of this picture. You have to go on discord all I can say is that it's like the most disturbing
Fucking photo I've ever seen in my life
It's like the stomach is it's the steadfast with the I guess the bladder is like full
And then there's like what's near the vagina a microphone is on the vagina. Oh really on the
Yeah
Yikes, it's pretty nice. Let me see. How do I get to this collections? I have this like collection of
Images somewhere around here. Oh here it is. I think it's in here at my albums genealogy. Oh here. He is okay
What are we on? What are we on nowadays Tommy?
What do you think now? He didn't look like Hitler. He didn't look like Hitler. He looks like Henry Ford, okay?
That's what Henry Ford look like a little bit. I know you do. I'm saying he kind of looks like it
I'm I am on only my prescribed medications
When a guy yelled at you were you smoking actually CBD in the park or are you smoking? No?
It was weed. I just fucking tried it. That was being a cloud even smoke CBD
I don't think I was it's not like it's over. Can you is it? No, you can smoke. There's CBD flower. It exists
It's not I mean nobody really does anymore. That was kind of
No, it doesn't get you high that was a little a little fad that happened like ten years ago
People were smoking CBD flower like nobody does that shit anymore
Well, you know, like I don't even think you could find that shit anywhere.
Like you could probably find it in like the bible belt states,
but you ain't going to find that shit.
Like, all right, here's the cops to say, Hey, there's this guy,
smoking weed right here.
Yeah, let's see how fast they respond to that.
Well, they responded pretty quickly to me, like yelling a beater today.
So who knows?
But yeah, well, here's him as a young man.
I'll show you the young man.
He's a good looking young man.
Um, who's that?
My great grandfather.
Okay.
I can see a resemblance between you and him.
Had a little bit, you know?
If you had a family.
Mary's older, and actually when he was real old,
there was a great-grandmother, great-grandfather.
They were really old.
There we go.
Yeah.
Very interesting. I'll show you my grandpa.
Y'all be y'all going and showing pics, but then man, you can't be crying when people start using them pictures.
That's my grandpa.
I mean, he's dead for like over a hundred years, and so I don't, I mean,
I'm just saying because I know a lot of y'all like this to start crying about that shit around here.
Well, they're actually alive and stuff, but they don't have, there's no name, and they'll be alive.
Oh, well, apparently around here, it's like, if the debtor they are, the more impact it is,
it's like, oh, don't make fun of my dead mommy, my dead daddy, like, well, they're dead.
Yeah, well, yeah, I just wanted to take that personally, but it's like, my grandparents,
I understand, it's like, you know, when I'm, you're 45 years old, usually,
you know, they have passed on by that time, and they'd be over in their hundreds by now,
you know, so I understand.
That's like a cave, it's like a caveman with fire right there.
Well, what happened at Christine's yesterday? Just tell me how much you pay for that was like 80 bucks
This was actually I got to get the pawn shop for like 40 bucks in brand new. That's not bad
$150
How's the what's the battery like on it?
Two hours look at midnight. They're not poor family. Do you I mean well
I'm assuming you can just, yeah, you can charge it up, yeah.
And I mean, my name, I like how it does all this.
And you can use it without all that, right?
Like, you can just use it like a regular selfie stick.
Like, yeah, you don't need all that shit.
God, yeah.
It's got all these different settings that you all need to change.
I think that's the same one that Omate has.
Hmm, fuck with it. I pretty much won't go live without this anymore. That's a gimbal. Come on. Yes, you know
Tommy don't know my question. What happened on Christine's yesterday. What'd you say about me?
Oh, uh, they were just all crying about you. So I just kind of shook my head and nodded and agreed.
Okay. No, no, no. Like I said, I respect you as a streamer. And it's like, you know, you're funny.
I'm not going to come up here and lie to you and be like, oh, I wasn't saying nothing.
Was I like talking mad shit, like going in on you?
No, I didn't, because I got the transcript and stuff. It didn't really mention you saying that much.
I just went on and showed my cat.
no pun. This community would be boring if people didn't talk shit through each other. Nobody would
watch. I know. I mean exactly because I mean there's bodybuilders that I think are freaking hot as
fuck and then it's like nobody's in their chat and I'm like wow I have like a chat with like
sometimes a hundred people and it's like that's crazy like this guy's fucking like just hot as
It's crazy
I'm there
Sometimes and it's like, you know, but I guess not people aren't into bodybuilders like I am. I see there's a
Well, no, be well, listen, listen, here's the thing about that. I
Can explain this to you right now when with with women
Like you would think like oh, this is some like a bodybuilder to you. He's like some super hot guy
Women's attractiveness scale is like so varied. You know what I'm saying like you could show a dude or you could show 50 dudes
The same fucking swimwear model calendar and they're all gonna say that all the girls are hot on there, right?
But you could do the same with women with like a fireman calendar and not like they'll be like, oh, no
I like fat guys. I like skinny guys. I like
Yeah, they're all different vexing shapes and sizes. Yeah
Select more of them. They have a better. Yeah, but this is like there's a ton of women out there
Who think that muscular like the super yoked-ass like bodybuilder dudes think that's like a weird look like they think that's like nasty
Looking like it looks goofy. It's like it's like you
gay
And there's some women out there that love that shit
Girls ladies, what do you think Kate Kate careless Kate thought he was hot
Yeah, yikes. Hey, what happened to that one guy you used to have around? What was his name?
Mizer
You've had a lot of people around that's gonna be hard
Like a like what like what around in what context like what was he like?
He used to be on all your streams. I think he was another gay dude
His name was
That's it. What happened?
Um, I don't know. I hope he's okay. Um, you know, it's like, I think like one of the last times I talked to him
He said that he was being you know gang-stocked by the Illuminati and had to like run out of a party and stuff
So hey all that's called meth
That's an enemy. Let's just say it's on mushrooms, but you know, I didn't think I do think he like oh, yeah mushroom
Yeah, just like Tommy is always smoking weed
But aren't a lot of people that do meth, aren't they really actually gang-stopped by the Illuminati?
Yes, I think we're all gang-stopped.
Yeah, you know, because the government's spending a ton of money to follow around a bunch of meth heads and monitor their every move.
You don't need to with AI and NSA.
Like I you know what those people legitimately make me mad because I'm just like man
Like you just you really think you're that fucking special. Don't you like I just want to fucking grab them and shake them and be like
Nobody fucking cares about you
This like AI like
It's like all my AI daughter or whatever
But there's a program where actually that like you can like install it and you would show the Wi-Fi
I can tell where the person is in the house like it like since it like will show like their whole like
Position they're sitting in and stuff like that and I can like download it right now
It's like I was like that's a little bit too interesting
I mean you don't even need all you don't even really need all that if even if you go
Even if you have your precise location like if say if you have an iPhone for example
And you have your precise location turned on you can go on the fucking Maps app and zoom in and it will literally show
Which corner of the fucking house you're in
Yeah, just on regular Apple Maps
It's not hard. It's not so if you stare your location out there with it with people man
Stupid
I don't feel bad, you know kind of like the same thing you giving your number out
Which I do all the time
What was it gonna say?
I put my number out a couple of days ago,
and I got a call from a random private number,
but that was it.
I was kind of expecting a bunch of people
to try to troll call me or whatever,
but it was only one private call,
and I didn't answer it,
because I don't answer private numbers.
I'm not retarded.
Pretty much the exact same thing happened to me.
Both times I put my number out.
They called when I was IRL, which is stupid.
Why would you cut?
But other than that, you know?
And everything do like yeah, I can't I only have one phone. I can't fucking I can't answer
I can't talk in stream at the same time
Lee I can do that at home obviously without a Wi-Fi, but
It is pretty nice to have a chat phone if you can I was paying for two phone lines for a while, but then it's like
Um, you don't even have to do that all you got to do is like if you have a if you're on a prepaid plan of some
Kind just get the fucking the unlimited hotspot for one phone and then hotspot the other one on to that one
It's a good idea. That's actually that's literally my roommate. He
He works he like he uses his phones for work and that's what he does like instead of paying for two plans
He just pays for the unlimited on one and then hotspots the other one all the time
You can actually even take your regular phone and even if you don't have a plan on it, like if it has Wi-Fi, because a lot of them with the Wi-Fi will work, you can just use the disposable numbers, like, you know, the text now numbers.
No, no, no, we're saying like for IRL, like going out like outside.
Yeah, I got you.
I just want to make something be known.
usually clumsy joins, I'm kind of hoping he'll join tonight.
He did scam me for $25 yesterday.
I don't care, I don't need his money.
I just want people to know that this fool's out here
scamming me.
What did you, what was the deal for the $25?
For me to join his stream while the alt
was in his chat to prove I wasn't the alt.
So I did, I showed my hands, the alt was typing
while I was showing my hands.
You know did some bitch, you know, I'm you know, and then after he's like, oh you all send it all send it
He never sent it. I don't need your money
But you shouldn't need this like if you need people to join your stream that bad. Just let us know dude. I'm sorry
That's just
Did my girl crystal and joined over here, right? Yeah, personally has been over a few times. She's cool
That's my girl, dude
like I'm not my girlfriend but like she's my own girl like that's my uh she's a real one
she's a real one i like crystal you want to talk about ginger's motherfucker that's a real ginger
yeah i love crystal she's awesome
crystal is all because she's really nice actually and it's like you know i don't know
people of
And I like either so many people like are like oh this and this and this and like I don't know some of these people
But then I usually meet the people
But and they're usually nice when I meet them and stuff
They're usually at these monsters people talk about the warrior them. Oh, yeah
Why did I take it with the grain of salt every year about people, you know usually?
Hey, we got that look at this one. This one's good. Um strawberry lemon
Lemonade
Hey, I don't care what anybody says, I like Crystalline and I think she's a really funny
character.
The entertainment value is more than fucking anybody else in this whole community combined.
Like her I like Lala and it's like, you know, it's like Lala's been on the show recently and then you know
Like everybody as long as they're not like, you know
Nobody has been through as much shit on the internet and this community is fucking Crystal Anne
Crystal Anne is a fucking gangster in an OG
Gangster fucking a not big big shout out Crystal Anne much love crystal
Um, yeah, that's cool. Nice to see her get around and be back
I like when people leave and then they come back after a couple years as a trip
Yeah, like am doesn't like her. You know who am is I thought I'd be what's happened
Leave they just stop coming on panels and like talking in the chat, but they're there
You're right. You're right. Is it can you see psyche and hearing his shit bugged out? You don't see me?
Very or never mind. I can see you know, it was probably my connection because I switched to mobile data. Yeah
And then
Clumsy and you know
And then Jamie was like, you know kind of mediating like Jamie's a great if you like, you know, you know mods like
like when I was just doing Plain Tarot without like the stream yard or anything like even
before I knew I knew Jamie and like Jamie has been like almost almost every show for
almost two years and they're so nice and sweet and they say man's picking on her like just
because she's like you know I my like modern stuff and everyone loves Jamie like you know
you know Jamie you guys know Jamie's Cowboys boys we miss Cowboys yeah yeah she's cool
Like literally like over like thousands of hours must have been like, you know, just like
Supporting and like, you know, I just appreciate her and I think she was here here, but I think
Yeah
Oh speedy is totally back on that I've been calling this for months and months while he's been lying crying about this is why I don't like speedy I love his content I thought he was a great like streamer the whole tweaking your mind out saying how I know I've done this before but man it's cringy it's cringy him crying
Well, if you if you hear speedy saying the n-word in any capacity, he's using he will not he will not use that word if he's not fucked up
He's on that he's on and literally earlier today
He posted a short where he said it and I was like yeah, he's back on that shit cuz he don't say that shit
He don't do that like fake black accent thing unless he's fucking high
He only does that when he's
To pay and word why you haven't been streaming and have been doing your fake sobriety for two years
You have been fucking commenting on my IRL streams and talking shit. I just I see it. I see it
Don't know why he's got this hate for me. I think that it's cuz I'm like out there streaming and he can't unless he's on
Well, I can stream no matter what I'm on bitch
Ziggy saying hi to us, you know Ziggy you're Ziggle like Ziggy. He's like
Speedy honestly dude. You're a good speeder. It's a good streamer, but you're a faggot dude. Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh
Well, what's my oldest quarter I got here. I think in 1983 is or 80. Yeah 1983
Wow
Midnight, I agree midnight. I do agree and I'm not gonna talk shit on the relapse
I just don't like the I'm clean your IRL sucks
I'm sober and then you're on meth dude, and you're not even doing IRL do better IRL
That's all
So bad go do better
What happened to you he was supposed to show us a wrench and then he saw what happened
I think he might like be grabbing his phone or something to go outside or something to show it up close
Sounds like he just witnessed something gnarly and didn't get it on fucking stream
I was in his house and so he must be running outside to show it on his other camera
It might be really really bad who fucking knows dude
He might be saving someone's life right now like you might be pulling someone out of the car right now
and it's just hold the camera and then you go over from out of the wreck, that'd be awesome.
That'd be great content actually, I want to. Actually, okay, so Tommy, one time I was walking
to the library at like six in the morning and there's this, all these police all surrounding
this homeless guy, the homeless guy's screaming and whatever, then they're all talking to him
and then they pick him up and everything and he's wearing, he's not wearing pants.
Yeah, it was crazy. Uh oh.
Are you okay Q?
He was like he was doing duster earlier in the parking lot and he was driving around in this fucking Mercedes over here
Wait, how do I fucking flip it back?
Like this
Yeah, he was driving around in that Mercedes right there and he fucking smacked that Nissan pulled up and just fucking cracked it right there
And then yeah, he was huffing duster in the parking lot earlier. They're singing songs. I remember
And the guy in Mercedes helping Duster.
I haven't seen anything that sad since that woman who was like.
No, well, that's the 2002 Mercedes.
You could buy one of those for $4,000
on Facebook Marketplace, that ain't an expensive car.
But if anything, you're dumb for buying one of those
because the maintenance on that thing
is going to be fucking ridiculous.
Yeah, that's a fucking S500 Benz.
That's like the top of the line fucking Benz.
That thing's going to be stupid to take care of.
Yeah
Mercedes SUV and it melted eventually they kept it, you know, it's okay. Oh, yeah, because Mercedes decided that they had that they were gonna use
Biodegradable wiring harnesses in the early 2000s models. That was a great idea. I think that's what mine
Yeah, I think I'm biodegraded and I melt they came they came up with this law
Where they said like one part of every car sold had to be biodegradable and Mercedes was like
Maybe let's make the electrical system biodegradable. That's a great fucking idea. Yeah, oopsie oopy
Yeah, I don't know. Yeah, I think I have a lot of people mad at me right now
We actually I don't know if you know Amanda Eric's and but like she's been screaming about me and then like
Like, you know RG's like open this picture up and it was like it turned out to be her I guess but
An O4 Acura TO will better have the manual because the automatics and the other thing will be destroy itself.
We're all dancing. Oh, he's soft.
Okay. He's too cool to dance with me.
I want to dance with Tommy is you don't know Tommy Tommy will dance with anybody
I've seen Tommy dance in fucking naked before forever. You couldn't make it
Well, be to said he was dancing his underwear once he turned around and it was like I've seen Tommy dancing his underwear more than
I've seen myself wearing underwear
Yeah, I'm pretty sad.
I'm gonna bring it back.
I'm gonna bring it back?
Yeah, it's gonna be a new trend.
Hey, I was basically dancing in my underwear today.
I'm like, Vita's a little bit.
And that was fun.
I'm gonna bring it back.
Actually, I was like, because I guess,
AM, you know who AM stands for?
She was like, she said, I'm stealing her act
and I'm trying to steal her thing.
And so she said, I'm actually gonna be taking injections
and having a sex change and to become a black woman.
And so I just went with that story line today.
I think I was like, we should go.
Yeah.
I said, you're still kind of new to this.
You're still kind of new to this whole thing,
but eventually you'll just learn to have fun with the Alex
thing.
You'll just learn to laugh at it.
I'll try to do it.
You have to try to do it.
Like literally she's actually like doing very bad things to me right now and no you think that she is you think that she is
But she's really not like let me she's like it seems like it, but I promise you as somebody who's been in this
I've had a website made after me Tommy's been through it more than anybody besides maybe just Jen like come on
We know
Yes
I was re-streaming her shit and she literally gave me my first ever copyright strike the first time I ever got one with her actually.
The only people who have ever copyright struck me is Blackout Handy and Alexander Manners.
But luckily when I'm sure you know when you get your first copyright strike they just make you go to like copyright strike school like and make you watch a little video thing or whatever so luckily I was able to get off of it with that you know just watch the little video and get off of it.
After that, I just learned how to uh, I learned how to play her shit without her being able to do that, you know
I know yeah, I mean it's like you should be able to use these for fair use
Especially if she's like you making AI with my picture and actually she's talking about me on her show
I play two minutes of her show and stuff
I mean it's well, yeah
I mean a lot of the times it is fair use a lot of the times the shit does go down as fair use
But YouTube is more on the thing where like they're gonna shoot first and ask questions later
Like they're gonna believe the they're gonna take the video down
and then worry about the details afterward, right?
And then they're usually gonna start,
they're usually gonna start with the fucking person
making the complaint, not the defendant.
Right, well, I've been, I mean,
I've had my channel taken down four times.
One time I was just deleted.
without any like explanation or anything.
And then it came back miraculously.
Like, you know, they brought it
into three clues later or actually three clues.
Thank yous over here, like, oh, has she ever fucking,
she ever copyright struck your channel?
Yeah, in 2023, this is how long
this shit's been going on for like,
like yeah, she got that for like a long time ago.
We've been dealing with Alex forever, forever.
There's Jamie's Cowboy. He had a Jamie's Cowboy. She's just
We just laugh at her at this point. She's just she's just fucking nobody takes her seriously bro
Like nothing that she says like I wouldn't even put any stock into it
She's literally just there to get you riled up
Me and a meme of me as Tyrax and then with like two little boys that she's their Betty and Joker
And me and a truck say oh, I like to pick up young boys and stuff like that
I mean, that's what she does, though, but she can't like no offense like you, but you don't have a job. What is she gonna do to you?
She got me fired one time, too, by the way. Oh wow. Well, yeah, tell me tell me you and I are like she was saying
On the other night, it was just about like you and me and stuff the other night and about like
Losers and because we don't have a family and she said we don't have a family
We're not we don't have kids and we're not married and we don't have a normal job and stuff and and and we do drugs or something like that
And then as like doesn't she do all those things? I don't know. I don't know
She's literally been kicked out of sex parties for smelling like fish. I don't give a fuck. Listen
I, all I have to say is my greatest get back ever was her approaching me while I was in
the middle of a crack fentanyl and X-Binge.
claiming she was my girlfriend, lying to the community saying I'm her boyfriend.
So I rolled with it. I got so many donations. She made so many videos. Love bombing me again
after she has said and done so much. CPSed my sister. Docs my house. Sent the police to my house.
Got me fired. Claimed that I'm a predator and a trafficker. All the same shit. Racist. All this
How do you do that and now it's documented that you love me and all this shit
And then she just got mad because she couldn't control my chat if I would have like a block to amber and just Jen for my chat
I could have got more donations and kept it cracking. Yeah, but you know I don't
It's like, yeah, it's like it's worth it to like have, you know, it's like have people tell you how to run your chat and you can talk to it.
That's where the joke, that's where the joke or the buddy troll ended with me.
But yeah, I went along with it. I love you, baby. Oh, I love you so much. Send me another cash app.
You know, it's all good. She deserves it. She totally makes, you know.
Deserves everything she gets she deserves is to be as lonely as she's gonna be when she passes into the afterlife
God bless her soul. I don't even want to like
Bottom of my heart is like I had a good six month run with her as friends and you know what she turned on me
Because I said are you turning against me and that was all
But I'm not gonna hate I'm not gonna really hate bond with you about it because fuck hate bonding and for two
I lived with her for a month like I know her
I didn't know her, so your reaction is a joke to me.
Okay, good, I know, but I did meet her too
in real life, so, you know.
I had lunch with her, dude.
I didn't know her.
Actually, I had dinner and then the next day
we went to Hollywood together
and like walked around for a few hours.
This bitch literally brought me around to her family
for Thanksgiving.
It's not the same, Psyche.
I know it's not the same.
I'm saying that I fucking met her too.
And I think she's the only person I've met.
Constantly feeding into it and crying about it.
It's never gonna stop.
Just laugh at her. She's a joke.
Well, I do sometimes.
I mean, I was like having a good time showing the memes.
I was laughing at the memes.
But it's not going to be good.
She'll get bored.
I should move on to somebody else.
Yeah, I don't know.
She'll get bored and she'll start talking
about Tommy or Goodtimes or Janigan or me or whoever.
I know.
But I remember that, right?
I was on peps and zays the other night and it's like, I just like,
I was like, I just apologize because it's like, you know, I mean,
But at the same time you went on pebs and Zea last night
Oh, no, he's been he's been going on pebs and Zea there. They're the besties now
Why why cuz I like pebs and I think they is cute
Oh, the groomers cute is grooming cute too. You do like Benny bonko. So I would be oh,
Benny grew me and Benny and he was on the show tonight, by the way
You grew me is on just it's a streaming taught me you grew me. It's a joker. I mean not in a bad way
I mean it's like they like basically told me. It's fine. You guys
Today you both like younger people
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
but I think we're just more friends and stuff
and it's kind of joking around about other stuff.
I'm not, like I dated a woman
that was really in her fifties and 250 pounds and stuff.
That was the only, that was my only relationship, okay?
Like literally, that's my only,
I've never even dated a guy or anything like that.
I don't really even like sex really, like, you know,
as like, I'm like, because it's always boring to me.
And so I don't, I get to go on Grindr every day,
literally if I wanted to,
and hook up with a different person every day
if I wanted to.
But I don't, oh, kitty cat, oh, kitty cat, oh, kitty cat.
Hey, baby.
Kitty cat.
Where's your brother at?
Where's your brother, Ginger?
Did you go to the RV with Benny Q?
I've actually met Benny twice.
I've been to his house.
Oh, wow.
Oh, yeah, he mentioned that tonight.
I mean, he said that you're kind of like.
Are not friends anymore or something you said you did something that little that little fact
It just does nothing but lie about everything that's that's my problem with him
And then after he hit his mom, I was just like I don't even want to fuck with you anymore
It was on my show tonight that I've never met before his mom
Well, yeah, they're all fucking listen. Here's the thing. They're all it's like
I don't know if you know this and I'm not trying to say this like talk shit or anything
They're all on fucking blues. You know what blues are
What are those?
They're they're fake fucking per their fake perks for fentanyl pills
Well, I mean
Like literally on my stream as nine several times. He's like did probably they're all fucked up that why do you think Benny is the way that he is?
Nothing blues and not go. Why do you think Benny is in a physical altercations with his parents?
Fucked up in the head that dude is literally a serial killer in the making
He was saying some shit last night where and he was like saying he's evil then he said he's in the gate program and other ginger
I
Benny had a stream where he fell asleep standing up digging in his own ass. Remember that? Yeah, you did and BG still has that clip somewhere
I know BG still has it.
The first night I watched his show, he fell asleep on his couch for like 6 hours and I was just doing terraries in his cat
and then he was like, he looked up at his shirt and he just like scratched for a while
and then I told the family that it was funny.
That's not called falling asleep psyche.
Oh, he's nodding out or what?
Yeah, that's called being on fucking drugs, bro.
Like, he's an alcoholist.
I know what the difference is between falling asleep
and being knotted out and being half awake, half asleep
on drugs, like half coming back to.
Yeah, he did.
He said it.
He told him he threatened to punch his mom again
on the stream.
And I was like, oh, fuck, I'm going to be in trouble.
He's like, and he calls him bitch.
And then he just laughed because I don't know.
It was just crazy.
It's just crazy somebody I'll never forget he'd be he'll be crying about the miscarriage. I never got to play with toys as a kid
I used to chop wood, I used to chop wood, and cook dinner for everybody else.
Yeah, just like at the RV, he was the tallest guy on the RV too, right, by the way.
Yeah, he was the biggest dude on the RV.
He was the smallest guy, he was scared of saint.
He was begging me to drive him home because he was scared of saint.
He was like, Q, please drive me home, please take me home.
He's well, he's a shot manak remember that he was like bro. I'm scared. I grew up in an abusive household and saints
Just going crazy right now. Please drive me home. I swear he said that to me on my mother
I believe this too.
I saw, I know I saw, I think he was cheeky Andy or somebody else that wanted to fight
with him and he would got like, you know, he got like really, and I think Trident got
between him and the guy and got the guy down or something, but it's like, yeah, that was
saying, that was saying, he got, he was scared of saying, bro, he was, he was scared of fucking
saying, and I was behind the camera for that.
So that for that clip, I'm the one holding the fucking camera.
How about big pipes, you know big pipes big pipes was like, you know, oh, yeah, we all know fucking we all know big pipes
That dude is a serious fucking weirdo
Yeah, Big Pipe sucks, we all smell of smoke.
Oh yeah, well Big Pipe, yeah, I mean it's like,
he was like, he started playing his banjo
when I'm like having a serious conversation with somebody
and he'd be like, then he starts singing.
I'd be like, I'd be like, I'd be like, I'm mutimating so bad.
We're like, oh my god, not the time.
I mean, I don't care if he plays like a song and stuff,
but he was like literally, you just hear strumming
and then we're talking to somebody and he starts singing.
And we're like, excuse me?
I don't know.
And he was a spy for AM at the time
because he was a streamer of the year.
Like two times streamer of the year or whatever.
I was like, wow.
He's getting some intrusive thoughts
about sitting on that thing.
Ooh.
And also sit on the gimbal
Yeah, well, yeah, so he so basically how this went for a long time right psyche he lived in his he was living in his parents
garage inside of his dad's yellow fucking broke down Corvette inside of the garage.
Basically, he was working as a waiter.
He was waiting for his grandparents to die so he could get the inheritance.
Fuck it black. He was so he that's what he said and I'm pretty sure that happened
And that's why he's not streaming anymore because he got his money
Yeah, I forget you you have met like a fair amount of streamers like a lot of streamers. I meant I'm not not a lot
I mean a couple I met
Dominandy some it's an enemy. I meant chicken thing
blade
any of you want to consider him a streamer, VB, all the people, all the other people that are
just kind of like somewhat streamers. I met Trostmo here. Yeah.
No, actually, I was, I was, I met stroke off.
I
Do you gas I was one day away from I was I almost met vegan patriot
But the day after I got the John D gas house was like the day before the day after she left
My favorite dance like she left that day and I got there that day
This thing was you've met but you've never met any of the ones that I've met. That's weird
i've been on the east coast for so long it's true we're like on the opposite sides of shit
but that's how you met so many people you've been east coast and now you're west coast you've
met a lot of streamers and gathers was it that rolled up on you like that was the best dream
when you're talking to like
I know you're the gay black guy.
Well, when we being pulled up on you was hilarious.
I was just like, I think you're like,
urgh, think you're the main thing is that wild
when she pulled up and she was gonna.
She was tweaking, she was tweaking, bro, she was tweaking.
It was a wild clip, dude.
How'd she think, get in, get in, come on, get in.
And of course somebody said that they were somebody said that they like clicked on to that stream when that was happening
And it was like when you load in the GTA and it like loads into Trevor
Like this is like a movie right here
Anybody says she was she was content. I don't care what anyone says
I well, I think he's coming to say, you know, but he has his personality that it's like, you know
I met him we get along for a day. Then like you probably punch me the face at some point. Maybe kill me
I don't know. I mean, you know, I don't know what would happen, but
Maybe I'm
No, you wouldn't do it
No, I the only reason I did that with Mike was because I told him I was gonna do it before I ever met him. I
Told him I was gonna fuck him up before I ever met him because he was a predator
Yeah
So that was already that was already dude. I didn't just pop off on him for no reason
I already told him that shit was gonna happen. Oh, that was that was tight
I was like through his ass to the ground
You can a few months a few months before that me and him were on blackout 80s panel going back and forth
And I was talking a bunch of shit to him about cuz he was like
43 years old feeding dex puppy meth and shit. She was 19. Like that's weird. Obviously, I'm not gonna say like, obviously, yeah, she's over 18. So you can't say he's a pedophile. But like, listen, if you're 43, and you're fucking with a 19 year old, that's weird, bro. I don't care what the law says about 18. And like, no, dude, 43 and 19 is fucking weird. Like, why can't you can't even get a chick that's 29, 30, 31?
about the pdf thing but when he was 29 he married like an 18 or 19 year old woman
and stuff and it's like but he's so like you know I don't know it's like and then
he's like oh well he didn't have a really good explanation for it but
I talked to Dex one time on Benny's panel and then her boyfriend or something sort of
threatening me and like it was just-
Yeah, that's Krogoff.
You're talking about Krogoff.
Krogoff?
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Oh, that's that was Mike. That's Mike Mike. He's been on my show, too. And it's like, yeah
That was him
I mean, he's the only boyfriend that she's ever had on stream like that's like, I don't like who else would have been
No, well, she was with IBL way before like he was ever a streamer that was all years before like he was even a streamer
That wouldn't be that wouldn't have
I've been streaming for maybe like a year and eight months and I've been like doing open panels
He was he when when Dex puppy was with fucking IBL this was like I still thought that was in 2024
Yeah, yeah
24 maybe this is when vegan patriot first went fucking homeless, you know, I mean like long time ago
Message hold on a second. Yeah, so I'll do
Everyone's having a good night. I think we're having a good panel. It's kind of like this is my like
We'll still get to having bros
We'll get you know
Like really in my life. And though it's like even if you guys don't really like me
It's like at least we can like have pretty good look at that fucking tail dude
That look at that cat is a monster that cast this cast not even six months old yet. It's already a monster
It is a monster. Maybe it's part of making you go into something because I have a cat like that.
Dude, honestly, I was thinking like, I was looking up what a Maine Coon looks like because I was like,
Ginger, are you a Maine Coon? But now I, she doesn't have that. He doesn't have the kind of face
of that a Maine Coon does. Yeah, well, you are fucking huge. Look at those muscles.
Yeah. Let's see if I can find it. I had a fucking good looking kitty right there, dude.
I have, I have a picture, I have a little thick little licks and we see cat licks, uh, my cats are like, this is like, like, my cats are like,
Bubs is fucking, Bubs is that weird, Bubs is just some like weird old lady or something, or somebody who's trying to like, pretend to be a weird old lady.
I'm not sure who Bubs is exactly.
it's
How about
Yeah, that's elder worship, I think
She's she was nice to me
They'll be nice to you when they first talk to you but like when you know as you've experienced when you spend enough time around them
They'll turn
Well, Christine, I mean, it's like her ego.
She went in for like, we beat it for like,
months and months and months to get like,
before she started her channel,
and then she was able to like, transition right into like,
50 people, people who are chat and a big chat,
doing super stuff like trivia and like, talk to them.
It's easy to leech off that.
It's easy to leech off the drama community, bro.
Hey, like, hey, it's beautiful to me.
And then all of a sudden I, like, I've never had like,
you know, bad numbers ever since then and stuff.
not like I'd be used for anything because I was just like I liked her for like her cat I saw her on
on um on on jokers channel like showing her cats I was like this is lady with a crazy voice
I think we need to come back in the game and start doxing some of these old ladies we need to get
them out of here what have you seen oh yeah cue and tell me have you seen this picture look at this
look what I made last night this I was so proud of this this is what I made last night um and I
hope you guys think it's funny but here you go this is what I made last night get a man
She told me to jump off a bridge several times and she's like went the harness and stuff.
So I did like I said, you know, if there are like little witches out there and there you
go.
I also made another one about Bronzebird.
If you know Bronzebird, this is what I made last night.
He's fat, or I couldn't I could never have imagined
No, that's what he looks like
That's him. Yeah, I got his picture. Yeah
They all look the same
It looks like I'd call the police on him just for walking down my street
Help us
Looks like Barry a little bit
Shout out Barry haven't seen him
So I get sent all kinds of shit for people.
Is that because he's a little white knight?
Oh, he was telling me that he said he's going to squat me today on beat-a-dove.
He said, he's going to squat me about 10 times.
The police are coming over for a brother attack.
And then he said I just named my name.
And then he started threatening my family and stuff.
So I don't care.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
And I was just laughing because he was always in his pee-pees.
I'd hardly got him, and even Beatty was like,
Bronzeberg, shut the fuck up.
And I was just laughing so hard.
It was the best day ever.
It was the best day that day.
Absolutely.
No, Link, I gotta leave you all, but I'll get
put it down right now, hold on a second.
But tell me, I do like you, and I hope you don't mind, I played your clip of smoking
in the weed and then going into the supermarket and stuff today, but you've grown on me, you've grown on me.
I hope you don't mind. I'm probably gonna leave the stream for other reasons, but um, I hope you don't mind like if I share, your, your cash
I don't care. I don't care about that. Okay. Okay. I didn't like know that I, I'm sorry if it wasn't like, you know, I didn't ask you first or something.
I don't care dude. You're good.
Drop the, I dropped the link right there.
I'm gonna say it real quick, but for why I'm still on here, I do appreciate you letting me on here, letting me hang out for a few chats.
know what time it is. Yeah, I
just want you to know that.
There is like, there are
even, even, you know, I'll say,
okay, I'm blessed that these
are new. I love and I've seen
how it is from the bottom of my
heart. Oh, nice. Hey, look at
our, look at that. Is that Mog
It looks like my god.
Oh my god.
Imagine when I'm looking back at you.
Yikes.
Imagine that looking right up in you.
That is.
Oh.
We have Ziggy coming on.
What's up, Ziggy?
Do you remember that picture?
Ziggy.
Yeah, what's up, man?
Tommy left.
Hey, what's up, Ziggy?
Do you know Q?
Like you left you they don't like you or something. What's going on? They just like ran. I don't know. I I don't know
I haven't seen them in a while
Yeah, I mean Z. I mean Ziki's a cool guy. I don't know Ziki actually looks like you know the singer of Good Charlotte
He doesn't I thought he was him for a long time, but
No, I knew I know I like Tommy and Q
No, Tommy said it'd be back. It wasn't personal. I think yeah Tommy said it would be right back
So I think he wants to say hey to you. Hey, Ziggy's a cool guy
I haven't actually seen his picture
I just saw someone had a picture of like the good Charlotte guys like this is and they're like everyone was like is that Ziggie?
Some people have seen are you have a girlfriend now Ziggie or what? Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, that sounded like kind of like a lie
No, no
Why would you say like that like you sound like geeky like, okay?
Ziggy likes dude. I've hit on Ziggy before and he's like no man. No, no, no, no, and then yeah
He's tried it with me. Nope. I'm good. Nope. Not even like one time one time one time one time
No, that was you and a beta
Oh, that was me and Vader. Oh, yeah, Vader and I got my speedo for Vader and then Vader's like show me more and like
I thought my things be on my head. Yeah, and he
He was on my show last night. Vader showed back up in my he was Lord Vader showed back that last night in my chair
God
Fuck he did. No, man. Tommy Tommy's cool, man
Like he like is a rapper and he does all kinds of cool shit, man. Yeah
Tommy was funny. He's funny. He's funny. Um, yeah, yeah, have you ever seen um, you know who Chris K is?
Yep. Yep. Have you ever seen his fight?
No, no, oh one time he was in Vegas, I guess and
I think it must have been like, some kind of reunion of 80s.
Dude, if it comes down to Chris K, you would have to ask Q,
because Q would probably remind me of stuff with Chris K.
No, Chris K literally wants to move in with me and start chatterbaiting with me.
Oh shit, like literally like like he's like he's like and then he was like hey, he's like well
He's like he's like hey
Yeah, he's like you are you I was thinking like you know suck a dick or something, but he was like
He's like, so you wouldn't fuck me in the ass instead?
I was like, whoa, I was like, I don't know, the first date.
But maybe, I mean, maybe.
What the fuck?
Yeah, I'm not sure.
But I mean, he's a nice guy.
I don't want to be weird.
I mean, don't make, dude, don't paint to the public.
I'm not painting anything.
That's what he said on my show.
he actually did. Yes. What the fuck. He said all my show. Yeah. That's crazy. Hey, how
about this? Hey, this is Laurie Diamond and Tommy James versus Alex on salmon. I've done
salmon if it's okay. But let me see if I can find the Chris K thing. Chris K. Oh, here
it is. You want to watch this? It's only a. No, I can't watch. I don't look. You can't watch.
No, I yeah, no, go ahead. Okay. Thank you so much. This is great and I'm just started up. Okay, there we go
You know a very long time with
What do you do buddy?
Hey, you can't brush it!
What's happening?
What are you talking about?
Man, what's up?
What's up?
Fuck is bigger
Now what?
Get that!
Yeah!
You don't want nobody out to bring it around here, back that!
You know what I'm saying?
Back that!
Get it on there!
Get that on there!
Back you don't want nobody out to bring it around here!
Now what?
Exactly!
How was that?
Did you burp right there?
Holy shit, fuck you, bitch!
Fuck in the- Oh, no!
Fuck in the-
Come on, man!
Okay, well, Tommy and- Tommy and fucking, uh, QRU-
You wanna get your ass?
I- I was too, like-
Okay, can you turn it off?
Yeah, Tommy and Q was to the L was to but man and be nice to fucking fuck the Tommy again at least
No, Tommy said he'll come back up. I'm gonna get the link up down again. Tommy can come in a few minutes
You like that clip guys?
Fucking guy
Then he like hurt his hurt his leg and stuff
I'm gonna start with a robot. Yeah, I have a robot that I made you have it
It's gonna like run the chat for me first like I'm gonna send a start it up once I got to go
I have to pull it give a robot. What are you talking about? You know, have you heard of nightbot?
Oh nightbot. Yeah, no, but I've been my own nightbot
I've made my own and it goes under my name and stuff
But I can't imitate it or pretend to be a real human so it's under my name and stuff
I know like
Blah blah blah. I made it on cloud code. I made it with cloud code and I designed it and everything
I'm gonna start my robot
Yeah
Well, are they coming back up or if they're not, I'm going to leave, man.
I was coming up to hang out with them too.
Go then, go then, go then.
I mean, he said he'll be back in a few minutes.
I'll hang out, but I mean, I thought they were coming back.
No, they are.
Like, well, Tommy James at least is coming back for sure, but I don't know what happened.
I don't like it.
I think you love because Tommy left and then it's like it would be kind of it's kind of too gay for him to be alone with me
And so it's okay
It's so gay, that's why that's why I'm saying it like Tommy come back
Well, it's okay
A little bit let me just touch your leg and put my hand
No, don't touch me what are you doing?
Don't touch me I was just it was just a bro bro tap
No
Okay
Okay, my balls will pack back pack themselves up and leave. Oh your balls. Oh my god. Now you're getting me thirsty
Whoa, bro, come on come on pay attention to your channel, dude. Oh, yeah. Oh, we have a guest was almost to talk to you, okay?
Yes
Ziggie stop lambing for a minute sucky. I really want to talk to you sucky
Oh, tell me what do you have to say? I fucking love you for these reasons that I'm gonna state right now
That you put up with these old women calling you all so you did this like you did that
At least you don't tell down to them at least
Fucking men
Then listen, shut the fuck up Ziggy when I'm talking to my boy, Suggie.
You never count down from Suggie.
When Beta came up on the fucking hill, everyone bowed down, everyone bowed down and then he went, nope.
No, listen, Ziggy, Ziggy, do me a favor.
When I'm talking to my friends, and I'll have to review Ziggy, I'll talk to you in a minute,
but do me a favor and shut your fucking mouth for one second, you understand me?
When I see Suggie get attacked by these cowards,
These cowards that team up on him.
That'd be what the fuck you laughing at, motherfucker.
The fuck so funny?
When I see this Cowboys attacking Suggie, I like this Suggie don't Suggie could be like, oh, I love you guys
I'll be I'll be your friend Suggie fucking trolls them back. That's why I love my boys. So you understand me
Ziggie you understand that lamb about that you
Hey, you don't say that to me
Whenever I'll take a fucking bullet precisely. I'll take a bullet precisely. Thank you
Bullet went whenever whenever a look when a fucking beetle was picking on everybody and shit
And it's like he was like nope. He went nope
I was like listen, I love being and I love psych. I love them both
But I see when a person's getting attacked and that's what psych is getting he's getting attacked by like
Like they all team up on him. I don't like that shit when people team up on a person
It's like every gang of these people, the Hepper Gang, the Broom Gang, the Kidney Gang,
fucking whatever gang. Like you're still standing. You're still standing!
I don't look as maybe like good as I used to like you know a year ago, I made it to age like 10 years
in a year. But you know what?
I've never been about being bullied into submission.
I've never been about, like my dad always is like,
you know what, you be proud of yourself,
no matter what you, no matter what you are,
my dad would always tell me this, right?
And he's like, he's like, you know, never be like,
never let anybody tell you you're less than them, you know?
And I don't, like he may have said you're better than them,
but I would just say, hey,
We're all equal in certain ways and like no one's better or worse than anybody else. Maybe maybe some people are worse
But uh, here we go. There's uh, who's that?
But the fuck be careful that could be a
It's cute. It's cute. Is that Harriet Tubman? Yeah
Don't do that
Okay, they gave the middle finger